<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.5.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251216000000 +0800" stop="20251216003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Kumar Vs The World</title>
    <desc lang="en">Swipe right or swipe wrong? Kumar dives headfirst into the chaotic world of modern love — dating apps, ghosting, situationships, red flags and a whole lot more. Are dating apps killing romance? All this and much more on Kumar VSModern Dating!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216003000 +0800" stop="20251216013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">FBI: Most Wanted S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Fugitive Task Force relentlessly tracks notorious criminals on the Bureau's Most Wanted list.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216013000 +0800" stop="20251216023000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Patagonia - Series 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over six stunning episodes, expert local crews join an international team of the world's best wildlife filmmakers to explore uncharted territory, discover new species and tell an urgent environmental story. Patagonia travels the 2000-mile length and Atlantic-to-Pacific breadth of this vast, enigmatic region to illuminate five distinct terrains: majestic mountains, the far south, dense forests, hostile deserts and breath-taking fjordlands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216023000 +0800" stop="20251216033000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Press Your Luck S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hosted by Elizabeth Banks, Press Your Luck is a game of wits, strategy and even higher stakes as contestants try to avoid the iconic and devilish WHAMMY for a chance at life-changing cash and prizes. During each game of Press Your Luck, three contestants compete against each other, answering questions to earn spins on the Big Board.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216033000 +0800" stop="20251216040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Donal's Irish Adventure</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the Emerald Isle as you've never seen it before, as we join Donal and his faithful dog Max on a culinary road trip around Ireland, discovering the people, places and ingredients that make it magical. In each episode, Donal will be cooking up a local dish, from fresh lobster rolls on the dramatic coastline of West Cork to oyster shooters in Galway's picturesque oasis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216040000 +0800" stop="20251216043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216043000 +0800" stop="20251216053000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Expedition With Steve Backshall S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this truly global series, three-time BAFTA-winning adventurer and wildlife expert, Steve Backshall ventures into uncharted territory in pursuit of new discoveries and world firsts. On 10 unique journeys, Steve scales unclimbed peaks, uncovers life unknown to science, meets local people and shines light into caves that have been dark for millions of years. Shot in stunning 4K, this is a beautifully filmed journey into the unknown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216000000 +0800" stop="20251216010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">斗罗大陆之燃魂战</title>
    <desc lang="en">全大陆高级魂师学院精英赛决赛后，唐三与小伙伴们依依惜别，他们约定五年后再聚首，随即分头踏上各自的人生道路。武魂殿比比东暗中布局，横扫几大宗门，妄图称霸斗罗大陆。于是唐三集结伙伴们创立唐门，秉持对正义的追求，坚定扛起重任。他们合力勇闯海神岛，对抗武魂殿，不畏黑暗势力和强权，携手维护全大陆和平，匡扶正义，共同成长为不屈不挠的战士。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216010000 +0800" stop="20251216020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">詹姆士出走料理 V</title>
    <desc lang="en">《詹姆士出走料理》以寻找詹姆士私厨菜单为节目主轴，为了寻找记忆中的美味料理，詹姆士将带领大家探索市场，品尝在地美味、寻访料理达人。并在节目中展现特殊食材的处理方式、尝试新的酱料或是新的料理作法，制作创意料理(料理教学)，最后在节目片尾时作出一道『詹姆士创意料理.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216020000 +0800" stop="20251216030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">咖啡乌.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216030000 +0800" stop="20251216040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">咖啡乌.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216040000 +0800" stop="20251216050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216003000 +0800" stop="20251216013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">天伦之情</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 新的视频证据曝光，将道贤与尚哲的死联系在一起。 同时，尹松接到治焕的电话后，立刻赶去寻找他。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216000000 +0800" stop="20251216000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216000300 +0800" stop="20251216010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216010000 +0800" stop="20251216013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216013000 +0800" stop="20251216020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">We use our bath towel daily but how often are we washing it? Steven Chia sends our viewers' bath towels to a lab to find out what could be growing in them, if they're not washed often enough.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216020000 +0800" stop="20251216030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216030000 +0800" stop="20251216040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251216040000 +0800" stop="20251216050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>