<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.2.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20250909000000 +0800" stop="20250909003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Provocative</title>
    <desc lang="en">Amira tries to convince Aida that moving away from Irfan's family is the best way forward. Caleb reels from the news of Tess going back to Pierce.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909003000 +0800" stop="20250909013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">FBI S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Special agents Maggie Bell and Zidan from the New York branch of the FBI work together to keep the city and country safe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909013000 +0800" stop="20250909020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909020000 +0800" stop="20250909030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sitting on a Fortune S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Players can win up-to 100,000 in prize money in this high-stakes, high-tension game show hosted by Gary Lineker. But with no lifelines or chances to walk away they will risk everything on getting the right answer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909030000 +0800" stop="20250909040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo UK S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909040000 +0800" stop="20250909043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909043000 +0800" stop="20250909050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cooking Up A Fortune</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brand new series where the UK's most passionate cooks get a once-in-a-lifetime chance to launch their own food brand to the British public. Cooking Up a Fortune sees amateur foodies, who dream of escaping the rat race and cooking for a living, create and sell their dishes to hundreds of real diners in a purpose-built food arena. Each week the winning kitchen gets to launch their idea for a food business to paying customers in one of Europe's busiest food markets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909050000 +0800" stop="20250914223000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Great British Bake Off Series 11: An Extra Slice</title>
    <desc lang="en">Each week, BAFTA-winning comedian Jo Brand shines a light on all the goings on from inside the tent. With the help of a celebrity panel, Jo serves up an extra helping of unseen moments, as well as devouring the tasty offerings brought in by the studio audience. Jo and her panel are also joined by the latest baker to leave to get all the gossip from their time on the show. And Tom Allen appears as a regular guest, reviewing audience members' bakes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909000000 +0800" stop="20250909010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">长风渡</title>
    <desc lang="en">扬州布商之女柳玉茹自小遭遇生母病重、庶母不慈、父亲不重视的困境，她不得已谨小慎微，做了十五年模范闺秀。不料，对婚姻抱有憧憬的她却被被家里安排嫁给了名满扬州的纨绔顾九思。顾九思也误会柳玉茹是因为攀附权贵才嫁给他，对其嗤之以鼻。柳玉茹幡然醒悟，不能将命运系之婚姻，系之他人，决定跟随顾母学习经商之道，真实、独立、精彩地实现自我价值。经过刻苦努力，柳玉茹顺利通过了顾母的考验，生意上逐渐得心应手，更是在此过程中改变了对顾九思的看法，发现其至纯至善、炽热真诚的一面，两个人的心也越靠越近。然而此时，扬州节度使王善泉凶狠毒辣、倒行逆施，导致百姓流离失所，顾家不得已举家逃亡，原本奢靡无度的顾九思看着万千流民，一夜之间长大。为结束混乱局面，让百姓安居，顾九思从捕快做起，官至户部尚书，与志同道合者扫除积弊，轻税轻徭。柳玉茹则内修善堂、外建商交，使得物资繁盛、百姓安康，两人共同谱写了一段盛世佳话。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909010000 +0800" stop="20250909020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">詹姆士出走料理 V</title>
    <desc lang="en">《詹姆士出走料理》以寻找詹姆士私厨菜单为节目主轴，为了寻找记忆中的美味料理，詹姆士将带领大家探索市场，品尝在地美味、寻访料理达人。并在节目中展现特殊食材的处理方式、尝试新的酱料或是新的料理作法，制作创意料理(料理教学)，最后在节目片尾时作出一道『詹姆士创意料理.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909020000 +0800" stop="20250909030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">想握你的手</title>
    <desc lang="en">以本地的社会时事为骨架，描述同一个邻里几个不同背景的家庭，如何由冷漠自我，到最终了解何谓"爱"。故事反映了血浓于水、守望相助、远亲不如近邻的可贵精神。新传媒艺人黄文永在此剧中饰演父亲，是一家咖啡店的老板，为人节俭，有三个女儿，分别由林湘萍、李心钰和蔡佩璇饰演，而陈丽萍则饰演文永的妻子。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909030000 +0800" stop="20250909040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">想握你的手</title>
    <desc lang="en">以本地的社会时事为骨架，描述同一个邻里几个不同背景的家庭，如何由冷漠自我，到最终了解何谓"爱"。故事反映了血浓于水、守望相助、远亲不如近邻的可贵精神。新传媒艺人黄文永在此剧中饰演父亲，是一家咖啡店的老板，为人节俭，有三个女儿，分别由林湘萍、李心钰和蔡佩璇饰演，而陈丽萍则饰演文永的妻子。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909040000 +0800" stop="20250909050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909003000 +0800" stop="20250909013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">台风的新娘</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 姜海用殷瑞妍开发的面膜谎称自己独立完成了面膜改版。然而在尹清风和台风的追问下才发现，原来姜海擅自挪用了别人的产品。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909013000 +0800" stop="20250914233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">台风的新娘</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 清风无意间发现了瑞妍的钥匙圈，并怀疑她就是姜风。另一边，遇见了神似允熙的女子后，白山开始怀疑允熙或许还活着，便打算着手调查此事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909000000 +0800" stop="20250909000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909000300 +0800" stop="20250909010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909010000 +0800" stop="20250909013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">I Am a Hawker: Bib Gourmand Edition follows Singapore's most celebrated hawkers—those who've earned and fight to keep their Michelin Bib Gourmand. Each episode spotlights one hawker's journey through tradition, innovation, and the relentless pressure of holding that title, revealing the personal stakes, sacrifices, and resilience behind every award-winning dish.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909013000 +0800" stop="20250909020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909020000 +0800" stop="20250909030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909030000 +0800" stop="20250909040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world._x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250909040000 +0800" stop="20250909050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>