<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.2.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20250817000000 +0800" stop="20250817003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Incredible Tales S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Short supernatural stories that are inspired by popular beliefs or myths in Singapore and in the region.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817003000 +0800" stop="20250817013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Transplant S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bash treats a man with a rare medical condition. Mags gets a visit from her parents, and goes above and beyond for a pregnant woman with an undiagnosed condition. A misunderstanding with a rabies patient lands Theo in trouble. June and Novak negotiate a tentative working relationship. Devi starts to make changes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817013000 +0800" stop="20250817020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Unbelievable Moments Caught On Camera S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">Voiced by Alexander Armstrong, the programme travels around the globe - meeting the people who filmed these amazing clips to get the stories behind the footage. Unbelievable Moments Caught on Camera features incredible, eye-witness footage shot by members of the public.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817020000 +0800" stop="20250817031000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">MasterChef UK Celebrity S18</title>
    <desc lang="en">This programme features UK celebrities who will compete against each other to win the coveted cookery competition title.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817031000 +0800" stop="20250817033500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S41</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Sajak hosts his final season of Wheel of Fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817033500 +0800" stop="20250817040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S41</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Sajak hosts his final season of Wheel of Fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817040000 +0800" stop="20250817043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Weather Gone Viral S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">From whirling tornadoes to torrential rains, to harrowing hurricanes, Weather Gone Viral gives viewers unprecedented access to some of the most insane meteorological moments from around the world. Featuring videos of the most extreme and destructive weather conditions, firsthand accounts, and professional meteorologists sharing tales from the front lines, viewers get to experience the fury of Mother Nature.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817043000 +0800" stop="20250817050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817050000 +0800" stop="20250817053000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Planet Action S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Planet Action takes you behind the scenes of the best action movies released. Each episode you'll get all the secrets straight from your favorite action heroes, get exclusive trivia and special reports from the most dangerous film sets, and get insight information on how the filmmakers make giant monsters come to life. This show is a sci-fi, cowboy, world-destruction, action-combo that will literally blow your mind!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817053000 +0800" stop="20250817060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Deal Or No Deal Australia S12</title>
    <desc lang="en">The exhilarating hit game show where contestants must beat The Banker to win a huge cash prize, is making a triumphant return. The ultimate contest of nerve, luck and pure gut instinct will be fronted by one of Australia's most beloved TV presenters, Gold Logie winner Grant Denyer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817060000 +0800" stop="20250817063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Hiccup And Sneeze S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hiccup and Sneeze are two young forest monsters that snuck in one day out of the rain. They are a brother and sister, who liked the place so much they decided to stay. (Monsters sometimes do that and it's not even considered rude - but that's just monsters). Anyway, they're all living together in Bibi's magical house even though sometimes Hiccup and Sneeze don't really understand that being a monster and being a human are two very different things...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817063000 +0800" stop="20250817070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">In Our House S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">IN OUR HOUSE is full of surprises and is more interactive and energetic than you have ever seen before. In an entertaining mix of song, dance, music and drama, join the wacky hosts as they introduce the LETTERS AND NUMBERS OF THE DAY and the adventures that they encounter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817070000 +0800" stop="20250817073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">123 Number Squad S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Number Squad is called in to hunt for coins and collect the correct value needed to make another wish that will restore everything back to normal when a wish at the magical fountain went wrong._x000d__x000a_Shelly asks for the Number Squad's help to look for different instruments for Sticky to play with his remaining 6 arms as a surprise to cheer him up as he has injured 2 of his arms in a drumming mishap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817073000 +0800" stop="20250817080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Hobby TV S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">From playing with skateboards to collecting stamps; from building models to drawing comics, hosts Randall and Gus show kids the ins n outs of hobbies – the wacky way!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817080000 +0800" stop="20250817081500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pororo the Little Penguin 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Pororo and friends in their fun adventures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817081500 +0800" stop="20250817083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pororo the Little Penguin 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Pororo and friends in their fun adventures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817083000 +0800" stop="20250817090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Songs &amp; Stories</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enjoy the best of Pinkfong's most loved songs and stories with all your favourite characters!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817090000 +0800" stop="20250817091500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Catch! Teenieping</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Princess Romi accidentally let go of her magical fairies, called Teeniepings. She and her friends are now on a mission to catch all her Teeniepings!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817091500 +0800" stop="20250817093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Catch! Teenieping</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Princess Romi accidentally let go of her magical fairies, called Teeniepings. She and her friends are now on a mission to catch all her Teeniepings!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817093000 +0800" stop="20250817094500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Chimera Keepers: Adventures with Incredible Creatures</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Thelma and Wendy on an extraordinary summer adventure, discovering the unique and magical Chimera creatures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817094500 +0800" stop="20250817100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Chimera Keepers: Adventures with Incredible Creatures</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Thelma and Wendy on an extraordinary summer adventure, discovering the unique and magical Chimera creatures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817100000 +0800" stop="20250817101500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dogmatix and the Indomitables S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Idefix and his indomitable friends Bantera, Stamina and Gluttonix are back to resist the Romans! There's no doubt they will triumph through their unwavering friendship and combined talents, in 52 new and unprecedented adventures filled with adventure and humor, by Toutatis!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817101500 +0800" stop="20250817103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dogmatix and the Indomitables S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Idefix and his indomitable friends Bantera, Stamina and Gluttonix are back to resist the Romans! There's no doubt they will triumph through their unwavering friendship and combined talents, in 52 new and unprecedented adventures filled with adventure and humor, by Toutatis!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817103000 +0800" stop="20250817110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Agents Of Sprawl</title>
    <desc lang="en">Norman runs out of power and collapses. So Zayd and Meiling do their best to lug the unconscious Norman back home to his "mother". But they'll need to escape Zero's mind-zombies, who are eager to steal Norman away. To make things worse, "mother" mistakes Zayd and Meiling for bad guys!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817110000 +0800" stop="20250817113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Transformers: Earthspark S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">After the end of the Transformers' war, the Malto family moves to Witwicky, Pennsylvania, to start a new life but their lives soon get entangled with a group of Terran Transformers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817113000 +0800" stop="20250817120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Totally Spies S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three teenage girls from Beverly Hills attempt to balance their lives as high school (later university) students with their undercover work as super-spies, battling an array of bizarre criminals!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817120000 +0800" stop="20250817123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Omega</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Malay) There are many universes, they may be similar, but they have their own characteristics, as in the case of Omegaverse. A universe that's similar to the original Ultra universe, but has its own ultras. Omega is a Space Garrison rookie who was sent to Earth on a mission to protect it from monsters that appear mysteriously.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817123000 +0800" stop="20250817124000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Grizzy &amp; The Lemmings S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarious misadventures of Grizzy and the Lemmings continue... now in unexpected places around the world!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817124000 +0800" stop="20250817125000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Grizzy &amp; The Lemmings S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarious misadventures of Grizzy and the Lemmings continue... now in unexpected places around the world!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817125000 +0800" stop="20250817130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Grizzy &amp; The Lemmings S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarious misadventures of Grizzy and the Lemmings continue... now in unexpected places around the world!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817130000 +0800" stop="20250817133000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Johnny Test S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of average suburban boy Johnny Test, who wittingly plays test subject for his genius twin sisters' various experiments, reluctantly fighting evil villains in the process.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817133000 +0800" stop="20250817140000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817140000 +0800" stop="20250817141500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Jungle Bunch S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Jungle Bunch tells the story of a group of loopy animals fighting injustice in the heart of the jungle, where every being who faces a problem knows who to call...."The Jungle Bunch: to the Rescue!".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817141500 +0800" stop="20250817143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Jungle Bunch S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Jungle Bunch tells the story of a group of loopy animals fighting injustice in the heart of the jungle, where every being who faces a problem knows who to call...."The Jungle Bunch: to the Rescue!".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817143000 +0800" stop="20250817150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Groom My Room S11</title>
    <desc lang="en">Host Charmian Tan, flanked by a creative Interior Designer and two handy Room Groomers, answers 13-year old Naisha's cry for help to transform her worn-out room into a spellbinding place. Mustering all her powers, this spirited young wizardess is ready to embark on a memorable 48-hour room makeover journey and make her magical dreams come true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817150000 +0800" stop="20250817184500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">National Day Parade 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">NDP 2025 celebrates the nation's 60th birthday with the theme “Majulah Singapura” and pays tribute to everyday heroes and pioneers who have shaped the nation's journey, while embracing the hopes of future generations. For the first time, the parade extends from the Padang to the Marina Bay and features dynamic military displays, light projections and a spectacular fireworks finale. (Live Captions).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817184500 +0800" stop="20250817191500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (Malay &amp; Mandarin Speeches - With English subtitles and Sign Language Interpretation).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817191500 +0800" stop="20250817200000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chef Jonathan revives a lost Nyonya dumpling recipe for a 93-year-old, stirring up taste memories and rekindling ties to cherished Peranakan roots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817200000 +0800" stop="20250817211500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (English Speech - With English subtitles and Sign Language Interpretation).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817211500 +0800" stop="20250817220000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817220000 +0800" stop="20250817230000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Asia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Vast deserts, dense jungles, polar landscapes and tropical seas are explored in this dazzling journey across Earth's biggest continent, Asia. Witness the breathtaking variety of Asia's wildest places. From the vast Arabian Desert to the unexplored jungles of Indonesia; the biting polar wilderness of Siberia to the tropical coral seas of the Indian Ocean. Dramatic wildlife stories are captured in extraordinary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817230000 +0800" stop="20250817230000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Fighting with My Family</title>
    <desc lang="en">A former wrestler and his family make a living performing at small venues around the country while his kids dream of joining World Wrestling Entertainment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817230000 +0800" stop="20250818010000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Fighting with My Family</title>
    <desc lang="en">A former wrestler and his family make a living performing at small venues around the country while his kids dream of joining World Wrestling Entertainment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818010000 +0800" stop="20250818015500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">LEGO Masters USA S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">This returning series brings imagination, design and creativity to life when teams of LEGO enthusiasts go head-to-head, with infinite possibilities and anunlimited supply of LEGO bricks. Teams of two will compete against each other in ambitious brick-building challenges to be crowned the country's most talented amateur LEGO builders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818015500 +0800" stop="20250818035500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">You Might Get Lost</title>
    <desc lang="en">After the tragic death of her son, Arlene loses everything, her husband, her home and she starts to lose her mind. When the mysterious Endeavour Institute offers her a chance to travel back and change things, she eagerly accepts and begins her journey to the past. Plagued by the memories of her alternate reality, Arlene must separate the real from the false without upsetting the delicate balance . She is unprepared for the terrible price she must pay for saving her son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818035500 +0800" stop="20250818044500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Modern Marvels: Food</title>
    <desc lang="en">Modern Marvels goes straight for the taste buds in an all-compassing celebration and exploration of food. Celebrated food expert Adam Richman crisscrosses the country taking a deep dive into how food products are made, detailing both the process of the craft and the inspiration behind the ideas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818044500 +0800" stop="20250818054500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Survivor 46</title>
    <desc lang="en">18 new castaways battle it out on the islands of Fiji for a million dollars and the title of Sole Survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818054500 +0800" stop="20250818060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Just For Laughs Gags S24</title>
    <desc lang="en">Just For Laughs will tickle everyone's funny bone with its hilarious practical jokes, hidden camera pranks, and other creative hijinks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818060000 +0800" stop="20250818061500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Alvinnn!!! &amp; The Chipmunks S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">A single dad has his hands full raising six rambunctious chipmunks in this animated comedy!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818061500 +0800" stop="20250818063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Alvinnn!!! &amp; The Chipmunks S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">A single dad has his hands full raising six rambunctious chipmunks in this animated comedy!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818063000 +0800" stop="20250818064500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Galapagos X</title>
    <desc lang="en">Four kids from the future, which is a troubled one, come to the present to help us prevent climate change problems. No more strawberry Jam? What will I put on my toast! Our team Orchid, Zephyr, Rae and Oshie are dispatched to unravel the mystery that is Dr. Crock, our super-rich social media entrepreneur/philanthropist kidnapping all the bees so she can monoplize honey products - candles, shampoo and cereal - forever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818064500 +0800" stop="20250818070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Galapagos X</title>
    <desc lang="en">Four kids from the future, which is a troubled one, come to the present to help us prevent climate change problems. No more strawberry Jam? What will I put on my toast! Our team Orchid, Zephyr, Rae and Oshie are dispatched to unravel the mystery that is Dr. Crock, our super-rich social media entrepreneur/philanthropist kidnapping all the bees so she can monoplize honey products - candles, shampoo and cereal - forever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818070000 +0800" stop="20250818071500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Chinese) Super BOOMi follows an animated bear and his friends as they learn and play in a virtual reality game universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818071500 +0800" stop="20250818073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Chinese) Super BOOMi follows an animated bear and his friends as they learn and play in a virtual reality game universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818073000 +0800" stop="20250818074500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Blippi Visits</title>
    <desc lang="en">Come explore the world with Blippi! There are so many exciting things to explore and learn. Feed your kids' curiosity while they learn about vehicles, animals, the natural world and so much more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818074500 +0800" stop="20250818080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Blippi Visits</title>
    <desc lang="en">Come explore the world with Blippi! There are so many exciting things to explore and learn. Feed your kids' curiosity while they learn about vehicles, animals, the natural world and so much more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818080000 +0800" stop="20250818081500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Leo The Wildlife Ranger: S3 Spinoff</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Junior Rangers come across a crocodile that is having the worst of days. Nothing seems to be going right for the poor reptile. The Junior Rangers help it out as the crocodile encounters various issues throughout the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818081500 +0800" stop="20250818083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Leo The Wildlife Ranger: S3 Spinoff</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Junior Rangers help a family of Asian House Shrews overcome obstacles in their path to escape a hungry predator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818083000 +0800" stop="20250818090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Songs &amp; Stories</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enjoy the best of Pinkfong's most loved songs and stories with all your favourite characters!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818090000 +0800" stop="20250818093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sesame Street S52</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elmo's newly-adopted puppy Tango joins the show in a new recurring animated segment, "Elmo &amp; Tango's Mysterious Mysteries"!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818093000 +0800" stop="20250818094000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supertato: Sr1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based on the bestselling books by Sue Hendra and Paul Linnet, this brand-new action-packed animation series follows the adventures of Supertato as he and his fruit and vegetable pals do everything they can to try and stop Evil Pea. Each episode brings new challenges and hilarious silliness - from riding an out-of-control toy dinosaur to building a baguette rocket to visiting the stinky cheese moon in the deli aisle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818094000 +0800" stop="20250818095000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supertato: Sr1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based on the bestselling books by Sue Hendra and Paul Linnet, this brand-new action-packed animation series follows the adventures of Supertato as he and his fruit and vegetable pals do everything they can to try and stop Evil Pea. Each episode brings new challenges and hilarious silliness - from riding an out-of-control toy dinosaur to building a baguette rocket to visiting the stinky cheese moon in the deli aisle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818095000 +0800" stop="20250818100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supertato: Sr1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based on the bestselling books by Sue Hendra and Paul Linnet, this brand-new action-packed animation series follows the adventures of Supertato as he and his fruit and vegetable pals do everything they can to try and stop Evil Pea. Each episode brings new challenges and hilarious silliness - from riding an out-of-control toy dinosaur to building a baguette rocket to visiting the stinky cheese moon in the deli aisle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818100000 +0800" stop="20250818103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">123 Number Squad S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Farmer Haywire invents a feeding machine for the animals. However, he is too busy to use it, leaving Number Squad to work out how much feed is needed for all the animals. The Farm is having a baby boom! 5 different animals have had babies today and Farmer Haywire is going to need a lot of help to feed all the different mummies and babies and that will require a lot of maths!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818103000 +0800" stop="20250818110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Paw Patrol S10</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everyone is ready for the Monster Truck Championship! But when a pup named Boomer takes his motorized mischief to the streets of Adventure Bay, will the PAW Patrol be able to get the race back on track?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818110000 +0800" stop="20250818111500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Chinese) Super BOOMi follows an animated bear and his friends as they learn and play in a virtual reality game universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818111500 +0800" stop="20250818113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Chinese) Super BOOMi follows an animated bear and his friends as they learn and play in a virtual reality game universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818113000 +0800" stop="20250818114500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Go Go Dino S7-S9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Rex, Tomo, Viki, Ping, and Rocky, a group of dinosaurs, team up to explore and find new friends on planet M25.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818114500 +0800" stop="20250818120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Go Go Dino S7-S9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Rex, Tomo, Viki, Ping, and Rocky, a group of dinosaurs, team up to explore and find new friends on planet M25.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818120000 +0800" stop="20250818121500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Alvinnn!!! &amp; The Chipmunks S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">A single dad has his hands full raising six rambunctious chipmunks in this animated comedy!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818121500 +0800" stop="20250818123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Alvinnn!!! &amp; The Chipmunks S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">A single dad has his hands full raising six rambunctious chipmunks in this animated comedy!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818123000 +0800" stop="20250818124500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Galapagos X</title>
    <desc lang="en">Four kids from the future, which is a troubled one, come to the present to help us prevent climate change problems. No more strawberry Jam? What will I put on my toast! Our team Orchid, Zephyr, Rae and Oshie are dispatched to unravel the mystery that is Dr. Crock, our super-rich social media entrepreneur/philanthropist kidnapping all the bees so she can monoplize honey products - candles, shampoo and cereal - forever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818124500 +0800" stop="20250818130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Galapagos X</title>
    <desc lang="en">Four kids from the future, which is a troubled one, come to the present to help us prevent climate change problems. No more strawberry Jam? What will I put on my toast! Our team Orchid, Zephyr, Rae and Oshie are dispatched to unravel the mystery that is Dr. Crock, our super-rich social media entrepreneur/philanthropist kidnapping all the bees so she can monoplize honey products - candles, shampoo and cereal - forever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818130000 +0800" stop="20250818133000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Totally Spies S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three teenage girls from Beverly Hills attempt to balance their lives as high school (later university) students with their undercover work as super-spies, battling an array of bizarre criminals!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818133000 +0800" stop="20250818134500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Jonny Jetboy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jonny Jones and his family are secretly superheroes known as The Jetfleet! Together they face off against their city's villains all the while learning what it is to be a true hero.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818134500 +0800" stop="20250818140000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Jonny Jetboy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jonny Jones and his family are secretly superheroes known as The Jetfleet! Together they face off against their city's villains all the while learning what it is to be a true hero.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818140000 +0800" stop="20250818143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Petronix Defenders</title>
    <desc lang="en">When crises strike wild animals around the planet, a team of heroic seven-year-olds transform their high-tech backpacks into robotic pets and rush off on daring missions to rescue them. This team of heroic kids and their robotic pets stands on call, ready to leap into action when danger strikes animals around the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818143000 +0800" stop="20250818150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pokemon Horizons: The Series</title>
    <desc lang="en">The series stars two new protagonists, Liko and Roy, who team up with the Rising Volt Tacklers, a group of adventurers that explore the Pokmon world and visit various regions. As they do, they are pursued by the Explorers, a mysterious organization seeking Liko's pendant for unknown reasons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818150000 +0800" stop="20250818153000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818153000 +0800" stop="20250818160000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818160000 +0800" stop="20250818163000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Kin</title>
    <desc lang="en">James and Emily return from their honeymoon and Ananya struggles to keep her emotions under control. Syirah hears about Zaryn's poor performance at Shelley Holdings. Ah Yoke is heartbroken when Dr Shen refuses to open up to her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818163000 +0800" stop="20250818173000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">MasterChef Junior USA S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">This week the seven remaining junior chefs test their culinary knowledge of different types of eggs and cuts of steak. In 45 minutes, the chefs must create a dish with an egg of their choice, ranging from a tiny quail egg to a giant ostrich egg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818173000 +0800" stop="20250818180000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cooking Up A Fortune</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brand new series where the UK's most passionate cooks get a once-in-a-lifetime chance to launch their own food brand to the British public. Cooking Up a Fortune sees amateur foodies, who dream of escaping the rat race and cooking for a living, create and sell their dishes to hundreds of real diners in a purpose-built food arena. Each week the winning kitchen gets to launch their idea for a food business to paying customers in one of Europe's busiest food markets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818180000 +0800" stop="20250818190000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo UK S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818190000 +0800" stop="20250818193000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S41</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Sajak hosts his final season of Wheel of Fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818193000 +0800" stop="20250818203000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 04</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818203000 +0800" stop="20250818210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Provocative</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nadrah's health deteriorates as her withdrawal symptoms intensify. Tess makes promising steps to reconnect with Aiden, but his heartbreak over Melody makes reconciliation challenging.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818210000 +0800" stop="20250818213000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818213000 +0800" stop="20250818220000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">John Torode's Asia</title>
    <desc lang="en">John Torode finds himself in the world's most densely populated region this week, The Las Vegas of Asia: Macau. As a former Portuguese colony, influences on Macanese cuisine come from all over the globe, and it's with this in mind that John finds himself baking and then tucking in to one of the spiciest dishes he's come across thus far: African Chicken.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818220000 +0800" stop="20250818230000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Matlock S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Madeline Matlock rejoins the work force at a prestigious law firm, where she uses her wily tactics to win cases and expose wrongdoing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818230000 +0800" stop="20250819000000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">So Help Me Todd S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margaret and Todd defend the "Queen of Hearts," a notoriously unscrupulous lawyer accused of orchestrating a fraudulent accident that resulted in the death of a "fake victim.".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819000000 +0800" stop="20250819003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Provocative</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nadrah's health deteriorates as her withdrawal symptoms intensify. Tess makes promising steps to reconnect with Aiden, but his heartbreak over Melody makes reconciliation challenging.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819003000 +0800" stop="20250819013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">FBI: International S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The FBI's International Fly Team tracks and neutralizes threats against American citizens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819013000 +0800" stop="20250819020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S41</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Sajak hosts his final season of Wheel of Fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819020000 +0800" stop="20250819030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 04</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819030000 +0800" stop="20250819040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo UK S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819040000 +0800" stop="20250819043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819043000 +0800" stop="20250819050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cooking Up A Fortune</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brand new series where the UK's most passionate cooks get a once-in-a-lifetime chance to launch their own food brand to the British public. Cooking Up a Fortune sees amateur foodies, who dream of escaping the rat race and cooking for a living, create and sell their dishes to hundreds of real diners in a purpose-built food arena. Each week the winning kitchen gets to launch their idea for a food business to paying customers in one of Europe's busiest food markets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819050000 +0800" stop="20250822220000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">MasterChef Junior USA S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">This week the seven remaining junior chefs test their culinary knowledge of different types of eggs and cuts of steak. In 45 minutes, the chefs must create a dish with an egg of their choice, ranging from a tiny quail egg to a giant ostrich egg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250822220000 +0800" stop="20250823001000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Captive</title>
    <desc lang="en">Eight years after the disappearance of Cassandra, some disturbing incidents seem to indicate that she's still alive. Police, parents and Cassandra herself, will try to unravel the mystery of her disappearance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823001000 +0800" stop="20250823011500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Remarkable Places to Eat S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the second series of Remarkable Places To Eat, Britain's best loved foodies take host Fred Sirieix to experience their favourite restaurants and explore what goes into making them so special. Series highlights include a visit to Marrakesh with Andi Oliver, exploring the delights of Vienna with Rachel Khoo and a road trip around Yorkshire with Nadiya Hussain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823011500 +0800" stop="20250823013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Just For Laughs Gags S24</title>
    <desc lang="en">Just For Laughs will tickle everyone's funny bone with its hilarious practical jokes, hidden camera pranks, and other creative hijinks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823013000 +0800" stop="20250823023000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823023000 +0800" stop="20250823030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823030000 +0800" stop="20250823033000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Arts 21</title>
    <desc lang="en">ARTS 21 is an arts magazine show focusing on the latest news and events on the culture scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823033000 +0800" stop="20250823040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823040000 +0800" stop="20250823045000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo UK S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823045000 +0800" stop="20250823051500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cooking Up A Fortune</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brand new series where the UK's most passionate cooks get a once-in-a-lifetime chance to launch their own food brand to the British public. Cooking Up a Fortune sees amateur foodies, who dream of escaping the rat race and cooking for a living, create and sell their dishes to hundreds of real diners in a purpose-built food arena. Each week the winning kitchen gets to launch their idea for a food business to paying customers in one of Europe's busiest food markets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823051500 +0800" stop="20250823060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">MasterChef Junior USA S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">The three semi-finalists go head-to-head in front of a live audience with a surprise visit from their loved ones. The chefs have one hour to prepare a dish inspired by their families for each judge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823060000 +0800" stop="20250823063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Hiccup And Sneeze S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hiccup and Sneeze are two young forest monsters that snuck in one day out of the rain. They are a brother and sister, who liked the place so much they decided to stay. (Monsters sometimes do that and it's not even considered rude - but that's just monsters). Anyway, they're all living together in Bibi's magical house even though sometimes Hiccup and Sneeze don't really understand that being a monster and being a human are two very different things...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823063000 +0800" stop="20250823070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">In Our House S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">IN OUR HOUSE is full of surprises and is more interactive and energetic than you have ever seen before. In an entertaining mix of song, dance, music and drama, join the wacky hosts as they introduce the LETTERS AND NUMBERS OF THE DAY and the adventures that they encounter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823070000 +0800" stop="20250823073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">123 Number Squad S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Number Squad goes on a musical journey to locate a magic shell that will help give Shelly back her beautiful voice, but they need to solve number puzzles along the way to retrieve the shell. Shelly is about to hold a concert for her clam friends when a sneezing frenzy causes them to fly everywhere! The Number Squad finds ways to bring the clams back and to minimize the sneezing at the concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823073000 +0800" stop="20250823080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Hobby TV S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">From playing with skateboards to collecting stamps; from building models to drawing comics, hosts Randall and Gus show kids the ins n outs of hobbies – the wacky way!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823080000 +0800" stop="20250823081500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pororo the Little Penguin 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Pororo and friends in their fun adventures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823081500 +0800" stop="20250823083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pororo the Little Penguin 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Pororo and friends in their fun adventures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823083000 +0800" stop="20250823090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Songs &amp; Stories</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enjoy the best of Pinkfong's most loved songs and stories with all your favourite characters!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823090000 +0800" stop="20250823091500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Blippi Singapore Adventures</title>
    <desc lang="en">Blippi Singapore Adventures.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823091500 +0800" stop="20250823093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Vegesaurs S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ginger the Tricarrotops explores the world of the crunchiest era, going on adventures throughout the colourful Vegesaur Valley.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823093000 +0800" stop="20250823100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cloudy With a Chance of Meatballs S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this prequel to the 2009 film, inventor boy Flint Lockwood and reporter girl Sam Sparks as best friends during high school!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100000 +0800" stop="20250823103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pokemon Horizons: Season 2 -The Search for Laqua</title>
    <desc lang="en">In order to learn and master Terastallization, Liko, Roy, and Dot have joined the Naranja Academy's "Tera Training"! They meet Clavell, the school's director, and Geeta, the chairwoman of Paldea's Pokmon League as well as the Elite Four of Paldea: Rika, Poppy, Larry , and Hassel. And so begins their adventure in Paldea Region, setting their sights on their Terastallization debut!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823103000 +0800" stop="20250823104500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Leo the Wildlife Ranger S7 Spinoff</title>
    <desc lang="en">Leo the Wildlife Ranger S7 Spinoff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823104500 +0800" stop="20250823110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Leo the Wildlife Ranger S7 Spinoff</title>
    <desc lang="en">Leo the Wildlife Ranger S7 Spinoff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823110000 +0800" stop="20250823111500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Infinity Nado</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Four Infinity Nado players and teammates decide to enter the Infinity Nado tower and challenge the other players, who plan to use their powers in order to destroy mankind and terraform planet Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823111500 +0800" stop="20250823113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Infinity Nado</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Four Infinity Nado players and teammates decide to enter the Infinity Nado tower and challenge the other players, who plan to use their powers in order to destroy mankind and terraform planet Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823113000 +0800" stop="20250823120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Totally Spies S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three teenage girls from Beverly Hills attempt to balance their lives as high school (later university) students with their undercover work as super-spies, battling an array of bizarre criminals!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823120000 +0800" stop="20250823123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Beyblade X S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Don't miss the continuing adventures as Beyblade pros from around the world gather to compete in the Pro League held inside the X Tower!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823123000 +0800" stop="20250823124000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Grizzy &amp; The Lemmings S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarious misadventures of Grizzy and the Lemmings continue... now in unexpected places around the world!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823124000 +0800" stop="20250823125000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Grizzy &amp; The Lemmings S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarious misadventures of Grizzy and the Lemmings continue... now in unexpected places around the world!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823125000 +0800" stop="20250823130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Grizzy &amp; The Lemmings S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarious misadventures of Grizzy and the Lemmings continue... now in unexpected places around the world!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130000 +0800" stop="20250823133000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Johnny Test S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of average suburban boy Johnny Test, who wittingly plays test subject for his genius twin sisters' various experiments, reluctantly fighting evil villains in the process.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823133000 +0800" stop="20250823140000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823140000 +0800" stop="20250823141500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Jungle Bunch S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Jungle Bunch tells the story of a group of loopy animals fighting injustice in the heart of the jungle, where every being who faces a problem knows who to call...."The Jungle Bunch: to the Rescue!".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823141500 +0800" stop="20250823143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Jungle Bunch S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Jungle Bunch tells the story of a group of loopy animals fighting injustice in the heart of the jungle, where every being who faces a problem knows who to call...."The Jungle Bunch: to the Rescue!".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823143000 +0800" stop="20250823150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Groom My Room S11</title>
    <desc lang="en">What to do you when you want to transform your depressing bedroom into a fantasy Gameworld? 11 year-old twin brothers Jayden &amp; Eden know the answer and call on Charmian Tan and her Groom My Room troopers to complete the challenging task of giving them an out-of-this world game room where they can be themselves, together and alone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823150000 +0800" stop="20250823153000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Spirit of Sport S10</title>
    <desc lang="en">Monthly sports television magazine show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823153000 +0800" stop="20250823160000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Unbelievable Moments Caught On Camera S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">Voiced by Alexander Armstrong, the programme travels around the globe - meeting the people who filmed these amazing clips to get the stories behind the footage. Unbelievable Moments Caught on Camera features incredible, eye-witness footage shot by members of the public.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160000 +0800" stop="20250823170000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Weather Files: Total Impact S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">This series takes viewers inside extreme weather events and natural disasters like never before! Through the eyes of real life survivors, first responders and scientific experts, we go inside the disasters with gripping, first-hand accounts, dramatic original footage, cutting-edge science and graphic animations of how things work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823170000 +0800" stop="20250823180000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Press Your Luck S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hosted by Elizabeth Banks, Press Your Luck is a game of wits, strategy and even higher stakes as contestants try to avoid the iconic and devilish WHAMMY for a chance at life-changing cash and prizes. During each game of Press Your Luck, three contestants compete against each other, answering questions to earn spins on the Big Board.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823180000 +0800" stop="20250823182500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823182500 +0800" stop="20250823185000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S41</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Sajak hosts his final season of Wheel of Fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823185000 +0800" stop="20250823210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dog</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two former Army Rangers are paired against their will on the road trip of a lifetime. Briggs (Channing Tatum) and Lulu (a Belgian Malinois) race down the Pacific Coast to get to a fellow soldier's funeral on time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210000 +0800" stop="20250823213000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823213000 +0800" stop="20250823220000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Weather Gone Viral S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">From whirling tornadoes to torrential rains, to harrowing hurricanes, Weather Gone Viral gives viewers unprecedented access to some of the most insane meteorological moments from around the world. Featuring videos of the most extreme and destructive weather conditions, firsthand accounts, and professional meteorologists sharing tales from the front lines, viewers get to experience the fury of Mother Nature.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823220000 +0800" stop="20250823234500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">When a Stranger Calls</title>
    <desc lang="en">During a babysitting gig, a high-school student is harassed by an increasingly threatening prank caller.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817004500 +0800" stop="20250817014500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">我的女侠罗明依</title>
    <desc lang="en">毕正、孙公公等坐船去马六甲，船到公海，毕正挟持龚王威胁孙公公，怒斥他陷害忠良，滥杀无辜，并将龚王丢入海中。潇洒和斯文同时偷袭孙公公，孙公公中刀，也被推下海，与龚王一起被海水吞没。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817014500 +0800" stop="20250817024500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">我的女侠罗明依</title>
    <desc lang="en">毕正和明依回返明朝，两人交换玉佩，互定终身。明依护送李时珍回乡，而毕正则出发去剿乱党。明依陪着李时珍及其子建元在乡间采草药，等着毕正前来提亲，谁知却等来毕正的死讯…….</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817024500 +0800" stop="20250817034500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">邻里厨王</title>
    <desc lang="en">新加坡是个多元种族、多元文化的岛国。这档节目通过比赛的方式让不同籍贯、不同种族的居民聚集在一起参与并展现他们的厨艺。主持人李国煌和钟琴每个星期将走进新加坡各个组屋区寻找该区的"邻里厨王"！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817034500 +0800" stop="20250817041000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">没那么简单</title>
    <desc lang="en">由钟琴和Pornsak携手主持的节目，每一集的节目里会邀请艺人朋友同我们一起讨论日常生活上经常会遇到的生活难题，教你各种千奇百怪和意想不到的生活妙招。网路上危言耸听的理论，到底是真是假？揭开迷思与偏方的的误区，让真相大白。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817041000 +0800" stop="20250817050500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">企鹅爸爸</title>
    <desc lang="en">刘帮在一间银行担任高级副总裁，太太杨欣北是个全职家庭主妇。邻居叶正康是一名"家庭主夫"，妻子陈美惠则负责在外工作养家。刘帮对于正康并不苟同，但一场金融海啸后，他万万没想到自己也加入了正康的行列。_x000d__x000a__x000d__x000a_演员：李南星饰刘帮；郭舒贤饰杨欣北；陈汉玮饰叶正康；许美珍饰陈美惠。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817050500 +0800" stop="20250817060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">企鹅爸爸</title>
    <desc lang="en">刘帮在一间银行担任高级副总裁，太太杨欣北是个全职家庭主妇。邻居叶正康是一名"家庭主夫"，妻子陈美惠则负责在外工作养家。刘帮对于正康并不苟同，但一场金融海啸后，他万万没想到自己也加入了正康的行列。_x000d__x000a__x000d__x000a_演员：李南星饰刘帮；郭舒贤饰杨欣北；陈汉玮饰叶正康；许美珍饰陈美惠。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817060000 +0800" stop="20250817065000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">我是媒体人</title>
    <desc lang="en">全新节目“我是媒体人”，为有志朝“中文媒体制作”发展的朋友提供一个发挥所长的平台。节目将通过“练习生”选拔模式，提供一系列相关专业培训，再让参与者经历各种职场实践和挑战，最终选出表现最佳者。与此同时，观众也能通过镜头一窥电视和广播生态鲜为人知的一面。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817065000 +0800" stop="20250817072000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817072000 +0800" stop="20250817081000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">起飞</title>
    <desc lang="en">《起飞》描述了三个热爱音乐的年轻人，他们的情感纠葛，以及在追逐音乐梦想的道路上，载沉载浮的奋斗和激励人心的感人故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817081000 +0800" stop="20250817090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">起飞</title>
    <desc lang="en">《起飞》描述了三个热爱音乐的年轻人，他们的情感纠葛，以及在追逐音乐梦想的道路上，载沉载浮的奋斗和激励人心的感人故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817090000 +0800" stop="20250817091500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">超级小熊布迷</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/英) 该片创新结合了科技、运动、冒险、历史等题材，以闯关对战的形式，讲述了小英雄布迷和小伙伴们在虚拟游戏世界里勇敢冒险、智斗巴戈大魔王的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817091500 +0800" stop="20250817093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">超级小熊布迷</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/英) 该片创新结合了科技、运动、冒险、历史等题材，以闯关对战的形式，讲述了小英雄布迷和小伙伴们在虚拟游戏世界里勇敢冒险、智斗巴戈大魔王的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817093000 +0800" stop="20250817100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">哆啦A梦</title>
    <desc lang="en">在这系列卡通动画里，小朋友们将看到哆啦A梦 - 这只来自未来世界的机器猫，如何应用它的法宝，协助其主人大雄解决生活上的各种难题。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817100000 +0800" stop="20250817103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">小红点之大世界</title>
    <desc lang="en">这一集，跟随两位团友参加缤纷多彩的菲律宾之旅！制作散发正能量的微笑面具、体验传统竹竿舞、品尝Kamayan盛宴、参与菲律宾家庭活动动手制作星型灯笼。最后，一起欣赏悦耳的隆达拉音乐！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817103000 +0800" stop="20250817104500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">变形联盟</title>
    <desc lang="en">由于基因源，武装战士变成变形机甲、生物进化为虫族、浩肯星人异化为变异战士，故事从变形机甲、机甲兽和变异战士三方之间的斗争展开。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817104500 +0800" stop="20250817110000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">变形联盟</title>
    <desc lang="en">由于基因源，武装战士变成变形机甲、生物进化为虫族、浩肯星人异化为变异战士，故事从变形机甲、机甲兽和变异战士三方之间的斗争展开。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817110000 +0800" stop="20250817113000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">星期二特写 ：两代之间</title>
    <desc lang="en">吴薇薇是本地画家吴珉权的小女儿。疫情阻断期间，她感悟到要及时回报父母的养育之恩，于是她毅然辞去工作，到父亲的画廊帮忙。父女之间得以重温过去的美好回忆，只是薇薇不再是当年的小女孩，她扛起看护父母的日常生活，还为父亲筹办回顾展。父女身份依旧，角色却大不相同，让薇薇重新认识父女间的关系。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817113000 +0800" stop="20250817114400 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">Biowell Vital Fish Oil 针对三高族群设计，含有高达97%纯度的Omega-3，并特别添加红曲，有助于维护心、血管健康、维护胆固醇、有助于稳定血压和血糖。Biowell concentrated Fish Oil, 95%高纯度浓缩鱼油；富含DHA并添加叶黄素，有助提升专注力、保护视力、缓解眼睛干涩疲劳，脑眼双补！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817114400 +0800" stop="20250817114600 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">这款La Gourmet 火焰电饭锅将火锅和烧烤炉结合一体。为您提供两全其美的享受。无论您是煮汤还是烧烤肉类和蔬菜，都能享受多功能的膳食准备！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817114600 +0800" stop="20250817120000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">Philips Azur 8000系列蒸汽熨斗有OptimalTEMP免调校温控技术，保证不会把面料烫坏。智能温控保证不熨焦，让您水平、垂直熨烫一机搞定！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817120000 +0800" stop="20250817130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">覆流年</title>
    <desc lang="en">随着一声水雷响起，安然睁开双眼，意外发现自己回到及笄礼的前一天，一切重新开始。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817130000 +0800" stop="20250817140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">覆流年</title>
    <desc lang="en">安然决定满足穆泽的心愿，答应嫁给他为妻，并收下玉佩为定情之物。可是，安然却表示与穆泽只有盟约，并无任何感情。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817140000 +0800" stop="20250817143000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">健康123 S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">本季依然有主持人萧慧敏坐镇，节目将透过动画短片，以有趣的方式带出许多人的健康迷思，然后再由中医、西医和营养师.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817143000 +0800" stop="20250817181500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">国庆庆典 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">2025年国庆庆典以“前进吧，新加坡”为主题，庆祝国家独立60周年，向为国家发展作出贡献的平凡英雄和开拓者致敬，同时寄托对未来一代的期许。今年的庆典首次从政府大厦前大草场扩展延伸至滨海湾，呈现多幕精彩的军事表演、灯光投影，并以璀璨壮观的烟花秀作为压轴。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817181500 +0800" stop="20250817184500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城六点半</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《狮城6点半》每日为您提供最全面的本地新闻头条与报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817184500 +0800" stop="20250817191500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">国庆群众大会2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 黄循财总理在工艺教育学院总部发表国庆群众大会演讲。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817191500 +0800" stop="20250817194500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">家简尘除 S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">在孩子的劝说下，Uncle Chee终于下定决心，为住了近半世纪的老房子来一个大改造。收集了一堆摆设品和工具的他，将如何实践断舍离？设计师和收纳达人又会如何为Uncle Chee打造一个梦寐以求的新客厅？《家简尘除》，为你实现烦恼尽除！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817194500 +0800" stop="20250817200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">古早味侦探 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">古早味侦探 3.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817200000 +0800" stop="20250817211500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">国庆群众大会2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 黄循财总理在工艺教育学院总部发表国庆群众大会演讲。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817211500 +0800" stop="20250817214500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">艺拍即合</title>
    <desc lang="en">林茜茜和钟坤华能否在四个小时时限内学习制作出一件玻璃和木雕艺术品呢？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817214500 +0800" stop="20250817220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">吃。东西 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">吃。东西 2.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817220000 +0800" stop="20250817224500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817224500 +0800" stop="20250817234500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories &lt; Chinese &gt;</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hidden Histories &lt; Chinese &gt;.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817234500 +0800" stop="20250817234500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">前线追踪</title>
    <desc lang="en">民情、民生、民意！【前线追踪】紧跟社会民生步伐，追踪调查时事动态，探讨新加坡人关心的课题，针对问题的核心追根究底。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817234500 +0800" stop="20250818001500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">前线追踪</title>
    <desc lang="en">民情、民生、民意！【前线追踪】紧跟社会民生步伐，追踪调查时事动态，探讨新加坡人关心的课题，针对问题的核心追根究底。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818001500 +0800" stop="20250818011500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">最火搭档</title>
    <desc lang="en">印尼富商的女儿失踪，要求警方协助调查，女警小曼在搜寻的过程中发现此案与人蛇集团有关。小曼带同组员到禁锢地点进行突袭，山番带领正仪等手下往后巷逃走，小曼追赶，虽然被他们逃脱，但小曼认出了正仪的背影。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818011500 +0800" stop="20250818021500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">最火搭档</title>
    <desc lang="en">小曼捉到正仪，但她装傻胡扯，不肯合作。重案组雨泽前来带走正仪，引起小曼不满。原来正仪是雨泽的卧底，雨泽早就猜到山番的计划，还故意让小曼展开行动，让黑痣成为正仪的替死鬼。正仪感内疚，表示捉到山番之后就不要再当线人。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818021500 +0800" stop="20250818031500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">十三鞭</title>
    <desc lang="en">十三鞭.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818031500 +0800" stop="20250818041000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">十三鞭</title>
    <desc lang="en">十三鞭.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818041000 +0800" stop="20250818050500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">企鹅爸爸</title>
    <desc lang="en">刘帮在一间银行担任高级副总裁，太太杨欣北是个全职家庭主妇。邻居叶正康是一名"家庭主夫"，妻子陈美惠则负责在外工作养家。刘帮对于正康并不苟同，但一场金融海啸后，他万万没想到自己也加入了正康的行列。_x000d__x000a__x000d__x000a_演员：李南星饰刘帮；郭舒贤饰杨欣北；陈汉玮饰叶正康；许美珍饰陈美惠。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818050500 +0800" stop="20250818060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">企鹅爸爸</title>
    <desc lang="en">刘帮在一间银行担任高级副总裁，太太杨欣北是个全职家庭主妇。邻居叶正康是一名"家庭主夫"，妻子陈美惠则负责在外工作养家。刘帮对于正康并不苟同，但一场金融海啸后，他万万没想到自己也加入了正康的行列。_x000d__x000a__x000d__x000a_演员：李南星饰刘帮；郭舒贤饰杨欣北；陈汉玮饰叶正康；许美珍饰陈美惠。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818060000 +0800" stop="20250818065000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">百味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">农历新年，是华人人情往来的重要时节。在这年岁交接的时节里，人们以百味佳肴团聚共享，抒发了对时节易逝的感怀，寄托了对美好生活的向往。各个籍贯华人以百味纷陈，丰盛美味的年菜来庆贺新年。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818065000 +0800" stop="20250818073500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818073500 +0800" stop="20250818080000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">前线追踪</title>
    <desc lang="en">民情、民生、民意！【前线追踪】紧跟社会民生步伐，追踪调查时事动态，探讨新加坡人关心的课题，针对问题的核心追根究底。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818080000 +0800" stop="20250818090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">心有所依</title>
    <desc lang="en">明珍安慰梓阳，没有拒绝他的追求。盛德和老大到葛芬多市找贯中，医生表示他时日无多，盛德通知明珍，明珍却姗姗来迟，对父亲的离世表现冷淡，盛德觉得她冷漠无情。芷晴和顺庆察觉到华姐行为异样，怀疑她患有失智症。盛德接获明珍邀约，竟发现明珍要解除领养协议，盛德大惊！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818090000 +0800" stop="20250818093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城热话</title>
    <desc lang="en">周一至周五晚上7点，《狮城有约》谈话性栏目《狮城热话》以汇集多元声音及专家看法为目标，通过网络投票和引导观点碰撞，打造能让观众参与的时事舆论场。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818093000 +0800" stop="20250818100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">巾帼枭雄之悬崖</title>
    <desc lang="en">桂嬋以商人身份接近日军，实则为获取特权，营救更多难民逃离战火。战事恶化，桂嬋被义士接至香港，与十七重逢，两人终坦白心意。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818100000 +0800" stop="20250818103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">贫民窟美食探索 -乡镇篇</title>
    <desc lang="en">尽管生活拮据，在甲米的Koh Klang岛上的居民仍能依靠海洋的丰富资源过上好日子。奇异的捕获如红树林黑蟹、魟鱼和巨型海螺都可以烹煮成美味佳肴。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818103000 +0800" stop="20250818113000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">甘味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">甘味人生，是一出阐述「一家人世代传承家业」的励志写实戏剧。剧中赵家是制作传统手工酱油的一个大家庭，家庭的父母兄弟姊妹，共同为这个家努力打拼的历程为主轴，描写刻画每个人在打拼的过程当中，与纠结在矛盾的感情世界里，所经历的悲欢喜乐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818113000 +0800" stop="20250818130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">甘味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">甘味人生，是一出阐述「一家人世代传承家业」的励志写实戏剧。剧中赵家是制作传统手工酱油的一个大家庭，家庭的父母兄弟姊妹，共同为这个家努力打拼的历程为主轴，描写刻画每个人在打拼的过程当中，与纠结在矛盾的感情世界里，所经历的悲欢喜乐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818130000 +0800" stop="20250818133000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">一点新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《一点新闻》为您提供更新的本地与全球新闻头条。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818133000 +0800" stop="20250818140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">愛‧回家之开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">该剧围绕「熊氏一家」在家中的生活点滴，叙述各人的生活繁忙，各有各烦恼，但由于家里多出了一只鬼魂，有时帮助解决了不少问题，成功地点明「灵异」的主题，更从中渗透出熊家各人为生活琐事而争吵，更引发不少误会，而最后却能和好如初。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818140000 +0800" stop="20250818143000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">愛‧回家之开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">该剧围绕「熊氏一家」在家中的生活点滴，叙述各人的生活繁忙，各有各烦恼，但由于家里多出了一只鬼魂，有时帮助解决了不少问题，成功地点明「灵异」的主题，更从中渗透出熊家各人为生活琐事而争吵，更引发不少误会，而最后却能和好如初。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818143000 +0800" stop="20250818153000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">愛‧回家之开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">该剧围绕「熊氏一家」在家中的生活点滴，叙述各人的生活繁忙，各有各烦恼，但由于家里多出了一只鬼魂，有时帮助解决了不少问题，成功地点明「灵异」的主题，更从中渗透出熊家各人为生活琐事而争吵，更引发不少误会，而最后却能和好如初。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818153000 +0800" stop="20250818160000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">法言人</title>
    <desc lang="en">主要是讲述了律师楼的师爷是开拓业务的开拓人，他作为一个桥梁来沟通市民和大状之间的关系，进而引发了一系列的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818160000 +0800" stop="20250818163000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">法言人</title>
    <desc lang="en">主要是讲述了律师楼的师爷是开拓业务的开拓人，他作为一个桥梁来沟通市民和大状之间的关系，进而引发了一系列的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818163000 +0800" stop="20250818173000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818173000 +0800" stop="20250818183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818183000 +0800" stop="20250818193000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城有约</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 总结一天大小事，关心属于你我的家园。每逢星期一至五，傍晚6.30-7.30pm，与你相约！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818193000 +0800" stop="20250818200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">巾帼枭雄之悬崖</title>
    <desc lang="en">桂嬋意外得知孩子的下落，独自追踪线索，却迷路与十七失散。两人辗转寻觅三年，终于在逃难途中重逢。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818200000 +0800" stop="20250818210000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">带爸妈去旅行</title>
    <desc lang="en">陪伴，是世上最奢侈的礼物。阿贤将联同江瀚和慧敏带着父母去旅行，帮他们完成旅行愿望清单，用父母的速度旅行，双手相握一起看世界，是再多钱也换不到的人生体验，一起踏上奇幻浪漫的旅途。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818210000 +0800" stop="20250818220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">心有所依</title>
    <desc lang="en">明珍跟盛德解除领养协议，盛德很是痛心，但是没有挽留。老四完成穿婚纱的梦想，没想到是老大的安排，她早就知道老四生病的事。盛德和梓阳来找明珍，意外发现明珍的人寿保险，受益人是盛德。老大和老友相聚，失踪多年的老公竟然出现，老大震惊。明珍萎靡不振，自暴自弃，直到收到了爸爸的电话。明珍意外，眼眶含泪…….</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818220000 +0800" stop="20250818223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818223000 +0800" stop="20250818230000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">港女野人奇遇记</title>
    <desc lang="en">港女野人抵达以温泉闻名的Taupo镇，以野外定向方式寻找目标温泉。此天然温泉完全融入大自然，旅客途经可随意跳入河中免费享用！四人持地图分别出发，单是定出自己所在位置已有难度！ Amber误入树林急流区，为找温泉试水温……Nicole与温泉入口擦身而过！ Jessica自认「路痴」，连摄影师也不禁出口相助？而Honey先谋后动，后发先至！谁人最终包尾？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818230000 +0800" stop="20250819000000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">大理寺少卿游</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事发生在女皇统治下的神都。唐宫夜宴，受女皇赏识李饼被任命为大理寺少卿。大理寺中陈拾、王七、阿里巴巴、崔倍和孙豹一众人在新任少卿白.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819000000 +0800" stop="20250819010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">长风渡</title>
    <desc lang="en">扬州布商之女柳玉茹自小遭遇生母病重、庶母不慈、父亲不重视的困境，她不得已谨小慎微，做了十五年模范闺秀。不料，对婚姻抱有憧憬的她却被被家里安排嫁给了名满扬州的纨绔顾九思。顾九思也误会柳玉茹是因为攀附权贵才嫁给他，对其嗤之以鼻。柳玉茹幡然醒悟，不能将命运系之婚姻，系之他人，决定跟随顾母学习经商之道，真实、独立、精彩地实现自我价值。经过刻苦努力，柳玉茹顺利通过了顾母的考验，生意上逐渐得心应手，更是在此过程中改变了对顾九思的看法，发现其至纯至善、炽热真诚的一面，两个人的心也越靠越近。然而此时，扬州节度使王善泉凶狠毒辣、倒行逆施，导致百姓流离失所，顾家不得已举家逃亡，原本奢靡无度的顾九思看着万千流民，一夜之间长大。为结束混乱局面，让百姓安居，顾九思从捕快做起，官至户部尚书，与志同道合者扫除积弊，轻税轻徭。柳玉茹则内修善堂、外建商交，使得物资繁盛、百姓安康，两人共同谱写了一段盛世佳话。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819010000 +0800" stop="20250819020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">食尚玩家 - 2天1夜Go S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">在新一辑的“食尚玩家 - 2 天1夜GO"里，主持人纳豆，六月，曾子余等会带领观众周游许多耳目一新的地方，国家包括韩国（首尔，釜山），日本（东京，大版），捷克，马来西亚等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819020000 +0800" stop="20250819030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">想握你的手</title>
    <desc lang="en">以本地的社会时事为骨架，描述同一个邻里几个不同背景的家庭，如何由冷漠自我，到最终了解何谓"爱"。故事反映了血浓于水、守望相助、远亲不如近邻的可贵精神。新传媒艺人黄文永在此剧中饰演父亲，是一家咖啡店的老板，为人节俭，有三个女儿，分别由林湘萍、李心钰和蔡佩璇饰演，而陈丽萍则饰演文永的妻子。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819030000 +0800" stop="20250819040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">想握你的手</title>
    <desc lang="en">以本地的社会时事为骨架，描述同一个邻里几个不同背景的家庭，如何由冷漠自我，到最终了解何谓"爱"。故事反映了血浓于水、守望相助、远亲不如近邻的可贵精神。新传媒艺人黄文永在此剧中饰演父亲，是一家咖啡店的老板，为人节俭，有三个女儿，分别由林湘萍、李心钰和蔡佩璇饰演，而陈丽萍则饰演文永的妻子。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819040000 +0800" stop="20250819050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819050000 +0800" stop="20250823000000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823000000 +0800" stop="20250823010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">长风渡</title>
    <desc lang="en">扬州布商之女柳玉茹自小遭遇生母病重、庶母不慈、父亲不重视的困境，她不得已谨小慎微，做了十五年模范闺秀。不料，对婚姻抱有憧憬的她却被被家里安排嫁给了名满扬州的纨绔顾九思。顾九思也误会柳玉茹是因为攀附权贵才嫁给他，对其嗤之以鼻。柳玉茹幡然醒悟，不能将命运系之婚姻，系之他人，决定跟随顾母学习经商之道，真实、独立、精彩地实现自我价值。经过刻苦努力，柳玉茹顺利通过了顾母的考验，生意上逐渐得心应手，更是在此过程中改变了对顾九思的看法，发现其至纯至善、炽热真诚的一面，两个人的心也越靠越近。然而此时，扬州节度使王善泉凶狠毒辣、倒行逆施，导致百姓流离失所，顾家不得已举家逃亡，原本奢靡无度的顾九思看着万千流民，一夜之间长大。为结束混乱局面，让百姓安居，顾九思从捕快做起，官至户部尚书，与志同道合者扫除积弊，轻税轻徭。柳玉茹则内修善堂、外建商交，使得物资繁盛、百姓安康，两人共同谱写了一段盛世佳话。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823010000 +0800" stop="20250823020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">再见单人床</title>
    <desc lang="en">演员：白薇秀饰张秋雪；方展发饰何廷凯；谢韵仪饰梁楚宁；王沺裁饰张秋雨。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823020000 +0800" stop="20250823030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">想握你的手</title>
    <desc lang="en">以本地的社会时事为骨架，描述同一个邻里几个不同背景的家庭，如何由冷漠自我，到最终了解何谓"爱"。故事反映了血浓于水、守望相助、远亲不如近邻的可贵精神。新传媒艺人黄文永在此剧中饰演父亲，是一家咖啡店的老板，为人节俭，有三个女儿，分别由林湘萍、李心钰和蔡佩璇饰演，而陈丽萍则饰演文永的妻子。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823030000 +0800" stop="20250823040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">想握你的手</title>
    <desc lang="en">以本地的社会时事为骨架，描述同一个邻里几个不同背景的家庭，如何由冷漠自我，到最终了解何谓"爱"。故事反映了血浓于水、守望相助、远亲不如近邻的可贵精神。新传媒艺人黄文永在此剧中饰演父亲，是一家咖啡店的老板，为人节俭，有三个女儿，分别由林湘萍、李心钰和蔡佩璇饰演，而陈丽萍则饰演文永的妻子。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823040000 +0800" stop="20250823050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823050000 +0800" stop="20250823060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823060000 +0800" stop="20250823065000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">古早味侦探 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">潮州粥对许多人来说是一道暖心又暖胃的美食。主持人王禄江与厨师王顺平拜访了老字号潮州粥摊档，打探到一些如今难得品尝的潮州粥配菜和杂咸，尽力还原潮州粥的古早味。主持人还飞往香港，体验了香港的打冷文化。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823065000 +0800" stop="20250823072000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823072000 +0800" stop="20250823081000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">起飞</title>
    <desc lang="en">《起飞》描述了三个热爱音乐的年轻人，他们的情感纠葛，以及在追逐音乐梦想的道路上，载沉载浮的奋斗和激励人心的感人故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823081000 +0800" stop="20250823090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">起飞</title>
    <desc lang="en">《起飞》描述了三个热爱音乐的年轻人，他们的情感纠葛，以及在追逐音乐梦想的道路上，载沉载浮的奋斗和激励人心的感人故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823090000 +0800" stop="20250823090700 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">帮帮龙出动 S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">宇宙的星球里面存活着各种各样的生命体，其中M25星球里面存活着大量的已在地球灭绝的恐龙。帮帮龙探险队为了给孩子们带给生命的美妙去往M25星球探险。他们通过探险发现恐龙，帮助恐龙，同时也跟恐龙成为好朋友，跟着星球的恐龙一起探索，成长!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823090700 +0800" stop="20250823091400 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">帮帮龙出动 S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">宇宙的星球里面存活着各种各样的生命体，其中M25星球里面存活着大量的已在地球灭绝的恐龙。帮帮龙探险队为了给孩子们带给生命的美妙去往M25星球探险。他们通过探险发现恐龙，帮助恐龙，同时也跟恐龙成为好朋友，跟着星球的恐龙一起探索，成长!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823091400 +0800" stop="20250823092100 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Piggy and Friends minisodes</title>
    <desc lang="en">Piggy and Friends minisodes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823092100 +0800" stop="20250823093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Piggy and Friends minisodes</title>
    <desc lang="en">Piggy and Friends minisodes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823093000 +0800" stop="20250823100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">哆啦A梦</title>
    <desc lang="en">在这系列卡通动画里，小朋友们将看到哆啦A梦 - 这只来自未来世界的机器猫，如何应用它的法宝，协助其主人大雄解决生活上的各种难题。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100000 +0800" stop="20250823101500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">迷你特工队之超级恐龙力量</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/英) 讲述的是一直以来保护着地球的迷你特工队面临着一个新的强大对手——怪诞博士。在人类高速发展的社会环境中，他利用高科技手段将生活中的垃圾等事物变化成大怪物，使得地球上的人类面临着一个个巨大危机。为了解除这些危机，来自迷你特工队M-03-G分队的弗特、赛米、露西、麦克斯、雷、里奥、小杰不得不召唤出拥有超级恐龙力量的新装备。迷你特工队通过打败怪诞博士创造出来的一个个新怪物来成长自我。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823101500 +0800" stop="20250823103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">迷你特工队之超级恐龙力量</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/英) 讲述的是一直以来保护着地球的迷你特工队面临着一个新的强大对手——怪诞博士。在人类高速发展的社会环境中，他利用高科技手段将生活中的垃圾等事物变化成大怪物，使得地球上的人类面临着一个个巨大危机。为了解除这些危机，来自迷你特工队M-03-G分队的弗特、赛米、露西、麦克斯、雷、里奥、小杰不得不召唤出拥有超级恐龙力量的新装备。迷你特工队通过打败怪诞博士创造出来的一个个新怪物来成长自我。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823103000 +0800" stop="20250823104500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">宇宙护卫队之钢甲霸王龙</title>
    <desc lang="en">为了保护地球居民，宇宙护卫队再次出发，与晴天霹雳斗智斗勇，一次次挫败他们的阴谋。他们在任务中相互协作，发挥各自特长，不仅帮动物们解决问题，还向动物们学习本领，一起成长。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823104500 +0800" stop="20250823110000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">宇宙护卫队之钢甲霸王龙</title>
    <desc lang="en">为了保护地球居民，宇宙护卫队再次出发，与晴天霹雳斗智斗勇，一次次挫败他们的阴谋。他们在任务中相互协作，发挥各自特长，不仅帮动物们解决问题，还向动物们学习本领，一起成长。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823110000 +0800" stop="20250823113000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">乡遇食光 – 砂拉越</title>
    <desc lang="en">亚答糖在砂拉越不但可以做甜品，还能做咸食，比如卤鸭、炒面、马来风味料理都可以找到亚答糖的独特味道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823113000 +0800" stop="20250823120000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">贫民窟美食探索 -乡镇篇</title>
    <desc lang="en">对于生活在民都鲁工业区的伊班人来说，美味的餐点总是触手可及。森林就是他们的超级市场。当自己种植食材时，就不会挨饿了。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823120000 +0800" stop="20250823130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">阿顺有煮意 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">《阿顺有煮意》今天的顺客，为什么让阿顺特别期待？原来这是阿顺首次迎来一群资历超过三十年的 “大哥级别”艺人 — 刘谦益、陈澍城、朱厚任和陈建彬！难得请来四位前辈，阿顺也为今天的佳肴放了很多心思。面对这四位爱讲话又急着帮忙的大哥，阿顺是否招架得住？四位历经风雨沧桑的艺人，又会给拍摄带来怎么样的天气呢？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130000 +0800" stop="20250823140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">黄金年华之斗歌竞艺 2025 S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">年过半百的乐龄人士，在为家庭和事业奉献多年后，终于迎来了人生的新篇章。那些藏在心底的梦想，如今将再次点亮舞台！《黄金年华》除了是一场歌艺竞赛，对参赛者来说更是一段难得的学习之旅。参赛者不仅能拜师学艺，也能交到志同道合的朋友。大家在一起展现真我、切磋技艺，以歌会友，让生活更喜乐安康。新系列的节目将延续团战的形式，为乐龄朋友们提供一个更多元、更有趣的荣誉舞台，让大家拥有同样的机会，携手走到最后。_x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823140000 +0800" stop="20250823153000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">寻味安徽第一季</title>
    <desc lang="en">旨在传播安徽美食文化，点亮安徽各地美食风味地图。每一期围绕城市最具代表性或最富有特色美食制作节目，体现安徽本地的风土人情和饮食文化，打造独具安徽特色的美食文化IP。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823153000 +0800" stop="20250823160000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">匠心传承 (2023)</title>
    <desc lang="en">匠心传承 (2023).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160000 +0800" stop="20250823163000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">亚洲面包巡礼</title>
    <desc lang="en">面包在亚洲形成了一种新的潮流，在这各种面包全景展开的战场里，让我们深入了解面包传统，看看中国、日本、台湾和韩国最具代表性的面包是什么。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823163000 +0800" stop="20250823173000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">时光倾城</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hanzo将月心掳走软禁，月心看见 Hanzo 前尘往事。月心获救，Hanzo 被捕，禾风则消耗过度晕倒。月心得知禾风默默付出对他剖白，禾风不敢承认内心感情。禾风知裘先生阴谋后向阿迪透露神秘力量，三人联手调查发现 Hanzo，TJ 的关系。Hanzo为保护月心，不顾自身安危供出裘先生犯罪证据…….</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823173000 +0800" stop="20250823183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">时光倾城</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hanzo提出合作，禾风将信将疑配合给 Hanzo 争取时间偷法器。Hanzo 得手后逃命， TJ 被枪伤身故，法器回到裘先生手中。 Hanzo 潜逃时通知禾风接应，月心发现春发之死与 Hanzo 有关，伤心欲绝。裘先生将月心禾风掳走，囚禁禾风在毒气室威胁月心将力量转移。Hanzo 暗中计划救出月心.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823183000 +0800" stop="20250823190000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城六点半</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《狮城6点半》每日为您提供最全面的本地新闻头条与报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823190000 +0800" stop="20250823200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">天雷正式认正彦做干儿子，又认真又讲究，让大家都很惊讶。他看出明凤担心正彦身世曝光，假装没听见秘密，悄悄把祖传平安扣戴在正彦身上。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823200000 +0800" stop="20250823210000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">嘉良假装要跟正彦公平竞争补助，没想到一龙突然把合约交给嘉良，让正彦措手不及。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210000 +0800" stop="20250823220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">缤纷万千在昇菘 S37</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《金禾歌唱新人王》第三场半决赛，六强排名是否会有更动？金曲奖得奖音乐人，片山凉太将用歌声陪你过个有声有色的周六！_x000d__x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823220000 +0800" stop="20250823223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817003000 +0800" stop="20250817023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">来看我们的演唱会</title>
    <desc lang="en">节目主打“真live”“全开麦”“放肆嗨”的演唱会式嗨点，旨在带动全民一起为音乐疯狂，跨越时空界限触动全民情绪共振。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817023000 +0800" stop="20250817090000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817090000 +0800" stop="20250817091400 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">羽衣甘蓝是一种富含23种必需营养素的超级食物，可满足日常膳食需求。我们的有机纯羽衣甘蓝粉无添加剂、防腐剂、抗氧化剂和色素，适合所有年龄段人群，有助于保持健康.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817091400 +0800" stop="20250817091600 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">抽气机加耐用压缩袋，小巧轻便吸力强，可节省高达2/3的收纳空间。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817091600 +0800" stop="20250817093000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">FEM &amp; HOM 防脱发套组，恢复头皮健康，减少男女头发稀疏问题。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817093000 +0800" stop="20250817094400 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">多功能不粘料理锅，一锅多盘，满足不同烹煮方式的需求！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817094400 +0800" stop="20250817094600 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">全套组合菜刀、剪刀、砧板，让你下厨更轻松！菜刀和剪刀附专业磨刀套！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817094600 +0800" stop="20250817100000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">18公斤四轮电动代步车，时尚轻巧可折叠，方便带出国！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817100000 +0800" stop="20250817120000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">17号音乐仓库 (第二季)</title>
    <desc lang="en">五位全新音乐人梁龙、胡夏、白举纲、希林娜依·高、黄子弘凡以歌手形象反转担任Live House工作人员，以全新姿态再度开启这趟音乐旅程。同时，节目带着全新口号“总有快乐发声”，将和观众一起共同见证更多生活中的美好与惊喜。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817120000 +0800" stop="20250817121400 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shakura结合先进日本科技，专注于解决色斑问题。采用温和、非侵入性的疗程方式，无需激光或刺激性化学成分，帮助淡化黑斑、痘印与肤色不均。每项疗程都根据顾客的肌肤状况量身定制，帮助肌肤恢复自然光泽。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817121400 +0800" stop="20250817121600 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">说再见脏地板，迎接闪亮干净！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817121600 +0800" stop="20250817123000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">果冻形态的关节保健品，含葡萄糖胺、软骨素、第2型胶原蛋白、抗炎草本等关节保健营养素，有助于修复软骨和缓解关节发炎症状，味道好，容易服用又方便。提早开始给软骨和滑液“加加油”，关节才能用得久、用得顺！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817123000 +0800" stop="20250817124400 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">护发要趁早！Ellixi打造更健康、更亮丽秀发。Ellixi 纯天然植物萃取、含精油和有助于护发的重要营养素，有助于促进头发生长，减少脱发。无论您是头发稀疏、干燥问题，或是希望保持浓密秀发，Ellixi都能帮助你滋养头皮，恢复秀发光泽，且不留任何残留。_x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817124400 +0800" stop="20250817124600 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">透气、舒适、安全，适合敏感肌肤使用的Ultimo凉感被，.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817124600 +0800" stop="20250817130000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">The Wonder Shop</title>
    <desc lang="en">Karihome Gold 成人羊奶粉口感顺滑，富含易吸收的羊奶蛋白，采用先进脱膻技术，保留营养与纯净口感，连肠胃敏感者都能安心饮用。 还特别添加叶黄素、胶原蛋白和 Omega-3，支持眼睛、关节及心脑血管健康。每天两杯，补钙增强免疫力，适合全家饮用，特别适合年长人士，助力骨骼健康与活力。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817130000 +0800" stop="20250817140000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">上山下海过一夜 - 漂留亚洲</title>
    <desc lang="en">三立最强旅游实境《上山下海过一夜》，由4位独具风格的专业职人共同组队开启上山下海全球大冒险，带你享受大自然好生活体验世界好人情，也看见台湾我们故乡的美丽。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817140000 +0800" stop="20250817143000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">7天我可以</title>
    <desc lang="en">要在7天内学会一门运动到底有可能吗？《7天我可以！》系列中，新闻主播们拜访本地运动健儿，挑战在一周内突破自己的体能极限，完成运动员们设下的挑战！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817143000 +0800" stop="20250817150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">逛遍全中国</title>
    <desc lang="en">旅行体验师将去到贵州、广西 、广东 三个省份的宝藏景区，品尝当地特色美食，领略当地的好山好水，感受当地深厚人文历史和奇特风味。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817150000 +0800" stop="20250817160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绝妙的遗产</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述身无分文的33岁单身女子与拥有百亿财产的80岁冷面店老板伪装结婚，一夜之间成为了四个儿子的继母后，他们之间克服偏见的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817160000 +0800" stop="20250817165500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绝妙的遗产</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述身无分文的33岁单身女子与拥有百亿财产的80岁冷面店老板伪装结婚，一夜之间成为了四个儿子的继母后，他们之间克服偏见的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817165500 +0800" stop="20250817175000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绅士与小姐</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述为了自己的选择而寻找幸福的「绅士」，与贫穷家庭出身的「小姐」相遇后发生的波澜壮阔故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817175000 +0800" stop="20250817184500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绅士与小姐</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述为了自己的选择而寻找幸福的「绅士」，与贫穷家庭出身的「小姐」相遇后发生的波澜壮阔故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817184500 +0800" stop="20250817191500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">国庆群众大会2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 黄循财总理在工艺教育学院总部发表国庆群众大会演讲。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817191500 +0800" stop="20250817194500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">小岛国 大发现2</title>
    <desc lang="en">新加坡缆车伴随国人近半世纪，你可想过缆车夜间休班后会去哪里？缆车会进行怎样的定期检查？另外，你是否知道新加坡传统米酒由什么酿成？酿酒工序看似简单，实则蕴含无尽心血和传承。为了提高国人的环保意识，新加坡随处可见的黄色织物回收箱，它可回收哪些物品？如何再循环衣物减少浪费呢？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817194500 +0800" stop="20250817200000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">上蔡乐</title>
    <desc lang="en">娘惹菜采用大量辛香料，且须手工捣碎，对主持人而言是个大挑战。两人向本地娘惹菜私厨Danial学做娘惹杂菜和叁巴臭豆炒虾仁，本来信心满满，结果却阴沟里翻船，招来嘉宾团的差评，究竟哪里出错？恩来和可乐信心受挫，他们还有勇气接受挑战吗？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817200000 +0800" stop="20250817211500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">国庆群众大会2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 黄循财总理在工艺教育学院总部发表国庆群众大会演讲。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817211500 +0800" stop="20250817214500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">三吃客</title>
    <desc lang="en">这一期，三吃客将品尝3道不同的羊肉料理，包括传统古早味的羊肉汤，创意十足的羊骨茶，以及小巧美味的羊肉汉堡，究竟是哪一道最没羊膻味、最令人惊艳呢？_x000d__x000a_三吃客除了大饱口福，也到访本地牧羊场，了解一些关于山羊的知识和体验牧羊人的生活。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817214500 +0800" stop="20250817220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">星牌运动员</title>
    <desc lang="en">记得学生时期的全国体能测验吗？时隔多年，星牌运动员将再次接受测验，而测验的创办人Robert Tan也会在旁观察、纠正错误。他们能否坚持跑完2.4公里？谁会是最全能、最强手的星牌运动员？星牌队长戚玉武和李腾根据体能测验的成绩筛选心仪队员，并带领团队，一起勇闯射箭场！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817220000 +0800" stop="20250817230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">强悍媳妇</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) 雯莉侥幸地从绑匪那儿逃脱。雯莉到医院一看见阮夫人便当面质问有关她被绑架的事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817230000 +0800" stop="20250817234500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817234500 +0800" stop="20250817234500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">智异山</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 故事围绕着守护智异山国家公园的“守山队队员”而展开。全智贤饰演的王牌守山员遇上朱智勋所饰演的新进守山员，两人携手揭开埋藏在智异山中的秘密。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817234500 +0800" stop="20250818003500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">智异山</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 故事围绕着守护智异山国家公园的“守山队队员”而展开。全智贤饰演的王牌守山员遇上朱智勋所饰演的新进守山员，两人携手揭开埋藏在智异山中的秘密。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818003500 +0800" stop="20250818024500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">牛气冲天的Riam</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818024500 +0800" stop="20250818144500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818144500 +0800" stop="20250818150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818150000 +0800" stop="20250818160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">型男大主厨 S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">《型男大主厨》由金钟主持人曾国城、卓文萱及专业主厨詹姆士、吴秉承等人所共同主持。 主要有「超省时宴客菜」「五星级料理秀」「型男同乐会」「新厨挑战赛」等主题，除了综艺节目笑料，更能获得实质料理知识。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818160000 +0800" stop="20250818170000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">幸福乡味</title>
    <desc lang="en">世界上什么菜最好吃？答案是家乡菜。异地生活的游子，一想起家乡美味，总会真情流露、百感交集。全新资讯节目《幸福乡味》，主持人将寻访在世界各地的新加坡人，烹调他们所熟悉的家乡美食，传递来自家的问候与温馨。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818170000 +0800" stop="20250818180000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">一起吃晚餐吗?</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧改编同名网络漫画，讲述因为曾经有过痛苦离别的恋爱经历，以及受到“单身文化”的影响，渐渐对恋爱冷感，爱情感知退化的两个男女，通过共进晚餐慢慢找回爱情的甜爱罗曼史。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818180000 +0800" stop="20250818190000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">闪婚</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) 剧情主要讲述一个女性社交名流和一个富有少爷之间搞笑浪漫的爱情故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818190000 +0800" stop="20250818200000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的眼裡只有你</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 当庆俊向盈怡求婚时，接到了华景的电话，得知海美试图轻生。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818200000 +0800" stop="20250818210000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的眼裡只有你</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 大家一听说海美服药过量，便立刻赶到医院探望她。海美见到盈怡时大声斥责她。另一方面，元燮向允熙透露世俊已经发现自己是他们的儿子。_x000d_ _x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818210000 +0800" stop="20250818220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾 S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">莎莎主持《大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾》, 带领大胃王们吃遍台湾，从传统美食、夜市小摊到饭店大餐，呈现最原汁原味的料理，藉由大胃王们幸福地享用美食，让人看了食慾大开！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818220000 +0800" stop="20250818230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绝佳的解决士</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 莎拉搬进律成家后，开始着手寻找与这两起案件有关的证据，却意识到穿着限量版运动鞋的一位男人很有可能就是掌握着揭开真相的关键。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818230000 +0800" stop="20250818233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818233000 +0800" stop="20250818233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾 S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">莎莎主持《大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾》, 带领大胃王们吃遍台湾，从传统美食、夜市小摊到饭店大餐，呈现最原汁原味的料理，藉由大胃王们幸福地享用美食，让人看了食慾大开！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818233000 +0800" stop="20250819003000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾 S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">莎莎主持《大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾》, 带领大胃王们吃遍台湾，从传统美食、夜市小摊到饭店大餐，呈现最原汁原味的料理，藉由大胃王们幸福地享用美食，让人看了食慾大开！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819003000 +0800" stop="20250819013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的眼裡只有你</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 当庆俊向盈怡求婚时，接到了华景的电话，得知海美试图轻生。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819013000 +0800" stop="20250822233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的眼裡只有你</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 大家一听说海美服药过量，便立刻赶到医院探望她。海美见到盈怡时大声斥责她。另一方面，元燮向允熙透露世俊已经发现自己是他们的儿子。_x000d_ _x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250822233000 +0800" stop="20250823003000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">台湾1001个故事 S10</title>
    <desc lang="en">这个节目介绍台湾当地的美食与老板背后的动人故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823003000 +0800" stop="20250823013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的眼裡只有你</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 允熙得知她杀害的那个人是盈怡已故的丈夫，为了世俊的利益想要保守一切秘密。元燮计划除掉盈怡。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823013000 +0800" stop="20250823023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的眼裡只有你</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 盈怡带着美丽娜拜访庆俊的家人，盈怡天真地提醒允熙要小心元燮以防远斜对她下手。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823023000 +0800" stop="20250823100000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100000 +0800" stop="20250823130000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">天赐的声音 S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">季赛制与前三季不同，共邀请十二至十五位歌手担任音乐合伙人，并由他们自行进行两两配对演唱；如果合伙人数量为单数，则最终会有一名歌手在该集节目轮空。在每轮歌曲演唱后，声音鉴赏团成员会在已演唱的歌曲中共同选出目前的待定金曲，最终获得推荐金曲的搭档将分别担任下一期的队长，带领本队的三对歌手进行歌曲表演并角逐金曲称号。从第二阶段起，每期均会由在场观看录制的两百位观众额外选出一首人气金曲。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130000 +0800" stop="20250823140000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾 S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">莎莎主持《大胃王来了! 吃遍台湾》, 带领大胃王们吃遍台湾，从传统美食、夜市小摊到饭店大餐，呈现最原汁原味的料理，藉由大胃王们幸福地享用美食，让人看了食慾大开！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823140000 +0800" stop="20250823150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">生活达人S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 本节目为您找出在不同领域有杰出表现的达人。他们可能不起眼、也容易被我们忽略，但他们拥有的技能绝对是无人能及的。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823150000 +0800" stop="20250823160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绝妙的遗产</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述身无分文的33岁单身女子与拥有百亿财产的80岁冷面店老板伪装结婚，一夜之间成为了四个儿子的继母后，他们之间克服偏见的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160000 +0800" stop="20250823170000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">绝妙的遗产</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述身无分文的33岁单身女子与拥有百亿财产的80岁冷面店老板伪装结婚，一夜之间成为了四个儿子的继母后，他们之间克服偏见的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823170000 +0800" stop="20250823180000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">你太过分了</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 命运的转折让一位耀眼的明星歌手和她的模仿者的生活交织在一起，经历了爱、恨与怜悯。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823180000 +0800" stop="20250823190000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">你太过分了</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 命运的转折让一位耀眼的明星歌手和她的模仿者的生活交织在一起，经历了爱、恨与怜悯。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823190000 +0800" stop="20250823210000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">来看我们的演唱会</title>
    <desc lang="en">节目主打“真live”“全开麦”“放肆嗨”的演唱会式嗨点，旨在带动全民一起为音乐疯狂，跨越时空界限触动全民情绪共振。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210000 +0800" stop="20250823220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">强悍媳妇</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) 一段关于雯莉被绑架的对话录音档疯狂地被传播。嘉南对阮夫人的所作所为感到非常失望。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823220000 +0800" stop="20250823230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">强悍媳妇</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) 小冰慌张地打电话给嘉玲通知她阮夫人被丁格抓走，但是没人相信，以为是阮夫人的苦肉计。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823230000 +0800" stop="20250823233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817000000 +0800" stop="20250817090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817090000 +0800" stop="20250817093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Makan Skuad</title>
    <desc lang="en">Makan Skuad is a fun children cooking show, a spin-off from the successful Skuad Cilik series. In each episode, the squad will be given the enormous task of researching and preparing a local dish. Follow their journey in in their quest to uncover stories and knowledge about the food we love and cooking up a storm to be critiqued by the professionals and personalities of the week for their verdict on the dish.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817093000 +0800" stop="20250817100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aroma Puncak Borneo S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The journey of a nomad to the peaks of the highlands in Borneo. Exploring gastronomy and cuisine while getting to know the customs and cultures of various ethnic groups on the Land of the Hornbills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817100000 +0800" stop="20250817110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Perang Malam Ini</title>
    <desc lang="en">Talkshow with guest celebrity and popular singer entertainining each week in the show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817110000 +0800" stop="20250817120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kembara Kasih S5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kembara Kasih kicks off Season 5 with Dalina Jaapar, passing the baton to her first celebrity host, Fadli Kamsani. Together with his volunteer, Zulayqha Zulkifli, they travel to Quezon city, Philippines, to visit a group of homeless people. Unique to them, home means living under a bridge, by the canal. Discover how vulnerable their day-to-day living is, through Fadli and Zulayqha as they navigate through their world under the bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817120000 +0800" stop="20250817123000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jalan Jalan Season 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join our documentary series as we traverse Indonesian cities, uncovering new and exciting places brimming with culture and fun. Embark on an adventure to experience the vibrant heart of Indonesia like never before. Each episode is a captivating journey that immerses you in the local way of life, providing a deeper connection to this enchanting archipelago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817123000 +0800" stop="20250817130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Food Adventure</title>
    <desc lang="en">Embark on an epic cilinary adventure across the diverse cities of Indonesia in this captivating documentary series. Join our intrepid hosts as they traverse the archipelago in search of delectable and culturally rish dishes. From bustling street food stalls to hidden gems, each episode unveils the flavors, stories and traditions that make Indonesia cuisine a tantalizing journey worth savoring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817130000 +0800" stop="20250817140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Siapa Jaga Mak S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Amin and Hajah, together with their mother, move into their new home. Amin struggles with cargiving as Arif's rarely available to help due to his busy schedule. Hajah requests a week-long cruise before giving birth. Tijah met with her estranged children. Patrick initially refuses chemotherapy but family gives him full support and he undergoes treatment but suffers side effects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817140000 +0800" stop="20250817150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Siapa Jaga Mak S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saloma chokes while eating fishball alone at home, sparking arguments between her sons about their responsibilities towards their mother. Saloma is concerned about Hajah's pregnancy but faces resistance when offering advice. This causes friction between Amin and his wife Hajah. Patrick tries to move back to his own house while Harith tries to help Nurin who he thinks is facing caregiver burnout. Ismail's decision to work temporarily at a coffee shop creates conflict with his son Iskandar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817150000 +0800" stop="20250817184500 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">National Day Parade 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">NDP 2025 celebrates the nation's 60th birthday with the theme “Majulah Singapura” and pays tribute to everyday heroes and pioneers who have shaped the nation's journey, while embracing the hopes of future generations. For the first time, the parade extends from the Padang to the Marina Bay and features dynamic military displays, light projections and a spectacular fireworks finale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817184500 +0800" stop="20250817191500 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (Malay &amp; Mandarin Speeches).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817191500 +0800" stop="20250817193000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Unboxing Art</title>
    <desc lang="en">The evolution of Batik has transformed through the years and what better way to understand its influence on the Singapore art scene than Zaki meeting two artists who are masters in that field, both senior and new. With the aid of master batik practitioner, Ika Zahri Sarkasi, and mark making designer, Huda Hosni, watch Zaki attempts to unearth how batik is one many art forms that can stand the test of time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817193000 +0800" stop="20250817200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817200000 +0800" stop="20250817211500 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (English Speech).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817211500 +0800" stop="20250817213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Air Tangan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join young influencer Fikah Zainal as she gets her hands dirty in the kitchen for a cooking lesson with her beloved grandmother, Madam Norah, on a traditional family recipe, fried beef lungs with potato and glass noodles. She then shares with her grandmother the recipe for one of her favourite food - Satay Burger!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817213000 +0800" stop="20250817223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cinta Bukan Milik Kita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Manis gets lost in the jungle to work on her thesis. Redza manages to find her and reminisces their past together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817223000 +0800" stop="20250817233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Andai Itu Takdirnya</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tan Sri Abbas is furious upon learning about Aizril's gold investment. Their argument escalates to the biggest yet within the family, leading to tension between them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817233000 +0800" stop="20250818000000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818000000 +0800" stop="20250818090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818090000 +0800" stop="20250818093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Beyblade Burst QuadDrive</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language Malay and English) The story centers on Bel Daizora, the leader of the Bey graveyard "Phantom's Gate". Bel, who holds Destruction Belfyre, declares war on Bladers across the world. With Ranzo Kiyama and Bashara Suiro, their journey unfolds as Bel advances to becoming the Dark Prince.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818093000 +0800" stop="20250818100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Makan Xtrim</title>
    <desc lang="en">Do you think a macho man is able to take sour food? What if we give him Indian Gooseberry, Belimbing Asam, Sauerkraut and Umeboshi? Can he and our adventurous foodies stomach and swallow these sour delicacies? Or do we need to standby a puke bucket?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818100000 +0800" stop="20250818110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Mengejar Mentari</title>
    <desc lang="en">Irma, a diploma holder, stopped working when her first child is born. Her family's economic situation becomes unstable as her husband, Rahim is job-hopping. As such, Irma and her family stay with her mum, Sapiah, who receives objections from her children, Irma &amp; Khairul about her relationship with a younger man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818110000 +0800" stop="20250818120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">I Love You, Stupid</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iris calls her father to complain about Firman. Firman does something unexpected that surprises Iris, Daus and Fatimah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818120000 +0800" stop="20250818130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Makan INC</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ashraf and Sofia get into a heated argument over the future ownership of Aneka Mi Minah. Aminah reluctantly agrees to let Sofia take over the stall for one year, but she is angered by Sofia's close friendship with Helmi. Helmi's past catches up on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818130000 +0800" stop="20250818140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">7 Hari</title>
    <desc lang="en">3 months into her mothers marriage to Aman, Cinta who was happy is now reserved and fearful of men. Life with Aman has been nothing but a hellhole for her and she wishes to put a stop to it all. She only has 7 days before he leaves again. And then, Cinta finds out that she is pregnant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818140000 +0800" stop="20250818150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ada Dua Cinta</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tells the story of two beautiful girls who have very different lives, named Mecca and Medina. Where Mecca was raised by Rohim and Aisyah, a husband and wife whose life was full of hardship. But in this family, Mecca's life never lacked love from her father and mother. Meanwhile, Medina lives in wealth, whatever he asks for, Bram his father, will always give him. However, unfortunately Medina's life was not as beautiful as other people imagined.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818150000 +0800" stop="20250818160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jejak Kita</title>
    <desc lang="en">EPISODE 3: ARTS &amp; CULTURE_x000d__x000a_We have a unique multiculturalism in Singapore. From local filmmakers to a world stage, our arts and culture is beginning to make its mark internationally. How much of our artistic inclinations come from British influences, and how much from regional roots? Have traditional songs and dance evolved into a modern art to keep up with times? In this episode, we explore what it means to be a truly "multicultural" country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818160000 +0800" stop="20250818170000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Shakira</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rizal brings Rykal out of the house without Kartini's knowledge and threatens Shakira that she will not be able to see Rykal again if she does not meet him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818170000 +0800" stop="20250818180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cinta Bukan Milik Kita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Manis gets lost in the jungle to work on her thesis. Redza manages to find her and reminisces their past together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818180000 +0800" stop="20250818183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Beyblade Burst QuadDrive</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language Malay and English) The story centers on Bel Daizora, the leader of the Bey graveyard "Phantom's Gate". Bel, who holds Destruction Belfyre, declares war on Bladers across the world. With Ranzo Kiyama and Bashara Suiro, their journey unfolds as Bel advances to becoming the Dark Prince.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818183000 +0800" stop="20250818190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Lesung S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yusuf decides not to sell Lesung but to take leave for the time being to take care of Veronica. He asks Gee to take charge while he is away. Yusuf cooks "Ayam Geprek" at home for Veronica. Everyone forgets its Ilyas's birthday and try to give Ilyas a birthday surprise. Khadijah cooks "Sambal Goreng Pulut Kuning" for Ilyas's birthday "cake". As they are preparing for the birthday celebration, Veronica is in pain to deliver her baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818190000 +0800" stop="20250818200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Dan Mimpi Pun Berguguran</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tragedy befalls Icha and Diana. Icha continues to suffer and relive her traumatic experience, shutting out Sofea and Saiful.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818200000 +0800" stop="20250818203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818203000 +0800" stop="20250818213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Travelawak: Projek Bapak Bapak</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comedy reality travel show, they will have to spend time together &amp; go through all the challenges that has been set..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818213000 +0800" stop="20250818223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Luruhnya Bunga Cinta 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Awal surprises Nuha by introducing her to his parents. Meanwhile, Nuh is feeling lost as he recovers from the accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818223000 +0800" stop="20250818233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Takdir Itu Milik Aku</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following Kamsiah's death, Dian finds it in her heart to forgive Datin Munirah but her resentment towards Zarif remains. Azura is furious when she learns that Zarif and Dian are slowly mending their marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818233000 +0800" stop="20250818233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818233000 +0800" stop="20250823000000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823000000 +0800" stop="20250823090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823090000 +0800" stop="20250823093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Geng Gajet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Geng Gajet follows a group of friends from various backgrounds who solve their everyday problems using their digital &amp; coding skills. Aly, the "leader" of the Gang - must find a way to open her father's bookstore together with her digitally savvy friend - from creating new products, to coding her own online store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823093000 +0800" stop="20250823100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Misi Gaia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Electricity used in homes requires the burning of fossil fuels. Amyrah Mustafa travels to Osaka, Japan to discover how organisations are using alternative sources of energy. She then parallels it with Singapore's efforts in this area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100000 +0800" stop="20250823110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kecoh Kahwin</title>
    <desc lang="en">Aminah does not seem to approve of Arif's girlfriend, much to his chagrin. Meanwhile, Nurul and Aminah discuss about Sham and they want to investigate about his background.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823110000 +0800" stop="20250823120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kasi Setel Itu Lirik</title>
    <desc lang="en">A variety show that requires the contestants to complete the lyrics of a song on an empty board infront of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823120000 +0800" stop="20250823130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Dan Mimpi Pun Berguguran</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rais brings Mazy to stay with Sofea and Mak Iti to take care of her. Icha begins to heal and Humaira decides to head back to KL to continue with her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130000 +0800" stop="20250823140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kids Nowadays</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jaafar and Farhan's stage props are destroyed moments before they step on the competition stage. Meanwhile, in the village, Jaafar's business is facing issues as trouble brews.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823140000 +0800" stop="20250823150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kids Nowadays</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hana's heart is broken when she sees Jaafar with Che Melur outside his house. As a result, she tries to open her heart to love someone else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823150000 +0800" stop="20250823160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Masak Macam Saya</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's Clash between Popular TV icons, Najip Ali and Era Farida! They are excellent in acting and hosting but can they cook? It's also the first time they compete in the kitchen. Who will cook and prepare the best Spicy Corn Fritters, Creme Brulee Tapioca Pudding and Spicy Tamarind Duck?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160000 +0800" stop="20250823180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Gracias Barcelona</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kamal and Fathia found love when studying in Barcelona but coming back to Malaysia to get married makes them ask, where did the love go? Fathia's ex also chooses to enter the scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823180000 +0800" stop="20250823183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Geng Gajet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Geng Gajet follows a group of friends from various backgrounds who solve their everyday problems using their digital &amp; coding skills. Aly, the "leader" of the Gang - must find a way to open her father's bookstore together with her digitally savvy friend - from creating new products, to coding her own online store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823183000 +0800" stop="20250823190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aroma Puncak Borneo S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The journey of a nomad to the peaks of the highlands in Borneo. Exploring gastronomy and cuisine while getting to know the customs and cultures of various ethnic groups on the Land of the Hornbills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823190000 +0800" stop="20250823200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Perang Malam Ini</title>
    <desc lang="en">Talkshow with guest celebrity and popular singer entertainining each week in the show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823200000 +0800" stop="20250823203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823203000 +0800" stop="20250823210000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Home Ideas</title>
    <desc lang="en">This program is perfect for those of you who are and want to build a house, especially one that has a minimalist size. Likewise, for those of you who are looking for interior design references for your home. A minimalist space in your home can be transformed into a comfortable and attractive area because there will be many tips given and you can apply it yourself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210000 +0800" stop="20250823213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Atlas Masjid Nusantara : Thailand &amp; Tanah Jawa</title>
    <desc lang="en">The host will take you to explore remote and modern mosques throughout the archipelago. A documentary travelogue that will provide a history of architectural information and deeper knowledge of remote mosques and its dissemination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823213000 +0800" stop="20250823223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cinta Bukan Milik Kita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Azalea pleads with Redza to stay married to her. Manis gets heartbroken and heads back to Jogjakarta, ready to get married with Radin. Redza continues to stay honest and fight for his true love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823223000 +0800" stop="20250823233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Andai Itu Takdirnya</title>
    <desc lang="en">Aizril's family experiences changes as they relocate to a new neighbourhood. Feeling uncomfortable in their new surroundings, Dania pleads with her father to return to their old home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817003000 +0800" stop="20250817010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817010000 +0800" stop="20250817013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817013000 +0800" stop="20250817090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817090000 +0800" stop="20250817093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Savaal Sapthaswaram</title>
    <desc lang="en">A fast-paced, exciting musical competition for teams comprising young Carnatic vocalists and instrumentalists. With rounds like "Raga Rapidfire" and "Guess the Raga" that supplement the main performance rounds, this is a show that is aimed at pleasing both the connoisseurs of classical music, as well as the lay viewer with an interest in good music. This showcase of young local talent is meant to both entertain and inspire our audiences, with the sheer wealth of talent on display.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817093000 +0800" stop="20250817123000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Kunguma Chimizh (1985)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Philomena and Ravi fall in love, but unemployment creates a barrier between them. They decide to take a break from their relationship. Finally, they end up working at the same company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817123000 +0800" stop="20250817150000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Ammane Mane</title>
    <desc lang="en">A physically challenged boy is raised by his single mother, who helps him overcome his physical limitations and lead a normal life. However, as a grown-up, he finds himself in a tight spot when faced with legal and emotional issues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817150000 +0800" stop="20250817184500 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">National Day Parade 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">NDP 2025 celebrates the nation's 60th birthday with the theme “Majulah Singapura” and pays tribute to everyday heroes and pioneers who have shaped the nation's journey, while embracing the hopes of future generations. For the first time, the parade extends from the Padang to the Marina Bay and features dynamic military displays, light projections and a spectacular fireworks finale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817184500 +0800" stop="20250817191500 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (Malay &amp; Mandarin Speeches).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817191500 +0800" stop="20250817194500 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot - Walk On The Wow Side</title>
    <desc lang="en">Little India is known for everything Indian but there's more. Join Joakim Gomez as he discovers hidden gems in what was voted as the world's 19th coolest neighbourhoods.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817194500 +0800" stop="20250817200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Enga Pettai S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an ever-changing Singaporean landscape, neighbourhoods hide endearing stories from the past. In Enga Pettai Season Two, we unearth stories from the "post-kampong" era through intimate conversations with the earliest HDB residents. Let us take a walk down memory lane !</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817200000 +0800" stop="20250817211500 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (English Speech).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817211500 +0800" stop="20250817213000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Enge Pettai Fillers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enge Pettai Fillers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817213000 +0800" stop="20250817220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817220000 +0800" stop="20250817220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Pulan Visaranai</title>
    <desc lang="en">Honest Raj a DCP investigating MLA case finds deeper roots with Anandraj auto driver who revolves behind political influence of RR who use him for entice women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817220000 +0800" stop="20250818010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Pulan Visaranai</title>
    <desc lang="en">Honest Raj a DCP investigating MLA case finds deeper roots with Anandraj auto driver who revolves behind political influence of RR who use him for entice women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818010000 +0800" stop="20250818013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818013000 +0800" stop="20250818090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818090000 +0800" stop="20250818093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Patti Samayal Pethi Kitchen</title>
    <desc lang="en">A cooking series that focus on vegetarian dishes, hosted by a Grandmother-Granddaughter duo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818093000 +0800" stop="20250818100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Vallamai Tharayo</title>
    <desc lang="en">Vallamai Tharayo follows the lives of Mahesh, an excellent doctor, as well as Sandhya, a chirpy art teacher and how their paths intertwine. Though Mahesh is backed by a good team of assistants he is haunted by the only failure in his career. With his competition waiting for him to fumble, his career becomes almost vulnerable. Will Mahesh and Sandhya be able to find the strength to overcome these challenges together?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818100000 +0800" stop="20250818103000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Indian Beat S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">A bilingual magazine show that serves as a platform by featuring activities and events organized by the various Tamil and Indian ethnic organizations around Singapore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818103000 +0800" stop="20250818110000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818110000 +0800" stop="20250818120000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Anjaraipetti S9</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anjaraipetti takes cookery onto a new level, transforming the home cooks into passionate chefs. The show helps viewers hone their culinary skills and brings new flavours to their kitchens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818120000 +0800" stop="20250818150000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Chakravarthy Thirumagal</title>
    <desc lang="en">Princess Kalamalini falls in love with Prince Udhayasuriyan. However, her friend also eyes him and is determined to win him at any cost even if it involves betraying the princess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818150000 +0800" stop="20250818160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Savaal Singapore 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">This game show concept is an adaptation from the English version of We are Singaporeans . All questions and everything about the show will be about Singapore .There will be 6 celebrities in each episode and they will banter with the host and contestants and also ask the questions!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818160000 +0800" stop="20250818190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Thaimel Aanai</title>
    <desc lang="en">Young Raja resolves to exact revenge for his mother's and sister's deaths. Nevertheless, his law-abiding police officer friend is unwilling to allow him to enforce the law on his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818190000 +0800" stop="20250818200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Samaippoma S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Samaippoma [Cookery Show] two dishes are presented in an entertaining way every episode, with lots of new varieties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818200000 +0800" stop="20250818203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Uppu Roti Chidambaram</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chidambaram runs a provision shop with his wife who is a retired teacher. They are blessed with 4 children, Vanmanthi, Shanker, Abhinaya &amp; Anbu. This story revolves around Vanmanthi and the struggles she faces in her extended family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818203000 +0800" stop="20250818210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818210000 +0800" stop="20250818213000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Sandamarutham</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Singapore story was no exception. Some resisted the inequality with rifles and swords while others resisted with their intellect and entrepreneurship. It was a long fight for individual rights and equal status as humans._x000d__x000a__x000d__x000a_Kanavu Seemai tells a story of how prominent pioneers of our, rose in status as equals of the colonial masters and how they uplifted the new migrants and nurtured the following generations that came to call Singapore home against a backdrop of c...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818213000 +0800" stop="20250818220100 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Theerpugal 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">A love story and an illegal liaison sets the stage for this episode. All good things must come to an end. The partners in crime enjoy the prime of their lives, until things fall apart and the law catches up with them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818220100 +0800" stop="20250818223000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Asura Vettai</title>
    <desc lang="en">Inspector Ganesan investigates Vettukilli who is an owner of a workshop and is suspected to assist in the brutal murders. Ameetha is hopeful she is getting nearer the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818223000 +0800" stop="20250818230000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Dhuruvangal</title>
    <desc lang="en">Set in a fictional law firm, Dhuruvangal - Truth Prevails, is an intense legal drama where battles are fought both in and out of the courtroom. Helmed by two individuals with very different ideologies, the law firm is set on a collision path right from the onset and becomes the perfect breeding ground for mistrust, envy and greed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818230000 +0800" stop="20250818233000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818233000 +0800" stop="20250818233000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818233000 +0800" stop="20250822220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250822220000 +0800" stop="20250823003000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Paayum Oli Nee Yenakku</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a catastrophe in his life, an entrepreneur with low light blindness embarks on a relentless hunt utilizing audio clues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823003000 +0800" stop="20250823010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823010000 +0800" stop="20250823090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823090000 +0800" stop="20250823093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Chhota Bheem S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chhota Bheem follows the adventures of a young boy named Bheem with his friends in protecting their village using his extraordinary strength and bravery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823093000 +0800" stop="20250823100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Chhota Bheem S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chhota Bheem follows the adventures of a young boy named Bheem with his friends in protecting their village using his extraordinary strength and bravery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100000 +0800" stop="20250823110000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Vasantham Junior Chef</title>
    <desc lang="en">Vasantham Junior chef is Vasantham's first culinary competition series for talented kids between the ages of 8 to 12 who are passionate about cooking and hold a burning desire to excel in culinary skills. _x000d__x000a_The show will give these promising young cooks the exciting opportunity to showcase their talent, culinary skills and passion for food through a series of delicious challenges and cook-offs._x000d__x000a_With lots of spice, drama, tears and joy,Vasantham Junior Chef is both hea...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823110000 +0800" stop="20250823113000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Muttaku</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of misfits try to make a home out of a haunted house coincidently and some intentionally. What happens to these individuals? what awaits? The Haunted Villa shall reveal more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823113000 +0800" stop="20250823120000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Muttaku</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of misfits try to make a home out of a haunted house coincidently and some intentionally. What happens to these individuals? what awaits? The Haunted Villa shall reveal more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823120000 +0800" stop="20250823130000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rayil Sneham</title>
    <desc lang="en">Popular host and actress Udaya is ready to make the journey of her life. Watch as she travels to interesting and intriguing destinations along the Railway Lines, starting from Singapore to Myanmar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130000 +0800" stop="20250823160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Motor Sundrum Pillai</title>
    <desc lang="en">A king and queen are murdered but their son survives and grows up to become a thief, who later decides to avenge the death of his parents and win back the throne.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160000 +0800" stop="20250823190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Race</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two stepbrothers own a huge stud farm and a horse racing business. When they learn that they have a common love interest, one of them tries to kill the other and inherit the insurance money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823190000 +0800" stop="20250823200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Lee Kuan Yew: In His Own Words</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lee Kuan Yew left an indelible mark on the world. In assembling some of his most insightful speeches and interviews, this film examines his values and ideas, many of which remain relevant today.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823200000 +0800" stop="20250823203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823203000 +0800" stop="20250823210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. _x000d_Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210000 +0800" stop="20250823220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">My Superstar Kudumbam 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Queenstown, Singapore's first satellite town, two families with young kids dive into_x000d_playful, action-packed challenges. Laughter fills the air, but it's the kids who steal the show_x000d_with surprise singing performances! With touching moments and a thrilling finish, this_x000d_episode celebrates family spirit, talent, and teamwork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817000000 +0800" stop="20250817000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817000300 +0800" stop="20250817003000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">The conflict in the Indonesian province of Aceh may have ended 20 years ago, but addressing human rights issues and ensuring equitable economic development for all Acehnese remain major challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817003000 +0800" stop="20250817010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817010000 +0800" stop="20250817013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Us</title>
    <desc lang="en">Have lunch in Singapore with a chef introducing a S$6 Michelin-endorsed hawker meal. Explore a hidden vegetarian hotspot inside a temple. And a halal food vlogger reveals a favourite food haunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817013000 +0800" stop="20250817020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can we break through our differences over a meal? This social experiment brings together three pairings of individuals who could not be more different to break down barriers of prejudice and tension.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817020000 +0800" stop="20250817023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817023000 +0800" stop="20250817030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817030000 +0800" stop="20250817040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Born in 1965</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gurmit Singh celebrates his 60th birthday by discovering traditions and attitudes towards ageing in Singapore and Japan, inspiring him to seek new purpose for life's next chapter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817040000 +0800" stop="20250817043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817043000 +0800" stop="20250817050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer flies to Lahore to get a close look at the city's most infamous street - Heera Mandi. Once the centre of royal court life, the street seems to be on the verge of a comeback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817050000 +0800" stop="20250817060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What lies beneath Singapore's polished exterior? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the ruins of Fort Serapong and Tanglin Barracks, uncovering hidden tales of war, resilience, and survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817060000 +0800" stop="20250817063000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817063000 +0800" stop="20250817070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">The conflict in the Indonesian province of Aceh may have ended 20 years ago, but addressing human rights issues and ensuring equitable economic development for all Acehnese remain major challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817070000 +0800" stop="20250817073000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817073000 +0800" stop="20250817080000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817080000 +0800" stop="20250817083000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817083000 +0800" stop="20250817090000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer flies to Lahore to get a close look at the city's most infamous street - Heera Mandi. Once the centre of royal court life, the street seems to be on the verge of a comeback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817090000 +0800" stop="20250817093000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817093000 +0800" stop="20250817100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can we break through our differences over a meal? This social experiment brings together three pairings of individuals who could not be more different to break down barriers of prejudice and tension.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817100000 +0800" stop="20250817100200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817100200 +0800" stop="20250817110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What lies beneath Singapore's polished exterior? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the ruins of Fort Serapong and Tanglin Barracks, uncovering hidden tales of war, resilience, and survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817110000 +0800" stop="20250817113000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817113000 +0800" stop="20250817120000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Us</title>
    <desc lang="en">Have lunch in Singapore with a chef introducing a S$6 Michelin-endorsed hawker meal. Explore a hidden vegetarian hotspot inside a temple. And a halal food vlogger reveals a favourite food haunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817120000 +0800" stop="20250817123000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817123000 +0800" stop="20250817130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817130000 +0800" stop="20250817130200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817130200 +0800" stop="20250817140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Japan Hour [English Subtitles]</title>
    <desc lang="en">Japanese researchers and entrepreneurs grapple with the impact of climate change on marine life, turning crisis into opportunity across coastal communities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817140000 +0800" stop="20250817143000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817143000 +0800" stop="20250817150000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer flies to Lahore to get a close look at the city's most infamous street - Heera Mandi. Once the centre of royal court life, the street seems to be on the verge of a comeback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817150000 +0800" stop="20250817153000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817153000 +0800" stop="20250817160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817160000 +0800" stop="20250817160200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817160200 +0800" stop="20250817170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Let Me Tell You A Story S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Beneath Sembawang's quiet streets lie stories of empire. From the 1930s to the 1970s, it was home to Britain's largest naval base in Asia – once among the most powerful outposts in the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817170000 +0800" stop="20250817173000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817173000 +0800" stop="20250817180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817180000 +0800" stop="20250817183000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817183000 +0800" stop="20250817191500 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (Malay &amp; Mandarin Speeches - With English subtitles).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817191500 +0800" stop="20250817200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817200000 +0800" stop="20250817213000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">National Day Rally 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Prime Minister Lawrence Wong delivers his National Day Rally Speech, ‘live' from Institute of Technical Education Headquarters. (English Speech - With English subtitles).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817213000 +0800" stop="20250817220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817220000 +0800" stop="20250817230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817230000 +0800" stop="20250817230300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250817230300 +0800" stop="20250818000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What lies beneath Singapore's polished exterior? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the ruins of Fort Serapong and Tanglin Barracks, uncovering hidden tales of war, resilience, and survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818000000 +0800" stop="20250818000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818000300 +0800" stop="20250818003000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818003000 +0800" stop="20250818010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">The conflict in the Indonesian province of Aceh may have ended 20 years ago, but addressing human rights issues and ensuring equitable economic development for all Acehnese remain major challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818010000 +0800" stop="20250818020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world._x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818020000 +0800" stop="20250818030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818030000 +0800" stop="20250818033000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Us</title>
    <desc lang="en">Have lunch in Singapore with a chef introducing a S$6 Michelin-endorsed hawker meal. Explore a hidden vegetarian hotspot inside a temple. And a halal food vlogger reveals a favourite food haunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818033000 +0800" stop="20250818040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818040000 +0800" stop="20250818043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818043000 +0800" stop="20250818050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer stretches the meaning of street' when he visits Maravanthuruthu, a picturesque village in Kerala that has undergone an enormous transformation to become a poster child for sustainability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818050000 +0800" stop="20250818060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What hidden histories lie within Singapore's iconic landmarks? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the National Gallery and Victoria Theatre, uncovering pivotal moments that shaped the nation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818060000 +0800" stop="20250818070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818070000 +0800" stop="20250818100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia First</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Top stories, business news and market updates from across the region as Asia gears up for the day ahead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818100000 +0800" stop="20250818110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What hidden histories lie within Singapore's iconic landmarks? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the National Gallery and Victoria Theatre, uncovering pivotal moments that shaped the nation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818110000 +0800" stop="20250818130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818130000 +0800" stop="20250818140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What lies beneath Singapore's polished exterior? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the ruins of Fort Serapong and Tanglin Barracks, uncovering hidden tales of war, resilience, and survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818140000 +0800" stop="20250818160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818160000 +0800" stop="20250818170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Born in 1965</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gurmit Singh celebrates his 60th birthday by discovering traditions and attitudes towards ageing in Singapore and Japan, inspiring him to seek new purpose for life's next chapter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818170000 +0800" stop="20250818170200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818170200 +0800" stop="20250818180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world._x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818180000 +0800" stop="20250818190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818190000 +0800" stop="20250818193000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818193000 +0800" stop="20250818200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818200000 +0800" stop="20250818210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818210000 +0800" stop="20250818220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore's Balancing Act: Trade-Offs Of A City-State</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore how city-states like Singapore safeguard sovereignty in a complex world. Host Kelly Latimer examines defence, diplomacy and resilience, revealing ancient wisdom and cutting-edge strategies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818220000 +0800" stop="20250818230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250818230000 +0800" stop="20250819000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What hidden histories lie within Singapore's iconic landmarks? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the National Gallery and Victoria Theatre, uncovering pivotal moments that shaped the nation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819000000 +0800" stop="20250819000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819000300 +0800" stop="20250819010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819010000 +0800" stop="20250819013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819013000 +0800" stop="20250819020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819020000 +0800" stop="20250819030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819030000 +0800" stop="20250819040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world._x000d_.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819040000 +0800" stop="20250819050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250819050000 +0800" stop="20250823000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore's Balancing Act: Trade-Offs Of A City-State</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore how city-states like Singapore safeguard sovereignty in a complex world. Host Kelly Latimer examines defence, diplomacy and resilience, revealing ancient wisdom and cutting-edge strategies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823000000 +0800" stop="20250823000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823000300 +0800" stop="20250823010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823010000 +0800" stop="20250823020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Born in 1965</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gurmit Singh continues his journey exploring marriage, friendship, and service leading him to Punjab, where he reflects on the importance of community and relationships in ones' golden years.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823020000 +0800" stop="20250823030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823030000 +0800" stop="20250823040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore's Balancing Act: Trade-Offs Of A City-State</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore how city-states like Singapore safeguard sovereignty in a complex world. Host Kelly Latimer examines defence, diplomacy and resilience, revealing ancient wisdom and cutting-edge strategies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823040000 +0800" stop="20250823050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823050000 +0800" stop="20250823060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823060000 +0800" stop="20250823070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823070000 +0800" stop="20250823073000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823073000 +0800" stop="20250823080000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823080000 +0800" stop="20250823083000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823083000 +0800" stop="20250823090000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823090000 +0800" stop="20250823093000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823093000 +0800" stop="20250823100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer stretches the meaning of street' when he visits Maravanthuruthu, a picturesque village in Kerala that has undergone an enormous transformation to become a poster child for sustainability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100000 +0800" stop="20250823100200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823100200 +0800" stop="20250823110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Born in 1965</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gurmit Singh continues his journey exploring marriage, friendship, and service leading him to Punjab, where he reflects on the importance of community and relationships in ones' golden years.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823110000 +0800" stop="20250823113000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823113000 +0800" stop="20250823120000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823120000 +0800" stop="20250823123000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823123000 +0800" stop="20250823130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Us</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lunch in Manila offers tasty meals for busy workers. Discover a carinderia with dishes that taste homemade. Let students take you on a street food hunt and get traditional cuisine from a jollijeep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130000 +0800" stop="20250823130200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823130200 +0800" stop="20250823140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823140000 +0800" stop="20250823143000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823143000 +0800" stop="20250823150000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">South Korea has sent thousands of children abroad under a flawed adoption system, which saw babies taken from their parents. Now many are beginning an often fruitless search for their birth families.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823150000 +0800" stop="20250823153000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823153000 +0800" stop="20250823160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer stretches the meaning of street' when he visits Maravanthuruthu, a picturesque village in Kerala that has undergone an enormous transformation to become a poster child for sustainability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160000 +0800" stop="20250823160200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823160200 +0800" stop="20250823170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What hidden histories lie within Singapore's iconic landmarks? Reuben Dhanaraj explores the National Gallery and Victoria Theatre, uncovering pivotal moments that shaped the nation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823170000 +0800" stop="20250823173000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823173000 +0800" stop="20250823180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823180000 +0800" stop="20250823183000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823183000 +0800" stop="20250823190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A Street Like This</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spancer stretches the meaning of street' when he visits Maravanthuruthu, a picturesque village in Kerala that has undergone an enormous transformation to become a poster child for sustainability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823190000 +0800" stop="20250823190200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823190200 +0800" stop="20250823200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Japan Hour [English Subtitles]</title>
    <desc lang="en">A moving episode on helping elderly Japanese fulfill their last wishes – through travel, family and a return home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823200000 +0800" stop="20250823203000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823203000 +0800" stop="20250823210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210000 +0800" stop="20250823210200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823210200 +0800" stop="20250823220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hidden Histories</title>
    <desc lang="en">What secrets lie within the ruins of Singapore's past? Reuben Dhanaraj uncovers the turbulent history of the Pasir Panjang Power Station.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823220000 +0800" stop="20250823223000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823223000 +0800" stop="20250823230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250823230000 +0800" stop="20250823230300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>