<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.5.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260111223000 +0800" stop="20260112003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Hating Game</title>
    <desc lang="en">Resolving to achieve professional success without compromising her ethics, Lucy embarks on a ruthless game of one-upmanship against cold and efficient nemesis Joshua, a rivalry that is complicated by her growing attraction to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112003000 +0800" stop="20260112013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dirty Home Rescue</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cleaning expert Hayley Leitch and her team of professional cleaners answer SOS calls from Britain's filthiest houses while identifying unhealthy habits which cause mess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112013000 +0800" stop="20260112020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112020000 +0800" stop="20260112024500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Cube USA S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dwyane Wade introduces The Cube, 15 square feet of steel-edged plexiglass where simple tasks become challenges; teams have nine lives to win seven games to beat The Cube for a chance to walk away with $250,000.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112024500 +0800" stop="20260112034500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Bake Off: The Professionals S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Twelve teams from top hotels, restaurants and small businesses compete to be crowned best patisserie team in Britain. Once again, judges Cherish Finden and Benoit Blin set exceedingly tricky challenges, to test the teams' creativity and precision. From towering, skyline-inspired chocolate constructions, to geometric tarts with moving parts, these incredible creations showcase bakers at the peak of their profession.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112034500 +0800" stop="20260112044500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Alexander Armstrong in Sri Lanka</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sri Lanka has a tumultuous past - civil wars, natural disasters and the economic crisis of 2022 that saw 700,000 people storm the President's home. As the country reopens to tourists, Alexander Armstrong speeds across the Indian Ocean to learn more about the land of serendipity'.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112044500 +0800" stop="20260112060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Survivor 47</title>
    <desc lang="en">18 new castaways battle it out on the islands of Fiji for a million dollars and the title of Sole Survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112060000 +0800" stop="20260112063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supa Strikas</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Malay) Follow Shakes, Rasta and the rest of the Supa Strikas on their quest to become the world's greatest football team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112063000 +0800" stop="20260112070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112070000 +0800" stop="20260112073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Gigantosaurus S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rocky, Bill, Tiny and Mazu are four young dinosaurs growing up in the Cretaceous period. Life is always an adventure: new volcanoes are popping up all the time, long-necked brachiosauruses and enormous triceratopses roam free, meteor showers light up the night sky and... the fierce Gigantosaurus reigns over it all!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112073000 +0800" stop="20260112080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Blippi 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Blippi's enthusiastic and expressive character engages children on their level through relatable adventures while sharing their excitement in discovering the world around us. Blippi is so entertaining, engaging and fun, kids don't even realize they're learning!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112080000 +0800" stop="20260112083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ollie &amp; Friends S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sonic almost had an accident at a playground and doesn't like playing at playgrounds anymore. It's now up to Ollie to teach Sonic that even at playgrounds, one needs to learn to play safe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112083000 +0800" stop="20260112084500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Wonderstar</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pinkfong crashes into the roof of a house, and in doing so, finds a best friend and problem-solving partner named Hogi. Pinkfong has the power to make wishes a reality, and Hogi has gained a lot of knowledge through reading. This inspires them to form Wonderstar', a problem-solving team that serves the townspeople of Wonderville - and beyond!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112084500 +0800" stop="20260112090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Wonderstar</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pinkfong crashes into the roof of a house, and in doing so, finds a best friend and problem-solving partner named Hogi. Pinkfong has the power to make wishes a reality, and Hogi has gained a lot of knowledge through reading. This inspires them to form Wonderstar', a problem-solving team that serves the townspeople of Wonderville - and beyond!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112090000 +0800" stop="20260112093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sesame Street Mecha Builders</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elmo, Cookie Monster, and Abby Cadabby are robot heroes-in-training who use their STEM superpowers to solve wacky larger-than-life problems!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112093000 +0800" stop="20260112093700 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sarah and Duck: Sr3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sarah and her loud, quacky friend Duck enjoy fun and heartfelt adventures as they explore the world around them. Joined by their quirky friends - John and Flamingo, Moon, Umbrella, Scarf Lady and Bag - Sarah and Duck's adventures include a magic show, playing with old toys, sticker collecting, catching the train and visiting a wonderful Planetarium Aquarium.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112093700 +0800" stop="20260112094500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sarah and Duck: Sr3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sarah and her loud, quacky friend Duck enjoy fun and heartfelt adventures as they explore the world around them. Joined by their quirky friends - John and Flamingo, Moon, Umbrella, Scarf Lady and Bag - Sarah and Duck's adventures include a magic show, playing with old toys, sticker collecting, catching the train and visiting a wonderful Planetarium Aquarium.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112094500 +0800" stop="20260112095300 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sarah and Duck: Sr3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sarah and her loud, quacky friend Duck enjoy fun and heartfelt adventures as they explore the world around them. Joined by their quirky friends - John and Flamingo, Moon, Umbrella, Scarf Lady and Bag - Sarah and Duck's adventures include a magic show, playing with old toys, sticker collecting, catching the train and visiting a wonderful Planetarium Aquarium.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112095300 +0800" stop="20260112100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sarah and Duck: Sr3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sarah and her loud, quacky friend Duck enjoy fun and heartfelt adventures as they explore the world around them. Joined by their quirky friends - John and Flamingo, Moon, Umbrella, Scarf Lady and Bag - Sarah and Duck's adventures include a magic show, playing with old toys, sticker collecting, catching the train and visiting a wonderful Planetarium Aquarium.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112100000 +0800" stop="20260112103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ollie And Friends S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Ollie Squad help an "old lady" to find a precious flower she lost. Little do they know, it's Poly-GON's ploy to lure them to the jungle. Noticing that a certain flower makes the Imp freeze, Poly-GON extracts the flower's essence to capture the Imp. Meanwhile, Rover can't stop sneezing and can't help but sense something fishy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112103000 +0800" stop="20260112110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Mumfie</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mumfie tells the story of a friendly, optimistic elephant and his best friends---a flying pig named Pinkey and a color-changing jellyfish named Jelly Bean---as they find adventure in daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112110000 +0800" stop="20260112113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Gigantosaurus S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rocky, Bill, Tiny and Mazu are four young dinosaurs growing up in the Cretaceous period. Life is always an adventure: new volcanoes are popping up all the time, long-necked brachiosauruses and enormous triceratopses roam free, meteor showers light up the night sky and... the fierce Gigantosaurus reigns over it all!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112113000 +0800" stop="20260112114500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Turbozaurs S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Turbozaurs are a dynamic team of friendly dinosaurs which can transform themselves instantly into amazing machines. They are discovered in the woods by three children, and together form a special rescue team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112114500 +0800" stop="20260112120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Turbozaurs S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Turbozaurs are a dynamic team of friendly dinosaurs which can transform themselves instantly into amazing machines. They are discovered in the woods by three children, and together form a special rescue team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112120000 +0800" stop="20260112123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supa Strikas</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Malay) Follow Shakes, Rasta and the rest of the Supa Strikas on their quest to become the world's greatest football team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112123000 +0800" stop="20260112130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112130000 +0800" stop="20260112133000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Miniforce: Super Dino Power [S3]</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) The peace in Blue City is disturbed by the new villain, the Captain Powerman! Our Miniforce must stop Powerman from punishing people who treated those "daily stuff" harshly. With their brand-new Super Dino Power, Miniforce transforms into dino rangers!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112133000 +0800" stop="20260112134500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Open Season: Call of Nature</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Boog and Elliot discover an abandoned Summer Camp in the middle of nowhere, they embark on a brave new adventure of creating a safe and special place to live that welcomes animals of every kind. Under the leadership of Boog and Elliot, the Campers must all work together to help create their own slice of paradise in the middle of the wilderness and to rediscover their inner wild.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112134500 +0800" stop="20260112140000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Open Season: Call of Nature</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Boog and Elliot discover an abandoned Summer Camp in the middle of nowhere, they embark on a brave new adventure of creating a safe and special place to live that welcomes animals of every kind. Under the leadership of Boog and Elliot, the Campers must all work together to help create their own slice of paradise in the middle of the wilderness and to rediscover their inner wild.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112140000 +0800" stop="20260112143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Saving Me</title>
    <desc lang="en">A super genius billionaire goes back in time to teach his 11-year-old self to be a better person.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112143000 +0800" stop="20260112150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pokemon Master Journeys: The Series (S24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join the continuing research fellowship adventures of Alola Champion Ash Ketchum and Goh, as they travel across all eight regions, including the new Galar region and Crown Tundra, based at Cerise Laboratory in Vermillion City in the Kanto region.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112150000 +0800" stop="20260112153000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112153000 +0800" stop="20260112160000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">FAM</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sammi's hero, Olivia, is impressed with her performance at the event and wants her to come work for her. Although Sammi is thrilled to learn that she'll get to work(intern) with her hero, she quickly realizes that it would crush her parents if she chooses Olivia over them. Meanwhile, Joy is secretly jealous that her own daughter embraces Olivia so much as an idol and not her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112160000 +0800" stop="20260112163000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Kin</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sparks fly between Ella and Shen Yang as they take a leap of faith together. As the issue of Khaled's adoption drags on, Rosnani and Adina's relationship sours further. Illya and Zaryf face troubles as Zaryf's work takes priority over their relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112163000 +0800" stop="20260112173000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Jamie's 5 Ingredient Mediterranean Meals</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brand-new series Jamie's 5 Ingredient Mediterranean Meals is packed full of easy, delicious and accessible recipes that use just five everyday ingredients. And to take things to the next level, all of the flavours are inspired by the Mediterranean.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112173000 +0800" stop="20260112180000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Nico's Cook in, Cook Out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nico's Cook in, Cook Out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112180000 +0800" stop="20260112190000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 03</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112190000 +0800" stop="20260112193000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112193000 +0800" stop="20260112203000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo USA S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this game show, hosted by the iconic RuPaul, the simplest of words could be worth thousands of dollars. Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112203000 +0800" stop="20260112210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Malaysia Gourmet With Justine Schofield</title>
    <desc lang="en">Embark on a tantalising adventure in this new eight-part series through Malaysia with Justine Schofield in "Malaysia Gourmet.” Explore the rich tapestry of Malay, Chinese, Indian, and indigenous flavours as Justine dives into the heart of Malaysia. From bustling markets to tranquil beaches, she immerses herself in local traditions, learns from talented chefs, and creates mouthwatering Malaysian dishes in exotic locations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112210000 +0800" stop="20260112214500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight With Highlights From Parliament</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112214500 +0800" stop="20260112221500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Alleys: Off The Beaten Tracks</title>
    <desc lang="en">Busan is the second largest city in Korea and a rapidly growing economic hub. As we explore the idyllic beaches of the Haeundae, we will also learn about Busan's important - and sometimes tragic - place in Korean history.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112221500 +0800" stop="20260112231000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Elsbeth S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Astute but unconventional attorney Elsbeth Tascioni utilizes her singular point of view to make unique observations and corner brilliant criminals alongside the NYPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112231000 +0800" stop="20260113000000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Transplant S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bash tries to reconnect with Elliot, after parting from his family abruptly years earlier. Bash and Mags fall into friendly competition at work in hopes of proving to Dr. Devi who should be hired for the fellowship. June tries group therapy for her self-harm issues. Theo faces a tribunal in hopes of getting his job back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113000000 +0800" stop="20260113003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Malaysia Gourmet With Justine Schofield</title>
    <desc lang="en">Embark on a tantalising adventure in this new eight-part series through Malaysia with Justine Schofield in "Malaysia Gourmet.” Explore the rich tapestry of Malay, Chinese, Indian, and indigenous flavours as Justine dives into the heart of Malaysia. From bustling markets to tranquil beaches, she immerses herself in local traditions, learns from talented chefs, and creates mouthwatering Malaysian dishes in exotic locations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113003000 +0800" stop="20260113013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">So Help Me Todd S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">A talented P.I. agrees to work as the in-house investigator for his mother, who is reeling from the recent dissolution of her marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113013000 +0800" stop="20260113020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113020000 +0800" stop="20260113030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo USA S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this game show, hosted by the iconic RuPaul, the simplest of words could be worth thousands of dollars. Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113030000 +0800" stop="20260113040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 03</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113040000 +0800" stop="20260113043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113043000 +0800" stop="20260113050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Nico's Cook in, Cook Out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nico's Cook in, Cook Out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112000000 +0800" stop="20260112010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">三个愿望</title>
    <desc lang="en">(PG)善美见子女们都不长进，担心自己一旦病逝，子女们无法自力更生，在前来安慰她的辉京怀里痛哭，被耀宗看见。耀宗误会辉京乘虚而入，与他发生冲突。善美极力阻止，结果昏迷倒地。辉京这时才透露善美患癌症的真相，耀宗感震惊！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112010000 +0800" stop="20260112020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">三个愿望</title>
    <desc lang="en">(PG)耀宗父在咖啡店再次遇见蔡花，得悉她为了生活跑去卖啤酒，还被酒客调戏。他同情蔡花，请她到家里做帮佣。蔡花非常能干，把家务处理得井井有条，全家都很喜欢她，唯独阿嬷对她有戒心，认为她想勾引耀宗父….</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112020000 +0800" stop="20260112030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">微笑正义</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着一群对揭发事实真相极具热忱的新闻工作者，从中带出新闻背后不为人知的秘密。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112030000 +0800" stop="20260112040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">微笑正义</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着一群对揭发事实真相极具热忱的新闻工作者，从中带出新闻背后不为人知的秘密。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112040000 +0800" stop="20260112050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">查某人</title>
    <desc lang="en">在一个坠楼女子的丧礼上，三个家庭主妇相识了―戴秀梅 (庄米雪) 是热心的前女警；云飞雪 (许美珍) 是典型的 Auntie；邱双喜 (洪乙心) 在家兼职卖美容品。三人发现女子的死存有疑点，联手侦查后发现凶手是死者的丈夫。秀梅和飞雪成立侦探社。飞雪对帅哥高翔 (张振寰) 存有幻想，双喜则对高翔印象不佳。秀梅和飞雪洗脱双喜虐待女佣罪名，双喜加入侦探社。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112050000 +0800" stop="20260112060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">查某人</title>
    <desc lang="en">在一个坠楼女子的丧礼上，三个家庭主妇相识了―戴秀梅 (庄米雪) 是热心的前女警；云飞雪 (许美珍) 是典型的 Auntie；邱双喜 (洪乙心) 在家兼职卖美容品。三人发现女子的死存有疑点，联手侦查后发现凶手是死者的丈夫。秀梅和飞雪成立侦探社。飞雪对帅哥高翔 (张振寰) 存有幻想，双喜则对高翔印象不佳。秀梅和飞雪洗脱双喜虐待女佣罪名，双喜加入侦探社。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112060000 +0800" stop="20260112070000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">特别的食物给特别的你</title>
    <desc lang="en">美国波士顿有家《社区便餐》非盈利组织针对各别病人的医疗情况，每天烹煮多达2400份营养餐点，免费送上门给低收入慢性和重病患者和家属享用。杨君伟实地了解组织如何把食物当成“药物”来减低病人的长期医疗开支。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112070000 +0800" stop="20260112073000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112073000 +0800" stop="20260112080000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">前线追踪</title>
    <desc lang="en">民情、民生、民意！【前线追踪】紧跟社会民生步伐，追踪调查时事动态，探讨新加坡人关心的课题，针对问题的核心追根究底。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112080000 +0800" stop="20260112090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">职不值得</title>
    <desc lang="en">职不值得.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112090000 +0800" stop="20260112093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城热话</title>
    <desc lang="en">周一至周五晚上7点，《狮城有约》谈话性栏目《狮城热话》以汇集多元声音及专家看法为目标，通过网络投票和引导观点碰撞，打造能让观众参与的时事舆论场。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112093000 +0800" stop="20260112100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">廉政行动 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">庞文伟因为知道学校入学门槛甚高，于是向有份参与收生工作的周文哲招手，向其他家长宣称有特别方法帮他们的子女考入德群中学，然后再请周文哲里应外合。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112100000 +0800" stop="20260112103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">焦点</title>
    <desc lang="en">《焦点》追踪国际时事，实地报道区域课题，以新加坡的视角分析时局发展的前因后果和潜在影响。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112103000 +0800" stop="20260112113000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">甘味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">甘味人生，是一出阐述「一家人世代传承家业」的励志写实戏剧。剧中赵家是制作传统手工酱油的一个大家庭，家庭的父母兄弟姊妹，共同为这个家努力打拼的历程为主轴，描写刻画每个人在打拼的过程当中，与纠结在矛盾的感情世界里，所经历的悲欢喜乐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112113000 +0800" stop="20260112130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">甘味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">甘味人生，是一出阐述「一家人世代传承家业」的励志写实戏剧。剧中赵家是制作传统手工酱油的一个大家庭，家庭的父母兄弟姊妹，共同为这个家努力打拼的历程为主轴，描写刻画每个人在打拼的过程当中，与纠结在矛盾的感情世界里，所经历的悲欢喜乐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112130000 +0800" stop="20260112133000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">一点新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《一点新闻》为您提供更新的本地与全球新闻头条。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112133000 +0800" stop="20260112140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着洪氏和龙氏家族、他们的工作生活和朋友展开，在之前的剧集中，龙景峰的幽灵与洪氏家族成员结下了深厚的友谊。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112140000 +0800" stop="20260112143000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着洪氏和龙氏家族、他们的工作生活和朋友展开，在之前的剧集中，龙景峰的幽灵与洪氏家族成员结下了深厚的友谊。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112143000 +0800" stop="20260112153000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着洪氏和龙氏家族、他们的工作生活和朋友展开，在之前的剧集中，龙景峰的幽灵与洪氏家族成员结下了深厚的友谊。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112153000 +0800" stop="20260112160000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">回归</title>
    <desc lang="en">区耀祖和邓丽娟离婚后，各自在两地经营粤德居，多年来相安无事，直至香港特区回归廿五周年，丽娟决定回港开设分店，更为争夺粤德居品牌，不惜与耀祖对簿公堂。幼子家健参加大湾区创业比赛，遇上担任导师的兄长家谦。兄弟长期分隔两地，南辕北辙，难免磨擦，但血浓于水，加深彼此认识后，重建深厚亲情，携手研发出高科技虚拟技术，让父母重新经历廿五年来的起起跌跌，明白原来一直关心对方，二人冰释前嫌，一家四口终得以团聚.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112160000 +0800" stop="20260112163000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">回归</title>
    <desc lang="en">区耀祖和邓丽娟离婚后，各自在两地经营粤德居，多年来相安无事，直至香港特区回归廿五周年，丽娟决定回港开设分店，更为争夺粤德居品牌，不惜与耀祖对簿公堂。幼子家健参加大湾区创业比赛，遇上担任导师的兄长家谦。兄弟长期分隔两地，南辕北辙，难免磨擦，但血浓于水，加深彼此认识后，重建深厚亲情，携手研发出高科技虚拟技术，让父母重新经历廿五年来的起起跌跌，明白原来一直关心对方，二人冰释前嫌，一家四口终得以团聚.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112163000 +0800" stop="20260112173000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112173000 +0800" stop="20260112183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112183000 +0800" stop="20260112193000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城有约</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 总结一天大小事，关心属于你我的家园。每逢星期一至五，傍晚6.30-7.30pm，与你相约！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112193000 +0800" stop="20260112200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">廉政行动 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">廉署接获匿名投诉，涉及一宗保险的行贿案件，投诉人指一班保险代理有组织地以不当手法赚取公司佣金，而主脑正是乐琦.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112200000 +0800" stop="20260112210000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">香港系列之原味道</title>
    <desc lang="en">香港人北上吃喝的热潮持续，久而久之或忽略了同样具有特色的本土味道。近年不少本地老字号、食肆、食品厂因不同原因结业，市民实应珍惜现时仍留下来、一直坚持「香港制造」的有心人。五位主持黄剑文、冼靖峰、潘静文、庄子璇、王汛文引领观众走进农田、鱼排，见识香港农业、渔业的发展。节目也会从土炮食材出发，寻找真正来自本港或香港制造的优质食材，借以支持一班坚守原味道的业界朋友，协助振兴本土经济。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112210000 +0800" stop="20260112220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">职不值得</title>
    <desc lang="en">职不值得.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112220000 +0800" stop="20260112224500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112224500 +0800" stop="20260112231500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">中东密探</title>
    <desc lang="en">在以金饰、银饰出名的塔伊夫中心市场研究各种金饰、还遇上路边贩售薄荷的热情少年，体验当地的市场生活。在天黑以前，前往沙乌地阿拉伯最大的博物馆之一，感受以过去塔伊夫传统市场为设计灵感的沉浸式博物馆体验。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112231500 +0800" stop="20260112231500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">流水迢迢</title>
    <desc lang="en">月落城少城主萧无瑕，忍辱负重潜伏梁国多年，化名为卫昭，背负佞臣骂名。卫昭为查清当年家族真相，试图掳走齐王案的唯一活口，但自己精心布置的计划却被突然出现的少女江慈所破坏。裴琰趁机将重伤的江慈养入府中，以求找到幕后“破坏者”。而卫昭的悲惨身世和民族大义也触动了天真烂漫的江慈，二人在相处中看到了彼此的闪光点，互生情愫。最终，卫昭、江慈、裴琰三人放下私人恩怨，共同对抗梁帝谢澈，实现了守护月落，建立清明天下的愿望。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112231500 +0800" stop="20260113001500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">流水迢迢</title>
    <desc lang="en">月落城少城主萧无瑕，忍辱负重潜伏梁国多年，化名为卫昭，背负佞臣骂名。卫昭为查清当年家族真相，试图掳走齐王案的唯一活口，但自己精心布置的计划却被突然出现的少女江慈所破坏。裴琰趁机将重伤的江慈养入府中，以求找到幕后“破坏者”。而卫昭的悲惨身世和民族大义也触动了天真烂漫的江慈，二人在相处中看到了彼此的闪光点，互生情愫。最终，卫昭、江慈、裴琰三人放下私人恩怨，共同对抗梁帝谢澈，实现了守护月落，建立清明天下的愿望。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113001500 +0800" stop="20260113011500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">斗罗大陆之燃魂战</title>
    <desc lang="en">全大陆高级魂师学院精英赛决赛结束，唐三跟小伙伴们恋恋不舍地分别，约定五年后重逢，便各自奔赴前程。而后，唐三随父亲唐昊去往隐秘山谷特训，提升自身能力。得益于唐昊的协助，唐三在积累经验的过程中变得更加沉稳，能从容应对更多挑战。戴沐白和朱竹清获得家族的肯定，分别成为星罗太子和准太子妃。奥斯卡和宁荣荣为提升实力开启艰苦训练，马红俊也外出游历以增长见识。就在此时，武魂殿的比比东暗中筹谋，横扫多个宗门，企图称霸斗罗大陆。于是，唐三召集伙伴创立唐门，坚守正义，勇挑重担。他们合力勇闯海神岛，与武魂殿对抗，不惧黑暗与强权，共同守护大陆和平，成长为坚毅的战士。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113011500 +0800" stop="20260113021500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">食尚玩家 S13</title>
    <desc lang="en">在新一辑的“食尚玩家 - 2 天1夜GO"里，主持人纳豆，六月，曾子余等会带领观众周游许多耳目一新的地方，国家包括韩国，日本（长崎，福冈），越南等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113021500 +0800" stop="20260113031500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113031500 +0800" stop="20260113041000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113041000 +0800" stop="20260113050500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260111233000 +0800" stop="20260112003000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">正义的重生</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此劇講述人生重來一次、 能力值滿點的熱血檢察官懲治絕對惡行的故事。背景配樂為英國作曲家 Holst 所寫行星組曲中，木星主題旋律穿梭劇情之中.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112003000 +0800" stop="20260112023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">亚洲新声</title>
    <desc lang="en">该节目由新声启航人Jessie J、新声召集人张靓颖、新声见证人张信哲、新声护航员尤长靖四位歌手加盟，携手亚洲新声代歌手共同开启跨越文化界限的音乐盛宴.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112023000 +0800" stop="20260112143000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112143000 +0800" stop="20260112150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112150000 +0800" stop="20260112160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">熊猫一家人</title>
    <desc lang="en">叛逆贤贤崽在线掀奶盆？二代熊猫人受父亲影响成为饲养员。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112160000 +0800" stop="20260112170000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">求学地图</title>
    <desc lang="en">本地少有以留学指南为主轴的资讯节目。节目以最为轻松的方式，让主持人重拾书包跟着本地留学生上学去，了解各国的教育制度、教育文化、就业市场。节目旨在给予本地家长和年轻人一个参考。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112170000 +0800" stop="20260112180000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">第二任丈夫</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述因无法停止的欲望酿成的悲剧，令一个女人无辜地失去家人，她在错综复杂的命运和爱情中展开复仇的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112180000 +0800" stop="20260112190000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">婚姻战争</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) 诺诺担心佩佩所以自己去找她，两人不幸遇上绑匪。在逃离绑匪时，诺诺突然昏倒。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112190000 +0800" stop="20260112200000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 珍国下定决心，向珍熙告白，两人终于开始第一天的恋情。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112200000 +0800" stop="20260112210000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 善熙终于知道智恩真正说不出真相的原因。智恩坚持不说出真相，善熙夹在自己女儿和自己姐姐中间，心力交瘁。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112210000 +0800" stop="20260112213000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112213000 +0800" stop="20260112220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">爆食姐妹 S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">“爆食姐妹”的两位年轻主持将带你走进台湾每一个角落，例如新竹，基隆，桃园，寻找当地美食。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112220000 +0800" stop="20260112230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">金秘书为何那样</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 成寅祝福英俊，还为他出主意怎么求婚，不要学别人那么铺张, 只要选择微笑喜欢的就好。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112230000 +0800" stop="20260112234500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112234500 +0800" stop="20260112234500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112234500 +0800" stop="20260113001000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113001000 +0800" stop="20260113003500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">爆食姐妹 S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">“爆食姐妹”的两位年轻主持将带你走进台湾每一个角落，例如新竹，基隆，桃园，寻找当地美食。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113003500 +0800" stop="20260113013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 珍国下定决心，向珍熙告白，两人终于开始第一天的恋情。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112000000 +0800" stop="20260112090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112090000 +0800" stop="20260112093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Arc</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story is about Arc protecting the future of the Earth and mankind from looming threats. Yuma transforms into Ultraman Arc by inserting the Arc Cube, which contains the power of the being of light, into the mystic Arc Ariser and unleashing his power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112093000 +0800" stop="20260112100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">SQFT</title>
    <desc lang="en">An informative and entertaining program that aims to show the uniqueness of the versatile small house and the minimalist life. This unique tv program also shares creativity with the use of small and limited space is unlimited. Viewers will also be taken to a new Tiny house construction project from start to finish over the course of 13 episodes in SQFT's Buiuld Info segment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112100000 +0800" stop="20260112110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Azam &amp; Johan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Azam &amp; Johan aspire to be professional footballers. An accident renders Azam paralyzed, dashing his football dream. Their mother blames Johan for the accident. Azam feels his world has ended. Wrecked with guilt, Johan wants to give up football but his father stops him. Will the family be torn apart forever by the tragedy or overcome to find happiness again?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112110000 +0800" stop="20260112120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kerasnya Takdir</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jiha rushes to the hospital upon learning that Saleha has been admitted. Aminah demands that Jiha leave Munir and Saleha.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112120000 +0800" stop="20260112130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">S.P.Y. S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The group of vandals come to a head when they were almost caught by the S.P.Y team. Alyssa catches Maria in a lie as she starts to tail her. With 2 of the vandals caught, Alyssa follows the lead on a new suspect much to Yusuf's chagrin. Although initially hesitant, Azrul finally agrees to let Ben help him with his case as Alyssa confronts Maria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112130000 +0800" stop="20260112140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aku Seorang Perempuan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adriana continues her mission to ruin lives by driving a wedge between Tasya and Hakim, insinuating that there was something going on between Hakim and Siti Noraisya. Meanwhile, Siti Noraisya was having complications with her pregnancy and had to be sent to the hospital, but Fareez was prevented from getting the news by Adriana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112140000 +0800" stop="20260112150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sayap Cinta Terindah</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dhani takes on the responsibility of caring for his younger siblings - Ariel, David and Isyana - navigating the challlenges of their intertwined lives. As their journey unfolds, each sibling harbors hidden secrets waiting to be uncovered. Will Dhani uncover the truths they're keeping from him?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112150000 +0800" stop="20260112160100 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sepahtu Reunion Live S8 ( 2023 )</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jep, Rahim, Pak Ya and Ebby Yus are back to entertain you in the latest season featuring special celebrity guests and unexpected cameos every week. Guest Artist - Atikah Suhaime Cameo Appearance - Syamsul Debat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112160100 +0800" stop="20260112170000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Once Upon Our Love</title>
    <desc lang="en">Haris and Ikhwan's friendship is tested when Ikhwan confesses his feelings to Akira. Meanwhile, Fatiha starts her own business but faces her abusive ex-husband again, prompting Akira to pause her relationship with Haris to focus on her studies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112170000 +0800" stop="20260112180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cinta Tiada Ganti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Khairil confronts Ara as she continuously gets flashbacks of her time with Riz when on vacation. Khairil interviews Riz for a marketing manager position under his company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112180000 +0800" stop="20260112183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Arc</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story is about Arc protecting the future of the Earth and mankind from looming threats. Yuma transforms into Ultraman Arc by inserting the Arc Cube, which contains the power of the being of light, into the mystic Arc Ariser and unleashing his power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112183000 +0800" stop="20260112190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Janji Sedap</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join our chef as he takes you to a culinary journey and learn how to whip up vibrant and flavoursome cuisine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112190000 +0800" stop="20260112200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Bukan Sekadar Lafaz 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hud decides to marry Aira as his second wife as a knee jerk reaction to Syikin's constant accusations of him having an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112200000 +0800" stop="20260112203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112203000 +0800" stop="20260112213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">TBC</title>
    <desc lang="en">TBC.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112213000 +0800" stop="20260112223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Dedaun Hijau Di Angin Lalu</title>
    <desc lang="en">Assad grows uneasy seeing his son Ismadi grow close to Intan, who spends much time caring for the boy. When Ismadi is injured at the playground, he unfairly blames Intan for the accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112223000 +0800" stop="20260112233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Andai Tiada Dia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suri plans a birthday surprise for Haikal, unaware that Haikal and Intan are on a getaway together during his business trip. Haikal lashes out at Suri when she turns up without warning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112233000 +0800" stop="20260112233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260111220000 +0800" stop="20260112010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">The GOAT: The Greatest of All Time</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of successful operations, an elite agent suddenly retires, choosing a quiet, ordinary life. However, when a past mission comes back to haunt him, he reunites with his team to prevent a catastrophic disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112010000 +0800" stop="20260112013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112013000 +0800" stop="20260112090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112090000 +0800" stop="20260112093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Oor Kuruvi</title>
    <desc lang="en">The show format would be that of a Info-ed, hosted by a single compere who would be well versed in Tamil and information savy with great conversation skills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112093000 +0800" stop="20260112100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Siri…Siri Siri Siri S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Compilation of comedy clips to tickle your laughing bone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112100000 +0800" stop="20260112103100 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Indian Beat S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">A bilingual magazine show that serves as a platform by featuring activities and events organized by the various Tamil and Indian ethnic organizations around Singapore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112103100 +0800" stop="20260112110000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112110000 +0800" stop="20260112120000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Kadalora Payanam</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chasing deep sea flavours across the Bay of Bengal and the Arabian sea while encapsulating the everyday lives of fishermen who live around the coasts and uncover the great Ocean tales as we savour the sea flavours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112120000 +0800" stop="20260112150000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Panchavarna Kili</title>
    <desc lang="en">Muthuraman and Jaishankar are sons of Sundarajan. Jaishankar is in the army. He marries without the knowledge of his family and has a kid. Balu (Jaishankar, in dual role) K.R.Vijaya's customary boy forces her to marry him. Sekar dies in the warfront and his wife dies in the shock. K.R.Vijaya escorts Sekar's child. The rest of the narration has more thrilling twists to the story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112150000 +0800" stop="20260112160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Uncle Taxi S5: Australian Adventure</title>
    <desc lang="en">Uncle Taxi Season 5 - An Australian Outback Adventure, is the 5th instalment of the iconic Uncle Taxi franchise. This remarkable travalogue series which started in Singapore went on to Malaysia, Thailand &amp; Indonesia now travels to Australia. This 1st of its kind Outback Adventure series will discover &amp; reveal the unknow of the massive Australian Outback in the Uncle Taxi style!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112160000 +0800" stop="20260112190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Keladi Kanmani (1990)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A single father hesitates to remarry due to his love for his daughter, but her tragic illness forces him to reconsider for her sake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112190000 +0800" stop="20260112193000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rasikka Rusikka Reloaded</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rasikka Rusikka is back with another exciting Season. Join Bala as he uncovers Malaysia's hidden culinary treasures, indulging in everything from delightful desserts to irresistible appetizers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112193000 +0800" stop="20260112200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rasikka Rusikka Reloaded</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rasikka Rusikka is back with another exciting Season. Join Bala as he uncovers Malaysia's hidden culinary treasures, indulging in everything from delightful desserts to irresistible appetizers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112200000 +0800" stop="20260112203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Abhiyum Naanum</title>
    <desc lang="en">"Abiyum Naanum" is a heartwarming family drama that follows 12-year-old Abimanyu, a boy genius on the autism spectrum, as he navigates the challenges of adolescence, school, and family life with a perspective that transforms the mundane into the magical.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112203000 +0800" stop="20260112210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112210000 +0800" stop="20260112213000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Aaha Kalyanam (The Con of Matrimony)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A charismatic but unconventional marriage broker who “fixes” flawed bachelors into dream grooms finds his quirky empire spiraling into chaos when a groom is found dead, a bride goes missing, and he's thrust into a twisted mystery that threatens to unravel every carefully curated lie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112213000 +0800" stop="20260112220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Koranjeh Velai Niranjeh Ooru S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">A television program where the host, Rabbit Mac takes viewers around Malaysia on a shoestring budget.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112220000 +0800" stop="20260112223000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Achamillai Manamae S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following a brazen escape from the world's most notorious prison a decade ago, a former MMA champion finds herself in the midst of turmoil again when a man rising to power seeks to destroy countless lives because of a prized dagger she swore to protect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112223000 +0800" stop="20260112230000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Yaar 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">They say all is fair in love and war, but what happens when war drowns out the love? As their lives come to a shocking standstill, the truth prevails.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112230000 +0800" stop="20260112233000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112233000 +0800" stop="20260112233000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112000000 +0800" stop="20260112000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112000300 +0800" stop="20260112010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">China's Night Boom</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Chengdu, youth fight burnout with "night schools" and forest blind walks, then escape into the Metaverse and luxury esports hotels. This is the future of leisure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112010000 +0800" stop="20260112020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112020000 +0800" stop="20260112023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112023000 +0800" stop="20260112030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112030000 +0800" stop="20260112033000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112033000 +0800" stop="20260112040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">Actress Hong Ling lost her mother just months ago — along with the unique Thai Laksa her mum used to make. Can chef Jonathan recreate a dish made only from memory? And will it taste like home again?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112040000 +0800" stop="20260112043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112043000 +0800" stop="20260112050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hobsessions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two men preserve history their way —one through a home museum of military memorabilia in Singapore, the other by restoring vintage books through antiquarian bookbinding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112050000 +0800" stop="20260112060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Elon Musk's Twitter Takeover</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elon Musk's long and often troubled relationship with Twitter. FRONTLINE traces Musk's journey from one of the platform's most provocative users to its sole proprietor, exploring the acquisition, free speech issues and the company's uncertain future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112060000 +0800" stop="20260112063000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112063000 +0800" stop="20260112070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112070000 +0800" stop="20260112100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia First</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Top stories, business news and market updates from across the region as Asia gears up for the day ahead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112100000 +0800" stop="20260112110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Wombless</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Maharashtra's Beed region, female cane cutters sacrifice their wombs to keep earning for their families. But these women are now fighting for a different future, determined to break the cycle and give their daughters a life beyond the sugarcane fields.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112110000 +0800" stop="20260112130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112130000 +0800" stop="20260112140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Legend In A Day</title>
    <desc lang="en">A documentary chronicling Singapore's early sporting history through the little-known life and career of Lim Bong Soon, a sportsman whose achievements transcended tennis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112140000 +0800" stop="20260112160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112160000 +0800" stop="20260112170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Limitless S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Limitless 2 follows five youth from Singapore, Vietnam, the Philippines, India and Cambodia whose poignant stories reveal how they push through challenges with remarkable resilience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112170000 +0800" stop="20260112170200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112170200 +0800" stop="20260112180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112180000 +0800" stop="20260112190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112190000 +0800" stop="20260112193000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112193000 +0800" stop="20260112200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">Actress Hong Ling lost her mother just months ago — along with the unique Thai Laksa her mum used to make. Can chef Jonathan recreate a dish made only from memory? And will it taste like home again?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112200000 +0800" stop="20260112210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112210000 +0800" stop="20260112220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Elon Musk's Twitter Takeover</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elon Musk's long and often troubled relationship with Twitter. FRONTLINE traces Musk's journey from one of the platform's most provocative users to its sole proprietor, exploring the acquisition, free speech issues and the company's uncertain future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112220000 +0800" stop="20260112230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260112230000 +0800" stop="20260113000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Wombless</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Maharashtra's Beed region, female cane cutters sacrifice their wombs to keep earning for their families. But these women are now fighting for a different future, determined to break the cycle and give their daughters a life beyond the sugarcane fields.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113000000 +0800" stop="20260113000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113000300 +0800" stop="20260113010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113010000 +0800" stop="20260113013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">Actress Hong Ling lost her mother just months ago — along with the unique Thai Laksa her mum used to make. Can chef Jonathan recreate a dish made only from memory? And will it taste like home again?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113013000 +0800" stop="20260113020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113020000 +0800" stop="20260113030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113030000 +0800" stop="20260113040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260113040000 +0800" stop="20260113050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>