<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.5.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260106000000 +0800" stop="20260106003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Streets, Hong Kong</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over this eight-part series, renowned chef, Dan Hong will explore every corner of Hong Kong, learning about its history and culture and how this has shaped the local food scene. Determined to hunt down the most authentic fare, Dan will scour the streets, markets and hawker halls to meet the vendors and find out how these traditional dishes are made and served to hordes of hungry customers every day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106003000 +0800" stop="20260106013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cobra: Rebellion S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The government face scrutiny for legislating an aggressive anti-protest bill, leading to police forces going on an unofficial strike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106013000 +0800" stop="20260106020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106020000 +0800" stop="20260106030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo USA S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this game show, hosted by the iconic RuPaul, the simplest of words could be worth thousands of dollars. Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106030000 +0800" stop="20260106040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 03</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106040000 +0800" stop="20260106043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106043000 +0800" stop="20260106050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Donal Skehan: Home Cook</title>
    <desc lang="en">Master builder and household favourite Tommy Walsh, expert pro cleaner Maxine nspired by his sunny days living in Los Angeles, treasured family memories, and his love of good food, Donal brings a collection of his favourite fondest recipes, adapted using no-fuss techniques, designed with the home cook in mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106000000 +0800" stop="20260106010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">斗罗大陆之燃魂战</title>
    <desc lang="en">全大陆高级魂师学院精英赛决赛结束，唐三跟小伙伴们恋恋不舍地分别，约定五年后重逢，便各自奔赴前程。而后，唐三随父亲唐昊去往隐秘山谷特训，提升自身能力。得益于唐昊的协助，唐三在积累经验的过程中变得更加沉稳，能从容应对更多挑战。戴沐白和朱竹清获得家族的肯定，分别成为星罗太子和准太子妃。奥斯卡和宁荣荣为提升实力开启艰苦训练，马红俊也外出游历以增长见识。就在此时，武魂殿的比比东暗中筹谋，横扫多个宗门，企图称霸斗罗大陆。于是，唐三召集伙伴创立唐门，坚守正义，勇挑重担。他们合力勇闯海神岛，与武魂殿对抗，不惧黑暗与强权，共同守护大陆和平，成长为坚毅的战士。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106010000 +0800" stop="20260106020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">食尚玩家 S13</title>
    <desc lang="en">在新一辑的“食尚玩家 - 2 天1夜GO"里，主持人纳豆，六月，曾子余等会带领观众周游许多耳目一新的地方，国家包括韩国，日本（长崎，福冈），越南等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106020000 +0800" stop="20260106030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106030000 +0800" stop="20260106040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">浓浓咖啡乌.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106040000 +0800" stop="20260106050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106003000 +0800" stop="20260106013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 汉杰看到荷妮受伤情绪激动，智恩全看在眼里，很不是滋味。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106000000 +0800" stop="20260106000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106000300 +0800" stop="20260106010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106010000 +0800" stop="20260106013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">After missionary Joseph Chean's death, his wife Kim enlists Jon's help to recreate his special Hakka Yong Tau Foo. But can anyone truly capture the soul of a dish only he ever knew how to make?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106013000 +0800" stop="20260106020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">Talking Point investigates another burning question from a viewer. Just how dirty are our kitchen sponges? Diana Ser takes viewers' sponges to a lab for a test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106020000 +0800" stop="20260106030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106030000 +0800" stop="20260106040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three years ago, Sri Lanka teetered on the edge of economic collapse. Now, it is one the road to recovery. Is tourism a sustainable pathway out of its economic doldrums?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260106040000 +0800" stop="20260106050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>