<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.2.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260215001000 +0800" stop="20260215004000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Incredible Tales S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cars play a crucial role in our lives today. Some prefer a secondhand car, instead of buying a brand new car. However, you must be careful when buying a car from a dealer because you never know when you're going to get more than what you paid for!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215004000 +0800" stop="20260215013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Ark S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follows the remaining crew of a spacecraft known as Ark One, who must become the best versions of themselves to stay on course and survive after experiencing a catastrophic event that caused massive destruction and loss of life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215013000 +0800" stop="20260215022000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo UK S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215022000 +0800" stop="20260215025000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215025000 +0800" stop="20260215032000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Monster Jam S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Returning season. Professional monster truck drivers compete against each other in races and freestyle competitions around the world to win the top prize.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215032000 +0800" stop="20260215034500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215034500 +0800" stop="20260215041000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215041000 +0800" stop="20260215044000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Famous Foodies S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Famous Foodies tells you about what &amp; where the celebrities eat, from healthy lifestyles to haute cuisine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215044000 +0800" stop="20260215053000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Beat the Chasers S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could you beat the greatest quiz team ever assembled? Bringing together all five of our favourite quiz geniuses, Beat the Chasers, hosted by Bradley Walsh, expands the award-winning The Chase brand for a primetime audience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215053000 +0800" stop="20260215060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Spirit of Sport S11</title>
    <desc lang="en">Monthly sports television magazine show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215060000 +0800" stop="20260215063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Mat Yoyo: The New Generation</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kim sets a few puzzles for Yoyo, Yaya and the audience to solve. The answers are all about shapes. Then they become shape detectives and attempt to spot the hidden shapes in the pictures that Kim shows them. Why segment - Why are wheels round? Yoyo and Yaya wonder why wheels have to be round and not some other shape. Kim conducts and experiment to show them why wheels that are round are the most efficient and effective. ..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215063000 +0800" stop="20260215070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Club M.A.G.I.C S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's time for some fun with toys! Sham, Ling and Didi can't wait to show Miss P their favourite toys. Sham has a toy robot, Ling a remote controlled car and Didi a music box with a ballerina inside. Didi comments that she would like to be a toy herself! Miss P, the Mistress Toymaker of Toyland fulfils their wishes and everyone ' turns' into a toy! Everybody agrees that toys make everyone happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215070000 +0800" stop="20260215073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Big Q S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Big Q S1.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215073000 +0800" stop="20260215080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cows &amp; Crayons S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Each week from his cow stomach studio and with the help of a Singaporean child Einstein explores art and imagination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215080000 +0800" stop="20260215081500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Tayo the Little Bus 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of Tayo, a blue bus with the number 120. He is very playful and mischievous with his passengers and his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215081500 +0800" stop="20260215083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Tayo the Little Bus 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of Tayo, a blue bus with the number 120. He is very playful and mischievous with his passengers and his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215083000 +0800" stop="20260215090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Songs &amp; Stories</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Pinkfong and friends for more fun and adventure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215090000 +0800" stop="20260215091000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">iYO</title>
    <desc lang="en">iYO, Tom and Mei pretend to board a plane to Japan with their new friend, Miyuki - all in the comfort of their home!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215091000 +0800" stop="20260215092000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">iYO</title>
    <desc lang="en">A house spider causes Tom and iYO to go into a fear frenzy but they soon discover there's nothing to be scared of and in fact, spiders are super cool!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215092000 +0800" stop="20260215093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">iYO</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tom and Mei are completely in love with a storybook but are sad because it has to be returned to the library soon. iYO comes up with a plan to keep the book so they can read it forever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215093000 +0800" stop="20260215100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wild Kratts S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">In each episode, Chris and Martin Kratt travel to a different corner of the world to meet amazing new animals. Join the Wild Kratts for a laugh-out-loud comedy adventure, as Martin and Chris activate their Creature Power Suits to rescue their animal friends!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100000 +0800" stop="20260215103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">SpongeBob SquarePants S13</title>
    <desc lang="en">A yellow sea sponge named SpongeBob SquarePants, who enjoys being a cook at Krusty Krab, lives in the Pacific Ocean. He embarks on various adventures with his friends at Bikini Bottom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215103000 +0800" stop="20260215110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Eco Rangers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mr Big Bucks' mega factory has been using up the water resources in a rural town and the waste that his factory puts out has also been polluting the groundwater! The Scholar assembles the Eco Rangers to the rescue! But can they make Mr Big Bucks fix the mess he's started?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215110000 +0800" stop="20260215113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Jade Armor S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Lan Jun, the unlikely Chinese teen hero who inherits a magical suit of armor, and her Beasticon talking animal friends, as they continue to defend their city of Ban Tang, against the Crimson Lord and Black Tiger!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215113000 +0800" stop="20260215120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Miraculous: Tales Of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">The continuing adventures of Marinette and Adrien, two normal teens, transform into superheroes Ladybug and Cat Noir when evil threatens their city!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215120000 +0800" stop="20260215123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Omega</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual Language English and Malay) There are many universes, they may be similar, but they have their own characteristics, as in the case of Omegaverse. A universe that's similar to the original Ultra universe, but has its own ultras. Omega is a Space Garrison rookie who was sent to Earth on a mission to protect it from monsters that appear mysteriously.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215123000 +0800" stop="20260215124500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">P. King Duckling</title>
    <desc lang="en">P. King Duckling is an animated comedy series that follows the adventures of a friendly but slightly hapless duck P. King and his two best friends, Wombat and Chumpkins, as they find hilarious and creative ways to overcome challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215124500 +0800" stop="20260215130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">P. King Duckling</title>
    <desc lang="en">P. King Duckling is an animated comedy series that follows the adventures of a friendly but slightly hapless duck P. King and his two best friends, Wombat and Chumpkins, as they find hilarious and creative ways to overcome challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130000 +0800" stop="20260215133000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Johnny Test S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of average suburban boy Johnny Test, who wittingly plays test subject for his genius twin sisters' various experiments, reluctantly fighting evil villains in the process.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215133000 +0800" stop="20260215140000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Space Nova S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Space Nova is an exciting and captivating space adventure which follows the Nova family's search for alien life throughout the universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215140000 +0800" stop="20260215141500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Jungle Bunch S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Jungle Bunch tells the story of a group of loopy animals fighting injustice in the heart of the jungle, where every being who faces a problem knows who to call...."The Jungle Bunch: to the Rescue!".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215141500 +0800" stop="20260215143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Jungle Bunch S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Jungle Bunch tells the story of a group of loopy animals fighting injustice in the heart of the jungle, where every being who faces a problem knows who to call...."The Jungle Bunch: to the Rescue!".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215143000 +0800" stop="20260215150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wild Wild Wow S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to find out why these animals are the cutest of them all! Join Allie and Alfie as they wrap a wooly alpaca and construct a strong house for some cute little piggies. They go to River Wonders to meet a real life Red Panda.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215150000 +0800" stop="20260215153000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215153000 +0800" stop="20260215163000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Bake Off: The Professionals S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Twelve teams from top hotels, restaurants and small businesses compete to be crowned best patisserie team in Britain. Once again, judges Cherish Finden and Benoit Blin set exceedingly tricky challenges, to test the teams' creativity and precision. From towering, skyline-inspired chocolate constructions, to geometric tarts with moving parts, these incredible creations showcase bakers at the peak of their profession.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215163000 +0800" stop="20260215173000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Nomad with Carlton McCoy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over a glorious summer of hard work and fantastic food, the series presents a sun-soaked escape to the country along with delicious, inspiring recipes you can try in From the towns of the Mississippi Delta to the bustling alleys of South Korea via diaspora communities, flourishing African townships and volcanic islands, world-class chef, master sommelier and arbiter of cool Carlton McCoy presents a new six-part series exploring the world like never before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215173000 +0800" stop="20260215183000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Cube USA S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dwyane Wade introduces The Cube, 15 square feet of steel-edged plexiglass where simple tasks become challenges teams have nine lives to win seven games to beat The Cube for a chance to walk away with 250,000.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215183000 +0800" stop="20260215210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Transformers: Rise of the Beasts</title>
    <desc lang="en">During the '90s, a new faction of Transformers - the Maximals - join the Autobots as allies in the battle for Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215210000 +0800" stop="20260215213000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215213000 +0800" stop="20260215223000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Gladiators</title>
    <desc lang="en">GLADIATORS is set in iconic and diverse battlefields: the wide open Outback, the vast plains of the Serengeti, the rugged heights of the Rockies and the life-rich Rainforest. Across the planet, there are animals born to fight and destined to face their foe. Some are fighting for territory, others for access to food or a mate but ALL are fighting for the same ultimate prize - survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215223000 +0800" stop="20260215223000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Upgraded</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upgraded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215223000 +0800" stop="20260216004000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Upgraded</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upgraded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216004000 +0800" stop="20260216013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dirty Home Rescue</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cleaning expert Hayley Leitch and her team of professional cleaners answer SOS calls from Britain's filthiest houses while identifying unhealthy habits which cause mess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216013000 +0800" stop="20260216020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216020000 +0800" stop="20260216024500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Cube USA S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dwyane Wade introduces The Cube, 15 square feet of steel-edged plexiglass where simple tasks become challenges teams have nine lives to win seven games to beat The Cube for a chance to walk away with 250,000.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216024500 +0800" stop="20260216034500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Bake Off: The Professionals S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Twelve teams from top hotels, restaurants and small businesses compete to be crowned best patisserie team in Britain. Once again, judges Cherish Finden and Benoit Blin set exceedingly tricky challenges, to test the teams' creativity and precision. From towering, skyline-inspired chocolate constructions, to geometric tarts with moving parts, these incredible creations showcase bakers at the peak of their profession.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216034500 +0800" stop="20260216044500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Nomad with Carlton McCoy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over a glorious summer of hard work and fantastic food, the series presents a sun-soaked escape to the country along with delicious, inspiring recipes you can try in From the towns of the Mississippi Delta to the bustling alleys of South Korea via diaspora communities, flourishing African townships and volcanic islands, world-class chef, master sommelier and arbiter of cool Carlton McCoy presents a new six-part series exploring the world like never before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216044500 +0800" stop="20260216060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Survivor 47</title>
    <desc lang="en">18 new castaways battle it out on the islands of Fiji for a million dollars and the title of Sole Survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216060000 +0800" stop="20260216063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supa Strikas S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow Shakes, Rasta and the rest of the Supa Strikas on their quest to become the world's greatest football team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216063000 +0800" stop="20260216070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216070000 +0800" stop="20260216071500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Thomas &amp; Friends S27</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas the Number One Engine and his loc-amigos are ready for more Sodor surprises! The engines are celebrating the grand opening of a new bakery-caf connecting farm-to-table routes and keeping busy bringing ingredients and sweet-smelling, flatcar-filling treats to festive tables. Thomas, Percy, Kana, Nia, Bruno and Diesel take on every challenge coupling with new and returning friends to get each job done.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216071500 +0800" stop="20260216073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Thomas &amp; Friends S27</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas the Number One Engine and his loc-amigos are ready for more Sodor surprises! The engines are celebrating the grand opening of a new bakery-caf connecting farm-to-table routes and keeping busy bringing ingredients and sweet-smelling, flatcar-filling treats to festive tables. Thomas, Percy, Kana, Nia, Bruno and Diesel take on every challenge coupling with new and returning friends to get each job done.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216073000 +0800" stop="20260216074500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Meekah Visits</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meekah exercises her body and mind at Munchkin's Indoor Playground! She plays a fun Matching Game that leads her to all sorts of play areas like a Doctor's Office, a Fire Station, and even a huge ball pit!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216074500 +0800" stop="20260216080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Meekah Visits</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meekah exercises her body and mind at Munchkin's Indoor Playground! She plays a fun Matching Game that leads her to all sorts of play areas like a Doctor's Office, a Fire Station, and even a huge ball pit!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216080000 +0800" stop="20260216093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Sing-Along Movie 3: Catch the Gingerbread Man</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Baby Shark, Pinkfong, and Hogi in their exciting new adventure as they set out to create the most delicious ice cream in the world! Just before the final touch, the perfect topping, Gingerbread Man dashes away. Will they be able to catch him and complete their ice cream masterpiece? Get ready for an exciting musical adventure and sing and dance to Pinkfong's most-beloved songs!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216093000 +0800" stop="20260216094500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Andy's Global Adventures</title>
    <desc lang="en">In his latest set of adventures, Andy travels to all corners of the globe, meeting an amazing new cast of animals - from chameleons in Sri Lanka to emperor penguins in Antarctica. Accompanied by tech wizard Jen and new information-seeking AI Scout, Andy travels the globe in a hi-tech expedition truck, a scientific research station that houses Jen's database of incredible facts about fauna and flora that inhabit our planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216094500 +0800" stop="20260216100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Andy's Global Adventures</title>
    <desc lang="en">In his latest set of adventures, Andy travels to all corners of the globe, meeting an amazing new cast of animals - from chameleons in Sri Lanka to emperor penguins in Antarctica. Accompanied by tech wizard Jen and new information-seeking AI Scout, Andy travels the globe in a hi-tech expedition truck, a scientific research station that houses Jen's database of incredible facts about fauna and flora that inhabit our planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216100000 +0800" stop="20260216110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Blippi Delivers The Mail</title>
    <desc lang="en">Blippi goes on a mail delivery adventure! He receives some envelopes that need to be delivered right away and journeys through the museum to find their drop-off spots! Blippi learns all about what it's like to be a postal worker as he plays interactive games along his mail route!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216110000 +0800" stop="20260216111500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Thomas &amp; Friends S27</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas the Number One Engine and his loc-amigos are ready for more Sodor surprises! The engines are celebrating the grand opening of a new bakery-caf connecting farm-to-table routes and keeping busy bringing ingredients and sweet-smelling, flatcar-filling treats to festive tables. Thomas, Percy, Kana, Nia, Bruno and Diesel take on every challenge coupling with new and returning friends to get each job done.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216111500 +0800" stop="20260216113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Thomas &amp; Friends S27</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas the Number One Engine and his loc-amigos are ready for more Sodor surprises! The engines are celebrating the grand opening of a new bakery-caf connecting farm-to-table routes and keeping busy bringing ingredients and sweet-smelling, flatcar-filling treats to festive tables. Thomas, Percy, Kana, Nia, Bruno and Diesel take on every challenge coupling with new and returning friends to get each job done.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216113000 +0800" stop="20260216114500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Zoonicorn S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Zooniverse is the magical dreamland where four enchanting Zoonicorns join their friends for a whirlwind of exciting dream adventures and show them how to solve real-life problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216114500 +0800" stop="20260216120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Zoonicorn S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Zooniverse is the magical dreamland where four enchanting Zoonicorns join their friends for a whirlwind of exciting dream adventures and show them how to solve real-life problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216120000 +0800" stop="20260216130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">LEGO Monkie Kid: A Hero Is Born</title>
    <desc lang="en">Monkey King comes to life as a young boy named MK obsessed with the legends of old, who discovers Monkey King's magical staff. After the Demon Bull King is released, our hero must go on a journey of self-discovery in order to become the hero this generation needs!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216130000 +0800" stop="20260216143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Out of the Nest</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow the story of Arthur, a young, ambitious goat who teams up with seven chicks to embark on a grand mission to defeat the dark power of an evil wizard and restore the kingdom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216143000 +0800" stop="20260216150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pokemon Ultimate Journeys: The Series</title>
    <desc lang="en">The stakes are higher than ever for Ash, Goh, and Chloe as they advance toward their goals! As the Pokmon World Coronation Series tournament heats up, intensive training is in store for Ash, Pikachu, and their Pokmon friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216150000 +0800" stop="20260216160000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216160000 +0800" stop="20260216163000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">Singapore saw a 27 increase in traffic accidents in recent years. We investigate if such accidents are caused by a lack of driving skills or bad attitudes on our roads.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216163000 +0800" stop="20260216173000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lion Mums S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chae Lian's exhaustion reaches tipping point, and her three children must band together to support her. Will the misunderstanding between mother and son be finally dissolved? Marcus attempts to right the wrongs of his company, going against his business partners to ensure justice. Marcus' decision to right the wrongs and fight for justice leaves him with a lot to lose, but will he hold on to the virtue of having done the right thing?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216173000 +0800" stop="20260216175000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Just For Laughs Gags S24</title>
    <desc lang="en">Just For Laughs will tickle everyone's funny bone with its hilarious practical jokes, hidden camera pranks, and other creative hijinks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216175000 +0800" stop="20260216185000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Chase S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bradley Walsh and his criminally clever Chaser are back for yet another battle of the brains - can our contestants beat the Chaser, or will it be just another day at the office?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216185000 +0800" stop="20260216203000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Tiger's Apprentice</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tom Lee, a Chinese-American boy, after the death of his grandmother, has to be apprenticed to the talking tiger Mr. Hu and learn ancient magic to become the new guardian of an ancient phoenix.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216203000 +0800" stop="20260216210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Aunty Lee's Deadly Delights</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yanna becomes the target of a stalker who is determined to become part of her life ... and remove Yanna's roommate and best friend Gabby in the process.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216210000 +0800" stop="20260216213000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216213000 +0800" stop="20260216220000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Double Yummy</title>
    <desc lang="en">CHICKEN CLASH: Ayam Penyet vs Salted Crispy Chicken! Andrew Chau and Yasminne Cheng kick off with a crowd favouritechicken! In Singapore, they sink their teeth into hawker stall La Porpo's smashing Ayam Penyet.. Then in Taiwan, it's straight into the island's essential street snack: Salted Crispy Chicken. Two styles, two cravingsone delicious showdown!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216220000 +0800" stop="20260217000000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Assassin Club</title>
    <desc lang="en">An assassin is given a contract to kill seven people around the world only to discover the targets are also assassins who have been hired to kill him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217000000 +0800" stop="20260217003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Aunty Lee's Deadly Delights</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yanna becomes the target of a stalker who is determined to become part of her life ... and remove Yanna's roommate and best friend Gabby in the process.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217003000 +0800" stop="20260217023000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Monster-in-Law</title>
    <desc lang="en">The love life of Charlotte is reduced to an endless string of disastrous blind dates, until she meets the perfect man, Kevin. Unfortunately, his merciless mother will do anything to destroy their relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217023000 +0800" stop="20260217030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217030000 +0800" stop="20260217040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Chase S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bradley Walsh and his criminally clever Chaser are back for yet another battle of the brains - can our contestants beat the Chaser, or will it be just another day at the office?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217040000 +0800" stop="20260217043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Famous Foodies S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Famous Foodies tells you about what &amp; where the celebrities eat, from healthy lifestyles to haute cuisine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217043000 +0800" stop="20260217050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215004500 +0800" stop="20260215014500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">灵探</title>
    <desc lang="en">警方从Lynn的同乡Zaw口中证实Lynn是被人杀死的Zaw还拍到凶手的模糊照片对方手上有一条疤痕婕珊偶遇家纯和司机兼保镖Kyla发现Kyla手臂上有类似凶手的疤痕请她到警局协助调查Kyla否认杀人但最后警方掌握了关键证据在Kyla准备逃离时将她逮捕.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215014500 +0800" stop="20260215024500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">灵探</title>
    <desc lang="en">真父怕鬼晚上不敢睡觉在空中撒红花柚叶水驱鬼另一边4977想带走志玲却不忍下手他突然见到看护Ray鬼鬼祟祟要帮志玲打针志玲惊醒反抗4977焦急不已幸好真父出现Ray找借口离去Ray告诉院长天诚和主治医生柯捷锐自己不想再害人.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215024500 +0800" stop="20260215034500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">食在好源头</title>
    <desc lang="en">食在好源头.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215034500 +0800" stop="20260215041000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">小屋大作</title>
    <desc lang="en">不同年纪的女人对于房屋需求也有所不同本周将迎来由黄嫊方饰演的贵妇姐姐和萧歆霓饰演的年轻妹妹一起来看公寓妹妹单纯活泼热爱新事物姐姐要求多又爱奢华陈汉玮饰演的房屋经纪 Barry Koo 将介绍两间风格大不同的两房式公寓看看是否能成功说服两姐妹顺利成交.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215041000 +0800" stop="20260215050500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">喜事年年</title>
    <desc lang="en">喜事年年.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215050500 +0800" stop="20260215060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">喜事年年</title>
    <desc lang="en">喜事年年.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215060000 +0800" stop="20260215065000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">阿嬷来做饭</title>
    <desc lang="en">阿嬷来做饭是全新实况趣味的烹饪节目每集节目将邀请一位阿嬷来做菜示范拿手料理并传承她的好厨艺由主持人钟琴搭配不同的男嘉宾主持人同步跟着阿嬷一起做菜过程中观察阿嬷烹调的独特方式与习惯领受她无价的真传将阿嬷的家传菜肴发扬光大.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215065000 +0800" stop="20260215072000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">晚间新闻每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215072000 +0800" stop="20260215081000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">钱来运转</title>
    <desc lang="en">此剧讲述独居老人钱老实朱厚任饰拥有百万洋房原本宁静的生活却被侄子钱仁杰王沺裁饰和侄女钱美玲钟琴饰扰乱大哥钱仁杰和妻子罗舒萍童冰玉饰面临财务困难走投无路下带着女儿钱宁宁罗美仪饰住进大伯的洋房不料妹妹钱美玲因老公吴国伦姚玟隆饰理财不慎无家可归的他们也带了女儿吴希希雅慧饰和儿子吴佳明陈昱志饰搬入大伯家.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215081000 +0800" stop="20260215090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">钱来运转</title>
    <desc lang="en">此剧讲述独居老人钱老实朱厚任饰拥有百万洋房原本宁静的生活却被侄子钱仁杰王沺裁饰和侄女钱美玲钟琴饰扰乱大哥钱仁杰和妻子罗舒萍童冰玉饰面临财务困难走投无路下带着女儿钱宁宁罗美仪饰住进大伯的洋房不料妹妹钱美玲因老公吴国伦姚玟隆饰理财不慎无家可归的他们也带了女儿吴希希雅慧饰和儿子吴佳明陈昱志饰搬入大伯家.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215090000 +0800" stop="20260215091500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">Super BOOMi S8.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215091500 +0800" stop="20260215093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">Super BOOMi S8.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215093000 +0800" stop="20260215100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">哆啦A梦</title>
    <desc lang="en">在这系列卡通动画里小朋友们将看到哆啦A梦 - 这只来自未来世界的机器猫如何应用它的法宝协助其主人大雄解决生活上的各种难题.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100000 +0800" stop="20260215103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">华文"浆"好玩</title>
    <desc lang="en">第五系列的 华文浆好玩 回来了兴致勃勃的小朋友勇闯蒋依讲博士的黏浆实验室为的就是挑战自己华文实力一旦失败就将成为蒋依讲博士的小跟班想要逃出实验室他们必须在五个回合解开所有的华文谜题他们能否成功逃脱还是得乖乖地接受黏浆浴的洗礼呢.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215103000 +0800" stop="20260215110000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">奇趣特工队 S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">凯奇是一个充满好奇心和正义感的男孩他还有一个神秘的身份奇趣特工队队长他和他的伙伴们调皮骄傲又听得懂外星语的宠物 "闪电猫" 彬彬有礼温和待人的管家 "艾尔" 以及意外流落地球的外星访客 "嘟嘟公主"组成了守护小镇的奇趣特工队.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215110000 +0800" stop="20260215120000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">星期二特写少年Z的烦恼</title>
    <desc lang="en">陪家人享用美味晚餐饭后帮弟弟写电邮看似行径正常的23岁青年高小虎却在隔天清晨轻生凌晨一点到四点是青少年自杀高危时段临床心理学家呼吁有自杀念头的青年要及时把念头斩断18岁的Art试图寻短那次脑里充斥活着没有价值的尖叫青少年组织教他稳定情绪使他得以在探索新方向的同时学着爱自己.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215120000 +0800" stop="20260215130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">嫣语赋</title>
    <desc lang="en">讲述了秋府最不受宠的大小姐秋嫣如何凭借自己的努力和智慧从深闺大院中走出来在一桩桩迷案中抽丝剥茧在一次次困难中辗转前行与冷面腹黑王爷梁翊从一路斗智斗勇到相伴相知最终二人收获了属于他们的幸福和爱情的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130000 +0800" stop="20260215140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">嫣语赋</title>
    <desc lang="en">讲述了秋府最不受宠的大小姐秋嫣如何凭借自己的努力和智慧从深闺大院中走出来在一桩桩迷案中抽丝剥茧在一次次困难中辗转前行与冷面腹黑王爷梁翊从一路斗智斗勇到相伴相知最终二人收获了属于他们的幸福和爱情的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215140000 +0800" stop="20260215153000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">健康2.0 (2024)</title>
    <desc lang="en">只要动手做健康就会来提供生活保健小撇步轻松看轻松学轻松做知名健康节目健康2.0每集邀请医生家庭医师复健专家和营养师共同守护全家健康.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215153000 +0800" stop="20260215163000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">部落探秘</title>
    <desc lang="en">在最后一趟的部落探秘之旅中探秘者潘嗣敬将拜访本地海人后代了解他们与海洋之间深厚的情感与连结随后他出发前往马来西亚柔佛新山拜访实里达海人村落了解这个坐落于繁华都市中的原住民族群如何延续以海为生的传统生活方式对于从小在海边长大的潘嗣敬而言这里的海人的生活他是否能够轻松应对.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215163000 +0800" stop="20260215173000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">再见明天</title>
    <desc lang="en">三人打开HENRY的水壶发现里面藏着一个加密的PDA水壶上刻着的诗句还有奶妈在各个领域屡获殊荣的剪报三人意识到HENRY的保定球正是控制时空循环的关键便决定再次利用水壶抓住HENRY他们成功擒住HENRY HENRY却揭示了一个令人震惊的真相这并不是时空循环而是多重宇宙.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215173000 +0800" stop="20260215183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">再见明天</title>
    <desc lang="en">1992年宇宙物理学家HENRY与图书管理员慧慈相恋并偶然发现能启动时空循环的陨石但他的野心让两人关系紧张慧慈最终摧毁了陨石2023年HENRY意识到自己多么需要慧慈开始从不同宇宙收集她的眼泪试图重组她的意识如今三人与HENRY争夺保定球时球体破裂四人被送入更遥远的宇宙.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215183000 +0800" stop="20260215190000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城六点半</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) 狮城6点半每日为您提供最全面的本地新闻头条与报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215190000 +0800" stop="20260215200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">天佑在许愿树下向雨菲告白成功接到仁芯来电急忙与雨菲去救尚豪尚豪躲过狙击手暗杀却被警方开枪击中受伤送医.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215200000 +0800" stop="20260215210000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">雨菲自愿留下照顾天佑真情告白让天佑起身回应她的爱仁美仁芯告知彩曦天雷派人暗杀尚豪彩曦震惊不已.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215210000 +0800" stop="20260215220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">天雷去喝酒遇见明凤为尚豪求情气愤中说已知道尚豪身世.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215220000 +0800" stop="20260215223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) 晚间新闻每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215223000 +0800" stop="20260215233000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">食尚玩家2天1夜GO (第三季)</title>
    <desc lang="en">在新一辑的食尚玩家 - 2 天1夜GO"里主持人纳豆曾子余等会带领观众周游许多耳目一新的地方国家包括泰国的曼谷和普吉岛日本的冲绳和台湾的嘉义台北以及桃园等.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215233000 +0800" stop="20260216000000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">前线追踪</title>
    <desc lang="en">民情民生民意前线追踪紧跟社会民生步伐追踪调查时事动态探讨新加坡人关心的课题针对问题的核心追根究底.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216000000 +0800" stop="20260216010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">三个愿望</title>
    <desc lang="en">善美发现钱币不见了怀疑在其中一个成员身上开始忧心忡忡害怕有人许愿家人会出事成龙考试得高分善美便怀疑他许了愿晓敏拿到唱片公司的合约得以出唱片善美也怀疑她许了愿把全家都当成贼.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216010000 +0800" stop="20260216020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">三个愿望</title>
    <desc lang="en">佑庭代理的保健品出了问题可能被控他不想坐牢向善美讨取钱币要许愿脱离困境善美和耀宗不希望佑庭逃避责任坦言就算钱币没有不见也不会给他佑庭痛心失望耀祖怂恿他出国避难佑庭临走前晓敏把一枚钱币交给他.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216020000 +0800" stop="20260216030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">微笑正义</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着一群对揭发事实真相极具热忱的新闻工作者从中带出新闻背后不为人知的秘密.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216030000 +0800" stop="20260216040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">微笑正义</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着一群对揭发事实真相极具热忱的新闻工作者从中带出新闻背后不为人知的秘密.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216040000 +0800" stop="20260216050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">喜事年年</title>
    <desc lang="en">喜事年年.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216050000 +0800" stop="20260216060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">喜事年年</title>
    <desc lang="en">喜事年年.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216060000 +0800" stop="20260216070000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">特别的食物给特别的你</title>
    <desc lang="en">曾代表新加坡出赛的大厨邱伟民传授厨艺为前囚犯创造就业机会傅孙明幸运逃过十年刑期出狱后创办咖啡厅聘请前囚犯帮他们重返社会杨君伟走访中途之家和社会企业了解食物如何帮助前囚犯开启第二人生.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216070000 +0800" stop="20260216073000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">晚间新闻每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216073000 +0800" stop="20260216080000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">前线追踪</title>
    <desc lang="en">民情民生民意前线追踪紧跟社会民生步伐追踪调查时事动态探讨新加坡人关心的课题针对问题的核心追根究底.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216080000 +0800" stop="20260216090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">迷茫又无惧的我们</title>
    <desc lang="en">迷茫又无惧的我们.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216090000 +0800" stop="20260216093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城热话</title>
    <desc lang="en">周一至周五晚上7点狮城有约谈话性栏目狮城热话以汇集多元声音及专家看法为目标通过网络投票和引导观点碰撞打造能让观众参与的时事舆论场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216093000 +0800" stop="20260216100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">企业强人</title>
    <desc lang="en">赵恺没有足够资金赎回董事们的股份只得将文浩留住宋翘提议为天空城引入第三方投资者方芳拒绝.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216100000 +0800" stop="20260216103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">焦点</title>
    <desc lang="en">焦点追踪国际时事实地报道区域课题以新加坡的视角分析时局发展的前因后果和潜在影响.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216103000 +0800" stop="20260216113000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">小明星大跟班新年特集</title>
    <desc lang="en">在这一个新年的特集里主持人吴宗宪和欧汉声将介绍给观众一些既经典又特别的年菜.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216113000 +0800" stop="20260216120000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">做节必食18道菜</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/广东话) 新春期间每家每户都会为团年做节花尽心思希望炮制最窝心美味的菜式与亲朋好友共享黄亚保三姐萧秀香祈积奇(Jacques)三位星级大厨带领一众艺员到访潮州顺德客家福建上海山东四川广东等地方菜代表从烹制过程中切磋交流还会品尝代表推介的新春名菜包括潮州围炉上海暖窝八仙过海水煮海鲜宴佛跳墙等吃尽各地的家乡风味.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216120000 +0800" stop="20260216130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">上山下海过一夜过年特集</title>
    <desc lang="en">2025年春节让"上山下海的一班主持跟你团圆过蛇年带你游山玩水蛇行天下.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216130000 +0800" stop="20260216133000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">一点新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) 一点新闻为您提供更新的本地与全球新闻头条.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216133000 +0800" stop="20260216140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">脚踏食地之新春游他乡</title>
    <desc lang="en">.新的一年新的旅途脚踏食地再次启程文杰携手王雪晶郭晓东曾洁钰和叶朝明游历槟城巴生班台和金马伦寻找年味和人情味他乡的美味丰富并滋养了这段旅程唯有光盘行动和感恩的心足以回报.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216140000 +0800" stop="20260216160000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">李茂扮太子</title>
    <desc lang="en">讲述的是已与富家女杨家珍结婚的小捕快李茂常远扮演意外发现自己与当朝太子同样由常远扮演相貌相同李茂因此想进宫获得晋升而当朝太子想出宫获得自由于是二人交换身份但都卷入了尚书的阴谋中.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216160000 +0800" stop="20260216180000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">阖家辣</title>
    <desc lang="en">本为音乐节搞手的Coba因COVID19疫情关系被逼在家工作每日与家人困兽斗直至无意间发现母亲的手工辣椒酱大受朋友好评Coba灵机一转决定说服父亲大姑妈一起制作辣椒酱销售在大赚一笔的同时亦可维持家庭和谐谁知辣椒酱生意一鸣惊人在创造销售奇迹的同时往后的发展也越来越超乎一家人的想象.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216180000 +0800" stop="20260216183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">老广的味道 第九季</title>
    <desc lang="en">老广的味道第九季继续坚持上山下海呈现地道广味通过现场纪录广东农民渔民的耕作及捕捞贴地气传播劳动者的正能量.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216183000 +0800" stop="20260216193000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城有约</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) 总结一天大小事关心属于你我的家园每逢星期一至五傍晚6.30-7.30pm与你相约.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216193000 +0800" stop="20260216194500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">古早味侦探 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">古早味侦探 3.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216194500 +0800" stop="20260216220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">出租家人</title>
    <desc lang="en">出身于破碎家庭的家聪陈家乐饰与演艺路上怀才不遇的单亲妈妈佩怡周家怡饰成立了一家可以提供出租家人服务的公司 一次偶然的机会家聪发掘了沉迷于演戏的临时演员志光曾志伟饰并诚邀他加入出租家人行列志光爽快答应 志光加入后又遇上喜欢跳舞的包租婆芳芳恬妞饰阴差阳错下两人出演临时夫妻并与家乐及佩怡变成一家人谁知这个临时家庭却在服务过程中发现了埋于深处的秘密究竟什么才算是家人最可贵的关系又是什么.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216220000 +0800" stop="20260216223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) 晚间新闻每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216223000 +0800" stop="20260216223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Chinese New Year Eve Special 2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chinese New Year Eve Special 2026.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216223000 +0800" stop="20260217003000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Chinese New Year Eve Special 2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chinese New Year Eve Special 2026.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217003000 +0800" stop="20260217033000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">热辣滚烫</title>
    <desc lang="en">大学毕业后仅仅工作短暂的一段时间杜乐莹便退回家中宅家长达十年之久她无所事事拒绝和外界做过多接触甚至和家人的关系也变得紧张起来在和离婚回到娘家的妹妹乐丹一次激烈的冲突后乐莹选择离家出走并且在烧烤店找了服务员的工作勉强维生爱情亲情人生似乎一时间均跌入了谷底而阴差阳错间乐莹又结识了落魄的拳击教练昊坤她支持着他的梦想彼此又不得不去面对残酷的现实人生至暗时刻随波逐流的女孩是否决心逆流而上.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217033000 +0800" stop="20260217040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">老广的味道 第九季</title>
    <desc lang="en">老广的味道第九季继续坚持上山下海呈现地道广味通过现场纪录广东农民渔民的耕作及捕捞贴地气传播劳动者的正能量.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217040000 +0800" stop="20260217050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">在世界的角落扎营</title>
    <desc lang="en">谢韵仪是公认的冒险玩家而郭妃丽则是大家眼中的贵妇两人却在近几年成为了好朋友一起到泰国挑战种种户外活动的她们会闹出什么样的笑话在营火旁聊起了各自的恋爱经历和爱情观她们又会透露出什么秘密.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215003000 +0800" stop="20260215020000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">歌手 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">歌手2025加盟歌手依旧汇聚了大中华地区以及其他地区的知名歌手首发歌手包括Mickey GuytonBENI单依纯Grace Kinstler歌手2019的陈楚生我是歌手第一季和歌手2017的林志炫歌手当打之年的白举纲以及歌手2018的GAI周延[1][2]补位歌手包括卫兰范玮琪火星电台郑欣宜以及我是歌手第三季的A-Lin黄丽玲揭榜歌手包括马嘉祺者来女唐汉霄Alexia Evellyn云飞歌手2019的声入人心男团成员阿云嘎.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215020000 +0800" stop="20260215023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">玩客疯高雄</title>
    <desc lang="en">"玩客疯高雄" 三组全新配备主持人为观众从不同的面向玩客疯高雄.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215023000 +0800" stop="20260215060000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215060000 +0800" stop="20260215100000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100000 +0800" stop="20260215130000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我想和你唱 (第五季)</title>
    <desc lang="en">节目继续升维星素共唱新玩法面向全民发布合唱邀约走进普通人的生活邀约全国各地素人为平凡人圆梦星素歌搭子结伴而来相聚在互动性年轻态的想唱音乐派对 出席歌手包括任贤齐李玖哲李宇春陈小春等.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130000 +0800" stop="20260215140000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">自由的旅行者</title>
    <desc lang="en">主持人由YouTuber融融担纲透过他独特的说故事方式带领观众去土耳其展开全新的冒险旅程.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215140000 +0800" stop="20260215150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">爸妈备多分</title>
    <desc lang="en">现实社会有约定俗成的规则但孩子能够理解并遵守吗本集有儿童心理学家和美学导师见证三组家长携带孩子参观美术馆的过程从中探讨父母应如何处理孩子在不同情境的状况以及如何透过美学培养孩子看待世界的眼光.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215150000 +0800" stop="20260215160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">基督山小姐</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 该剧讲述了一个被信任的朋友逼到死亡的女人下定决心报仇找回被夺走的人生.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215160000 +0800" stop="20260215170000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">基督山小姐</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 该剧讲述了一个被信任的朋友逼到死亡的女人下定决心报仇找回被夺走的人生.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215170000 +0800" stop="20260215180000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">黄金面具</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述三个女人因错误的欲望和贪欲酿成悲剧她们在疯狂斗争中寻找人生答案的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215180000 +0800" stop="20260215190000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">黄金面具</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述三个女人因错误的欲望和贪欲酿成悲剧她们在疯狂斗争中寻找人生答案的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215190000 +0800" stop="20260215203000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">亚洲新声</title>
    <desc lang="en">该节目由新声启航人Jessie J新声召集人张靓颖新声见证人张信哲新声护航员尤长靖四位歌手加盟携手亚洲新声代歌手共同开启跨越文化界限的音乐盛宴.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215203000 +0800" stop="20260215210000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">逛遍全中国</title>
    <desc lang="en">旅行体验师将去到贵州广西 广东 三个省份的宝藏景区品尝当地特色美食领略当地的好山好水感受当地深厚人文历史和奇特风味.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215210000 +0800" stop="20260215220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的野蛮新娘</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) Kham Duang姑娘必须成为一名士兵或一列水牛列车的领队以代替她生病的父亲出售水牛这导致她成为大爵爷名义上的妻子.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215220000 +0800" stop="20260215230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我的野蛮新娘</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) Kham Duang姑娘必须成为一名士兵或一列水牛列车的领队以代替她生病的父亲出售水牛这导致她成为大爵爷名义上的妻子.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215230000 +0800" stop="20260215233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">晚间新闻每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215233000 +0800" stop="20260215233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">正义的重生</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此劇講述人生重來一次 能力值滿點的熱血檢察官懲治絕對惡行的故事背景配樂為英國作曲家 Holst 所寫行星組曲中木星主題旋律穿梭劇情之中.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215233000 +0800" stop="20260216003000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">正义的重生</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此劇講述人生重來一次 能力值滿點的熱血檢察官懲治絕對惡行的故事背景配樂為英國作曲家 Holst 所寫行星組曲中木星主題旋律穿梭劇情之中.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216003000 +0800" stop="20260216020000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">亚洲新声</title>
    <desc lang="en">该节目由新声启航人Jessie J新声召集人张靓颖新声见证人张信哲新声护航员尤长靖四位歌手加盟携手亚洲新声代歌手共同开启跨越文化界限的音乐盛宴.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216020000 +0800" stop="20260216023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">逛遍全中国</title>
    <desc lang="en">旅行体验师将去到贵州广西 广东 三个省份的宝藏景区品尝当地特色美食领略当地的好山好水感受当地深厚人文历史和奇特风味.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216023000 +0800" stop="20260216060000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216060000 +0800" stop="20260216140000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216140000 +0800" stop="20260216160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">我想和你唱 (第五季)</title>
    <desc lang="en">节目继续升维星素共唱新玩法面向全民发布合唱邀约走进普通人的生活邀约全国各地素人为平凡人圆梦星素歌搭子结伴而来相聚在互动性年轻态的想唱音乐派对 出席歌手包括任贤齐李玖哲李宇春陈小春等.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216160000 +0800" stop="20260216200000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">浙江卫视2026跨年晚会</title>
    <desc lang="en">盛典将以经典金曲串联温暖记忆用创意舞台点燃新年期许五大篇章初绽共聚破晓同心华章层层递进让我们的同心力量成为贯穿始终的主旋律演出艺人及歌手包括张信哲韩庚白鹿游鸿明阿云嘎等等.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216200000 +0800" stop="20260216220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">逐梦练习曲</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 一位失势的音乐制作人遇到了一位拥有一切成名条件的艺术家池勋却发现唯一阻碍他走向成功的是令他无法登台的严重怯场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216220000 +0800" stop="20260216230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">台湾百味</title>
    <desc lang="en">这个节目专门推荐台湾美食餐厅透过节目将台湾料理带给更多人认识以及餐馆背后动人故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216230000 +0800" stop="20260216233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">晚间新闻每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216233000 +0800" stop="20260216233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">临时劫案</title>
    <desc lang="en">两个颓废中年难兄难弟慕蓉辉任贤齐饰阿怂林家栋饰计划抢劫却意外被悍匪梅蓝天郭富城饰搅局阴差阳错间三人临时组队不料钱款早已被捷足先登一时间匪徒各怀鬼胎互相吞并与此同时女警探姜姐张可颐饰也将三人锁定枪战抢钱一触即发临时劫案谁生谁死谁破案.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216233000 +0800" stop="20260217014500 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">临时劫案</title>
    <desc lang="en">两个颓废中年难兄难弟慕蓉辉任贤齐饰阿怂林家栋饰计划抢劫却意外被悍匪梅蓝天郭富城饰搅局阴差阳错间三人临时组队不料钱款早已被捷足先登一时间匪徒各怀鬼胎互相吞并与此同时女警探姜姐张可颐饰也将三人锁定枪战抢钱一触即发临时劫案谁生谁死谁破案.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217014500 +0800" stop="20260217023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">台湾百味</title>
    <desc lang="en">这个节目专门推荐台湾美食餐厅透过节目将台湾料理带给更多人认识以及餐馆背后动人故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215000000 +0800" stop="20260215090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215090000 +0800" stop="20260215093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Legenda Puteri Qaseh</title>
    <desc lang="en">A story in the kingdom of Kayajaya, a kind-hearted village girl realizes that she is the rightful heir to the throne and must quickly learn the customs to become a queen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215093000 +0800" stop="20260215100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Indonesia Authentic Places</title>
    <desc lang="en">For most of the time, Indonesia is a magnet for most travelers and adventurers. With more than seventeen thousand islands scattered across over five million kilometers and three time zones that needs a lifetime to explore and appreciate its natural beauty. Same with its title, the program sums it all up into twenty-five must-visit authentic destinations that simply cannot be missed. From defining beaches to magical mountains and wild forests, be prepared to be amazed by authentic Indonesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100000 +0800" stop="20260215110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ekspedisi Ekstrem</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ekspedisi Ekstrem explores the human stories behind those living in unusual and extraordinary spaces. Each week, a celebrity guest will follow the host for a stay with communities living in remote, rugged terrains. Stepping out of their comfort zones, they will learn essential livelihood skills and be tasked with challenges that will test their skills and character. At the same time, Ekspedisi Ekstrem gives an intimate glimpse of the communities' unique dwellings and their ways to survive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215110000 +0800" stop="20260215120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Tetamu Ramadan</title>
    <desc lang="en">This year's Ramadan is quite special for Salahudin's family. They are waiting for their daughters return from London. Nina comes home with her boyfriend, Farid. Their intention is to get the blessings from their family but it took a toll on them. Rozainah, Ninas mother, seem unwelcoming towards Farids presence. What made Rozainah anxious about Farid? Is there a secret between them? Will the other family members know about their secret? Watch Tetamu Ramadan a family drama filled with secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215120000 +0800" stop="20260215123000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kembara Chef Wan Laluan Sutera</title>
    <desc lang="en">Datuk Chef Wan venturing hidden gems of SILK ROAD culinary scene in his quest of the ultimate gastronomic experience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215123000 +0800" stop="20260215130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Resepi Most Wanted</title>
    <desc lang="en">A travelogue that showcases the diverse cuisines of different races, ethnicities, and cultures in Malaysia, enriched with humor and illustrations by the two hosts and the local community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130000 +0800" stop="20260215140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aku Yang Kau Sakiti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Amanda is upset when Cika slaps her after a misunderstanding over a guy. Raikal tries his best to win over Amanda's heart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215140000 +0800" stop="20260215150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aku Yang Kau Sakiti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Afraid that Zaki's company may fall into the hands of others, Mazwin seeks Amanda's help to persuade Bella to work at Zaki's company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215150000 +0800" stop="20260215153000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kyrgyzstan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kyrgyzstan is a country that resembles a hidden paradise and is seldom explored. This Central Asian nation is home to 1,001 extraordinary treasures that remain untouched by modernity. With its snowy mountains, sea-blue lakes, rows of white yurts, and hundreds of tame horses, Kyrgyzstan offers a unique experience for travellers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215153000 +0800" stop="20260215160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ini Baru Rare: Iceland</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iceland, a sub-Arctic country, boasts breathtaking landscapes and natural phenomena that are rarely found elsewhere in the world. Recently, it has gained recognition among global travelers, becoming a paradise for photographers, 4WD drivers, and enthusiasts of cold climates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215160000 +0800" stop="20260215170000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Hospital Loveline</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr Arfan, a charismatic young doctor, begins his first day at the hospital owned by his father, Dr Farhad. Sophia finds him arrogant, and their frequent encounters only deepen her negative impression of him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215170000 +0800" stop="20260215180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aku Seorang Perempuan</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Fareez's death, Siti Noraisya decides to make a comeback to the recording industry. Ehsan's confesses to Siti Noraisya that he has feelings for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215180000 +0800" stop="20260215183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Legenda Puteri Qaseh</title>
    <desc lang="en">A story in the kingdom of Kayajaya, a kind-hearted village girl realizes that she is the rightful heir to the throne and must quickly learn the customs to become a queen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215183000 +0800" stop="20260215190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Indonesia Authentic Places</title>
    <desc lang="en">For most of the time, Indonesia is a magnet for most travelers and adventurers. With more than seventeen thousand islands scattered across over five million kilometers and three time zones that needs a lifetime to explore and appreciate its natural beauty. Same with its title, the program sums it all up into twenty-five must-visit authentic destinations that simply cannot be missed. From defining beaches to magical mountains and wild forests, be prepared to be amazed by authentic Indonesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215190000 +0800" stop="20260215193000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kembara Chef Wan Laluan Sutera</title>
    <desc lang="en">Datuk Chef Wan venturing hidden gems of SILK ROAD culinary scene in his quest of the ultimate gastronomic experience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215193000 +0800" stop="20260215200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Resepi Most Wanted</title>
    <desc lang="en">A travelogue that showcases the diverse cuisines of different races, ethnicities, and cultures in Malaysia, enriched with humor and illustrations by the two hosts and the local community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215200000 +0800" stop="20260215203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215203000 +0800" stop="20260215213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sepahtu Reunion Live S8 ( 2023 )</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jep, Rahim, Pak Ya and Ebby Yus are back to entertain you in the latest season featuring special celebrity guests and unexpected cameos every week. Guest Artist - Sherry Ibrahim and Uqasha Senrose Cameo Appearance - Tomok.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215213000 +0800" stop="20260215223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Hospital Loveline</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sophia's grandmother is admitted to hospital after a fall near her home. As Sophia tends to her Opah, she does not realise that someone has been quietly following her every move.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215223000 +0800" stop="20260215233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Marina</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marina believes Haqiem intentionally humiliates her on his podcast and gets back at him. Meanwhile, Delisha begs Haqiem for a chance to prove herself worthy of being his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215233000 +0800" stop="20260216000000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216000000 +0800" stop="20260216090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216090000 +0800" stop="20260216093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Upin &amp; Ipin S13</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual Language Malay and English) The 13th season of Upin &amp; Ipin' will features among those include new activities like entering a fun run, facing crisis of missing friends, worrying about their Opah having a bad mood and many more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216093000 +0800" stop="20260216100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Indonesia Authentic Places</title>
    <desc lang="en">For most of the time, Indonesia is a magnet for most travelers and adventurers. With more than seventeen thousand islands scattered across over five million kilometers and three time zones that needs a lifetime to explore and appreciate its natural beauty. Same with its title, the program sums it all up into twenty-five must-visit authentic destinations that simply cannot be missed. From defining beaches to magical mountains and wild forests, be prepared to be amazed by authentic Indonesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216100000 +0800" stop="20260216110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Couple Cosmo</title>
    <desc lang="en">Albeit their tough love, Remy is determined to start his marriage with Ruby on a right foot but Ruby is getting frustrated with living frugally. Firman's and Happy's life is a juggling act between career and family. And Marzuki plans to spend his retirement days with Sofea. Watch how these three families life cross paths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216110000 +0800" stop="20260216120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Melur Untuk Firdaus 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hariz suspects that Zachery has a crush on Melur and warns her to be wary of him. Mawar continues to annoy Firdaus at work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216120000 +0800" stop="20260216130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">S.P.Y. S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">A series of acts of arson set the SPY team off into investigation mode. Rebel youths, a masked figure, a veteran firefighter, and an aged hoarder make up the suspects in the investigations that ensue. Meanwhile Ben provides advice and delicate support to one of his mentees who is behaving dubiously. Hasif struggles to juggle work with handling his teenage brother Nizam who is drifting away from him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216130000 +0800" stop="20260216140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aku Seorang Perempuan</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Fareez's death, Siti Noraisya decides to make a comeback to the recording industry. Ehsan's confesses to Siti Noraisya that he has feelings for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216140000 +0800" stop="20260216150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sayap Cinta Terindah</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dhani takes on the responsibility of caring for his younger siblings - Ariel, David and Isyana - navigating the challlenges of their intertwined lives. As their journey unfolds, each sibling harbors hidden secrets waiting to be uncovered. Will Dhani uncover the truths they're keeping from him?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216150000 +0800" stop="20260216160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sepahtu Reunion Live S8 ( 2023 )</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jep, Rahim, Pak Ya and Ebby Yus are back to entertain you in the latest season featuring special celebrity guests and unexpected cameos every week. Guest Artist - Sherry Ibrahim and Uqasha Senrose Cameo Appearance - Tomok.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216160000 +0800" stop="20260216170000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Hospital Loveline</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sophia's grandmother is admitted to hospital after a fall near her home. As Sophia tends to her Opah, she does not realise that someone has been quietly following her every move.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216170000 +0800" stop="20260216180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Papa Ricky</title>
    <desc lang="en">Realising Zara is about to leave, Alisya reaches out to her, spending time together to lift her spirits. She invites Zara to celebrate her birthday with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216180000 +0800" stop="20260216183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Upin &amp; Ipin S13</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual Language Malay and English) The 13th season of Upin &amp; Ipin' will features among those include new activities like entering a fun run, facing crisis of missing friends, worrying about their Opah having a bad mood and many more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216183000 +0800" stop="20260216190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Janji Sedap</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join our chef as he takes you to a culinary journey and learn how to whip up vibrant and flavoursome cuisine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216190000 +0800" stop="20260216200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Akad Yang Terlindung</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tan Sri Ismail shocks everyone by appointing Remy as the CEO, overturning all expectations. Enraged by the decision, Lisa turns her fury on Sophia, escalating her harassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216200000 +0800" stop="20260216203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216203000 +0800" stop="20260216213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Travelawak Projek Bapak Bapak S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Projek Bapak Bapak S3 returns with a new twist this time they are travelling to Dubai and Korea. Will they survive a double location adventure with jet lag, language barriers and crazier challenges?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216213000 +0800" stop="20260216223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cuci S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a tense encounter at a cafe, Chris goes into hiding as police intensify their search following new evidence. Tensions rise at CSS when Husin clashes with Mairah's management style, while Hana urges him to leave and seek a better future. Hilmi grows suspicious of Dani. Emma is haunted by increasingly gory visions of Janice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216223000 +0800" stop="20260216233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Andai Tiada Dia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Intan is left paralysed after the accident. Suri remains conflicted, unsure whether she can forgive Intan or not.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216233000 +0800" stop="20260217000000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217000000 +0800" stop="20260217010000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jendela Hati</title>
    <desc lang="en">Farah agrees to marry her brother-in-law, Lukman, to fulfill her sister's final wish. However, Lukman seems reluctant to marry Farah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217010000 +0800" stop="20260217020000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jendela Hati</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lukman decides to move back to his own place with Farah. He worries about Myra when she goes missing after the wedding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217020000 +0800" stop="20260217030000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jendela Hati</title>
    <desc lang="en">Myra is curious as to why Johan is volunteering to help her out despite being only recently acquainted. Farah wonders if Lukman is hiding something from her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217030000 +0800" stop="20260217040000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jendela Hati</title>
    <desc lang="en">Budi tries to advise Lukman when Lukman is still unsure about his marriage to Farah. Farah feels slighted by Lukman's action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217040000 +0800" stop="20260217050000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jendela Hati</title>
    <desc lang="en">Farah comes up with a plan to win Lukman's heart. Lukman has been reminded of the past in his dreams for the past few days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215010000 +0800" stop="20260215013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215013000 +0800" stop="20260215090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215090000 +0800" stop="20260215100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Legends of India Season 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Legends of India is a Tamil documentary Series that celebrates the lives and legacies of iconic Indian Personalities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100000 +0800" stop="20260215130000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Aruvadai Naal</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nirmala, a young woman who wants to become a nun, unexpectedly falls in love with Muthuvel. However, the latter's father does not approve of their relationship and makes all the arrangements for his marriage without telling him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130000 +0800" stop="20260215160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Kushi</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young man from an agnostic family falls in love with the daughter of his father's arch-rival, a devout Hindu leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215160000 +0800" stop="20260215190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Perazhagan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chinna, a phone booth operator, falls for a woman who is blind and wants to help her regain her eyesight. On the other hand, Kartik, his lookalike, is in love with the police commissioner's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215190000 +0800" stop="20260215200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Vizag in Concert</title>
    <desc lang="en">Vizag in Concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215200000 +0800" stop="20260215203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with a new season of Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215203000 +0800" stop="20260215210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215210000 +0800" stop="20260215220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Ithu Enna Paatu S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ithu Enna paatu a game show all about songs. It will test your knowledge, memory and everything &amp; anything about tamil cine songs and will keep anyone who loves kollywood music glued to the set. It is catered to all age groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215220000 +0800" stop="20260215220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Irugapatru</title>
    <desc lang="en">The perfect life of a marriage counsellor becomes complicated by her own methods and techniques. There are ups and downs with two other couples as she returns to her happy married life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215220000 +0800" stop="20260216010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Irugapatru</title>
    <desc lang="en">The perfect life of a marriage counsellor becomes complicated by her own methods and techniques. There are ups and downs with two other couples as she returns to her happy married life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216010000 +0800" stop="20260216013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216013000 +0800" stop="20260216090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216090000 +0800" stop="20260216093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rusiyai Thedi Sr 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rusiyai Thedi is back with new mouth-watering segments! Join hosts Thivyaa and Kishore as they embark on this gastronomy journey. Also, there will be exclusive guests appearances, from food experts to your favorite celebrities!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216093000 +0800" stop="20260216100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">SiriSiri Siri Siri S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Compilation of comedy clips to tickle your laughing bone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216100000 +0800" stop="20260216103100 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Indian Beat S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">A bilingual magazine show that serves as a platform by featuring activities and events organized by the various Tamil and Indian ethnic organizations around Singapore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216103100 +0800" stop="20260216110000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216110000 +0800" stop="20260216120000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Suvai 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suvai 3 (HD).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216120000 +0800" stop="20260216150000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Parthal Pasitheerum</title>
    <desc lang="en">Believing his wife to be dead, a soldier in the British-Indian army marries another woman and moves on. After few years, he finds out that his ex-wife is still alive and feels miserable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216150000 +0800" stop="20260216160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Kaadhal Kaditham</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kaadhal Kaditham is back once again with 2 more beautiful stories! The problems these couples faced were huge. What seemed impossible was made possible by them. Their stories allow us to learn that everything is possible with love &amp; care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216160000 +0800" stop="20260216190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Uzhaippaali (1993)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A struggling laborer learns he is the heir to a wealthy empire and must battle deceitful relatives to claim his rightful place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216190000 +0800" stop="20260216193000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Damu's Kitchen</title>
    <desc lang="en">Time to deep dive into some old, lesser known recipes that have been lost in time. Learn it from Chef Damu as he unveils the treasure trove of heritage recipes in this season of Damu's Kitchen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216193000 +0800" stop="20260216200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Damu's Kitchen</title>
    <desc lang="en">Time to deep dive into some old, lesser known recipes that have been lost in time. Learn it from Chef Damu as he unveils the treasure trove of heritage recipes in this season of Damu's Kitchen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216200000 +0800" stop="20260216203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Magarantham</title>
    <desc lang="en">Madhan and Shankari have an emotional heart-to-heart talk, while Suseela reconsiders her mother's words, mindful of her health. Madhan also confronts Geetha, Kelvin's wife, and realizes his past selfishness. Eventually, both Madhan and Suseela meet their alliances but choose to reject them. In the meantime, Kelvin and Pravin Banu impersonate Madhan and Suseela during the meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216203000 +0800" stop="20260216210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216210000 +0800" stop="20260216213000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Aaha Kalyanam (The Con of Matrimony)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Intense lead-up to the finale, wedding preparations are disrupted by troubling events. As past grievances surface, an unexpected figure adds to the intrigue. At the wedding hall, Ravi connects Mdm Rani's disappearance to recent mysteries. The stage is set for a finale full of revelations and confrontations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216213000 +0800" stop="20260216220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Koranjeh Velai Niranjeh Ooru S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">A television program where the host, Rabbit Mac takes viewers around Malaysia on a shoestring budget.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216220000 +0800" stop="20260216220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Eleven</title>
    <desc lang="en">A brave and skilled officer with a strong record of solving tough cases is assigned to a new, more challenging serial killing investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216220000 +0800" stop="20260217003000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Eleven</title>
    <desc lang="en">A brave and skilled officer with a strong record of solving tough cases is assigned to a new, more challenging serial killing investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217003000 +0800" stop="20260217010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with a new season of Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217010000 +0800" stop="20260217013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217013000 +0800" stop="20260217040000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">David (2013)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A gangster in trouble with the law, an amateur guitarist planning to assassinate a politician and a fisherman in love with a woman he cannot be with are all named David, and they share a connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217040000 +0800" stop="20260217043000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Live in Bytes</title>
    <desc lang="en">Groove to some new live music with your favourite artists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215000000 +0800" stop="20260215000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215000300 +0800" stop="20260215003000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215003000 +0800" stop="20260215010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Salt of the Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">A special salt that is engineered and shaped by tides and the moon. Precision meets instinct as salt is designed, one grain at a time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215010000 +0800" stop="20260215013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215013000 +0800" stop="20260215020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215020000 +0800" stop="20260215023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215023000 +0800" stop="20260215030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 10th arrondissement in Paris is known locally as "Little Jaffna", a haven for the city's South Asian population and a hub for 50,000 Sri Lankan Tamils who call France their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215030000 +0800" stop="20260215040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">How Graphic!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Syaqil Sarafian, a freelance graphic designer is tasked by snack brand manufacturer Uncle Saba's to create a vintage shop signboard with an iconic Singaporean mascot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215040000 +0800" stop="20260215043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215043000 +0800" stop="20260215050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Salt of the Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">A special salt that is engineered and shaped by tides and the moon. Precision meets instinct as salt is designed, one grain at a time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215050000 +0800" stop="20260215060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Love Auditors</title>
    <desc lang="en">Love Auditors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215060000 +0800" stop="20260215063000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215063000 +0800" stop="20260215070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215070000 +0800" stop="20260215073000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215073000 +0800" stop="20260215080000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 10th arrondissement in Paris is known locally as "Little Jaffna", a haven for the city's South Asian population and a hub for 50,000 Sri Lankan Tamils who call France their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215080000 +0800" stop="20260215083000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215083000 +0800" stop="20260215090000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Salt of the Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">A special salt that is engineered and shaped by tides and the moon. Precision meets instinct as salt is designed, one grain at a time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215090000 +0800" stop="20260215093000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215093000 +0800" stop="20260215100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100000 +0800" stop="20260215100200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215100200 +0800" stop="20260215110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Love Auditors</title>
    <desc lang="en">Love Auditors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215110000 +0800" stop="20260215113000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215113000 +0800" stop="20260215120000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215120000 +0800" stop="20260215123000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215123000 +0800" stop="20260215130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130000 +0800" stop="20260215130200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215130200 +0800" stop="20260215140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Japan Hour</title>
    <desc lang="en">The area around 'Jingu' the Grand Shrine of Ise, was a popular place even during the Edo period. We visited the suburban spot to check out unique lifestyles of locals on our 300km journey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215140000 +0800" stop="20260215143000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215143000 +0800" stop="20260215150000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Salt of the Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">A special salt that is engineered and shaped by tides and the moon. Precision meets instinct as salt is designed, one grain at a time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215150000 +0800" stop="20260215153000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215153000 +0800" stop="20260215160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 10th arrondissement in Paris is known locally as "Little Jaffna", a haven for the city's South Asian population and a hub for 50,000 Sri Lankan Tamils who call France their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215160000 +0800" stop="20260215160200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215160200 +0800" stop="20260215170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">How Graphic!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brindha Menon, a self-taught illustrator has been tasked by a multi-generational food manufacturer and hawker stall owner Pondok Abang to create a heritage-themed menu design.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215170000 +0800" stop="20260215173000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215173000 +0800" stop="20260215180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215180000 +0800" stop="20260215183000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215183000 +0800" stop="20260215190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215190000 +0800" stop="20260215190200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215190200 +0800" stop="20260215200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215200000 +0800" stop="20260215203000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215203000 +0800" stop="20260215210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Salt of the Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">This is a one-of-a-kind salt, drawn from geothermal springs and the pressure of geological time that captures the taste of the earth itself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215210000 +0800" stop="20260215210200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215210200 +0800" stop="20260215220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A.I. Isn't</title>
    <desc lang="en">A.I. Isn't.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215220000 +0800" stop="20260215223000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215223000 +0800" stop="20260215230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cambodia's busy capital of Phnom Penh is home to about a 1,000 Nigerians who are beginning to seamlessly integrate into their adopted country's culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215230000 +0800" stop="20260215230300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260215230300 +0800" stop="20260216000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216000000 +0800" stop="20260216000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216000300 +0800" stop="20260216010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">How Graphic!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brindha Menon, a self-taught illustrator has been tasked by a multi-generational food manufacturer and hawker stall owner Pondok Abang to create a heritage-themed menu design.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216010000 +0800" stop="20260216020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Insight investigates and analyses topical issues that impact Asia and the rest of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216020000 +0800" stop="20260216023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216023000 +0800" stop="20260216030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cambodia's busy capital of Phnom Penh is home to about a 1,000 Nigerians who are beginning to seamlessly integrate into their adopted country's culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216030000 +0800" stop="20260216033000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216033000 +0800" stop="20260216040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 10th arrondissement in Paris is known locally as "Little Jaffna", a haven for the city's South Asian population and a hub for 50,000 Sri Lankan Tamils who call France their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216040000 +0800" stop="20260216043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216043000 +0800" stop="20260216050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Salt of the Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">This is a one-of-a-kind salt, drawn from geothermal springs and the pressure of geological time that captures the taste of the earth itself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216050000 +0800" stop="20260216060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A.I. Isn't</title>
    <desc lang="en">A.I. Isn't.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216060000 +0800" stop="20260216063000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216063000 +0800" stop="20260216070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cambodia's busy capital of Phnom Penh is home to about a 1,000 Nigerians who are beginning to seamlessly integrate into their adopted country's culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216070000 +0800" stop="20260216100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia First</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Top stories, business news and market updates from across the region as Asia gears up for the day ahead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216100000 +0800" stop="20260216110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A.I. Isn't</title>
    <desc lang="en">A.I. Isn't.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216110000 +0800" stop="20260216130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216130000 +0800" stop="20260216140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Love Auditors</title>
    <desc lang="en">Love Auditors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216140000 +0800" stop="20260216160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216160000 +0800" stop="20260216170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216170000 +0800" stop="20260216170200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216170200 +0800" stop="20260216180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216180000 +0800" stop="20260216190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216190000 +0800" stop="20260216200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">IPS SG Perspectives Conference</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Institute of Policy Studies holds its annual Singapore Perspectives conference discussing the public policy challenges Singapore faces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216200000 +0800" stop="20260216210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216210000 +0800" stop="20260216220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A.I. Isn't</title>
    <desc lang="en">A.I. Isn't.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216220000 +0800" stop="20260216230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260216230000 +0800" stop="20260217000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">A.I. Isn't</title>
    <desc lang="en">A.I. Isn't.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217000000 +0800" stop="20260217000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News 2025/2026</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217000300 +0800" stop="20260217010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217010000 +0800" stop="20260217013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 10th arrondissement in Paris is known locally as "Little Jaffna", a haven for the city's South Asian population and a hub for 50,000 Sri Lankan Tamils who call France their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217013000 +0800" stop="20260217020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The New Locals</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cambodia's busy capital of Phnom Penh is home to about a 1,000 Nigerians who are beginning to seamlessly integrate into their adopted country's culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217020000 +0800" stop="20260217030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217030000 +0800" stop="20260217040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260217040000 +0800" stop="20260217050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>