<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.2.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251125000000 +0800" stop="20251125003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Provocative</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sivan hopes Venya can regain her memory without any prompting on his part, but Vasundra has other ideas. Nadrah worries that Irfan will misconstrue her concern for his recovery as a chance to rekindle their relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125003000 +0800" stop="20251125013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">FBI: Most Wanted S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Fugitive Task Force relentlessly tracks notorious criminals on the Bureau's Most Wanted list.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125013000 +0800" stop="20251125020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125020000 +0800" stop="20251125030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sitting on a Fortune S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Players can win up-to 100,000 in prize money in this high-stakes, high-tension game show hosted by Gary Lineker. But with no lifelines or chances to walk away they will risk everything on getting the right answer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125030000 +0800" stop="20251125040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125040000 +0800" stop="20251125043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125043000 +0800" stop="20251125050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Mark Moriarty – Cook Like A Chef - Series 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Cook Like a Chef, award-winning chef Mark Moriarty invites viewers to rethink the way they cook at home. Forget the notion that great food demands endless ingredients or hours in the kitchen. With a handful of core ingredients, a well-stocked pantry, and a few pro tips, Mark shows how anyone can create restaurant-worthy meals in their own kitchen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125050000 +0800" stop="20251129235000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">LEGO Masters USA S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">This returning series brings imagination, design and creativity to life when teams of LEGO enthusiasts go head-to-head, with infinite possibilities and anunlimited supply of LEGO bricks. Teams of two will compete against each other in ambitious brick-building challenges to be crowned the country's most talented amateur LEGO builders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129235000 +0800" stop="20251130002000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Incredible Tales S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">A routine walk home, in the wee hours of the morning, becomes a life-altering ordeal, when a Bartender finds himself becoming the only witness in a terrifying assault case. He may have decided to turn his back, and distance himself from the incident, but injustices have a peculiar way of haunting those who are guilt-ridden, and he was about to be served a reminder, from the netherworld...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130002000 +0800" stop="20251130011500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Good Karma Hospital S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">'The Good Karma Hospital' follows doctor Ruby Walker who swaps England for India and finds herself at an under-resourced and over-worked cottage hospital run by eccentric Englishwoman Lydia Fonseca (Amanda Redman).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130011500 +0800" stop="20251130021000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo UK S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130021000 +0800" stop="20251130024000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Planet Action S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Planet Action takes you behind the scenes of the best action movies released. Each episode you'll get all the secrets straight from your favorite action heroes, get exclusive trivia and special reports from the most dangerous film sets, and get insight information on how the filmmakers make giant monsters come to life. This show is a sci-fi, cowboy, world-destruction, action-combo that will literally blow your mind!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130024000 +0800" stop="20251130031000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Monster Jam S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Returning season. Professional monster truck drivers compete against each other in races and freestyle competitions around the world to win the top prize.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130031000 +0800" stop="20251130033500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130033500 +0800" stop="20251130040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130040000 +0800" stop="20251130043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Weather Gone Viral S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">From whirling tornadoes to torrential rains, to harrowing hurricanes, Weather Gone Viral gives viewers unprecedented access to some of the most insane meteorological moments from around the world. Featuring videos of the most extreme and destructive weather conditions, firsthand accounts, and professional meteorologists sharing tales from the front lines, viewers get to experience the fury of Mother Nature.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130043000 +0800" stop="20251130053000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Press Your Luck S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hosted by Elizabeth Banks, Press Your Luck is a game of wits, strategy and even higher stakes as contestants try to avoid the iconic and devilish WHAMMY for a chance at life-changing cash and prizes. During each game of Press Your Luck, three contestants compete against each other, answering questions to earn spins on the Big Board.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130053000 +0800" stop="20251130060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Deal Or No Deal Australia S12</title>
    <desc lang="en">The exhilarating hit game show where contestants must beat The Banker to win a huge cash prize, is making a triumphant return. The ultimate contest of nerve, luck and pure gut instinct will be fronted by one of Australia's most beloved TV presenters, Gold Logie winner Grant Denyer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130060000 +0800" stop="20251130063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Hiccup And Sneeze S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hiccup and Sneeze are two young forest monsters that snuck in one day out of the rain. They are a brother and sister, who liked the place so much they decided to stay. (Monsters sometimes do that and it's not even considered rude - but that's just monsters). Anyway, they're all living together in Bibi's magical house even though sometimes Hiccup and Sneeze don't really understand that being a monster and being a human are two very different things...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130063000 +0800" stop="20251130070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Club M.A.G.I.C S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's Sports Day on CLUB M.A.G.I.C! Miss P is conducting a friendly race among her Positive Agents! Sham makes Miss P proud when he readily congratulates Didi for winning the race. Miss P says he has great sportsmanship! THE BIG WORD is 'marathon' and the smaller words featured are ran, hot and moth. In ROCKIN' RHYTHM, Didi does a sporty aerobicize that gets everyone moving their bodies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130070000 +0800" stop="20251130073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">123 Number Squad S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shelly has trouble with her 10 musical pipes. The Number Squad needs to determine the operational pipes and those requiring fixing. Can they solve the musical mystery and restore harmony? Number squad helps Captain Red to locate the Golden Fluffwort. The squad faces the challenge of deciphering the numerical clues on a mysterious paper to locate the elusive plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130073000 +0800" stop="20251130080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cows &amp; Crayons S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cows &amp; Crayons S1.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130080000 +0800" stop="20251130081500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Tayo the Little Bus 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of Tayo, a blue bus with the number 120. He is very playful and mischievous with his passengers and his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130081500 +0800" stop="20251130083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Tayo the Little Bus 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">The adventures of Tayo, a blue bus with the number 120. He is very playful and mischievous with his passengers and his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130083000 +0800" stop="20251130090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Songs &amp; Stories</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enjoy the best of Pinkfong's most loved songs and stories with all your favourite characters!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130090000 +0800" stop="20251130091500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Catch! Teenieping</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Princess Romi accidentally let go of her magical fairies, called Teeniepings. She and her friends are now on a mission to catch all her Teeniepings!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130091500 +0800" stop="20251130093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Catch! Teenieping</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) Princess Romi accidentally let go of her magical fairies, called Teeniepings. She and her friends are now on a mission to catch all her Teeniepings!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130093000 +0800" stop="20251130094500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Chimera Keepers: Adventures with Incredible Creatures</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Thelma and Wendy on an extraordinary summer adventure, discovering the unique and magical Chimera creatures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130094500 +0800" stop="20251130100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Chimera Keepers: Adventures with Incredible Creatures</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Thelma and Wendy on an extraordinary summer adventure, discovering the unique and magical Chimera creatures!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100000 +0800" stop="20251130101500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dogmatix and the Indomitables S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Idefix and his indomitable friends Bantera, Stamina and Gluttonix are back to resist the Romans! There's no doubt they will triumph through their unwavering friendship and combined talents, in 52 new and unprecedented adventures filled with adventure and humor, by Toutatis!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130101500 +0800" stop="20251130103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dogmatix and the Indomitables S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Idefix and his indomitable friends Bantera, Stamina and Gluttonix are back to resist the Romans! There's no doubt they will triumph through their unwavering friendship and combined talents, in 52 new and unprecedented adventures filled with adventure and humor, by Toutatis!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130103000 +0800" stop="20251130104500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Puberteens</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mike is showered with attention as the ambassador of the popular Pim &amp; Pop juice drink - the Mega Mangosteen Mix! However, he soon discovers that the school's favorite drink harbours a delicious, dark secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130104500 +0800" stop="20251130110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Puberteens</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following the Pim &amp; Pop debacle, the Puberteens have become the public enemy. Celeste takes it upon herself to single-handedly rehiblitate the Puberteens' image, and encounters a nemesis of old.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130110000 +0800" stop="20251130113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Transformers: Earthspark S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">After the end of the Transformers' war, the Malto family moves to Witwicky, Pennsylvania, to start a new life but their lives soon get entangled with a group of Terran Transformers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130113000 +0800" stop="20251130120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Totally Spies S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">Season 7 takes the Spies on their biggest adventure yet, relocating from Beverly Hills to Singapore, experience a new culture and taking on a fresh crop of bizarre villains!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130120000 +0800" stop="20251130123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Omega</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Malay) There are many universes, they may be similar, but they have their own characteristics, as in the case of Omegaverse. A universe that's similar to the original Ultra universe, but has its own ultras. Omega is a Space Garrison rookie who was sent to Earth on a mission to protect it from monsters that appear mysteriously.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130123000 +0800" stop="20251130124500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">P. King Duckling</title>
    <desc lang="en">P. King Duckling is an animated comedy series that follows the adventures of a friendly but slightly hapless duck P. King and his two best friends, Wombat and Chumpkins, as they find hilarious and creative ways to overcome challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130124500 +0800" stop="20251130130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">P. King Duckling</title>
    <desc lang="en">P. King Duckling is an animated comedy series that follows the adventures of a friendly but slightly hapless duck P. King and his two best friends, Wombat and Chumpkins, as they find hilarious and creative ways to overcome challenges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130000 +0800" stop="20251130150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Dragon Rider</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young silver dragon teams up with a mountain spirit and an orphaned boy on a journey through the Himalayas in search for the Rim of Heaven.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130150000 +0800" stop="20251130153000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130153000 +0800" stop="20251130163000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Bake Off: The Professionals S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Twelve teams from top hotels, restaurants and small businesses compete to be crowned best patisserie team in Britain. Once again, judges Cherish Finden and Benoit Blin set exceedingly tricky challenges, to test the teams' creativity and precision. From towering, skyline-inspired chocolate constructions, to geometric tarts with moving parts, these incredible creations showcase bakers at the peak of their profession.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130163000 +0800" stop="20251130173000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Around the World in 80 Weighs</title>
    <desc lang="en">If current trends continue, a quarter of the world's population will be obese by 2035; it is a global crisis. The six tourists come face-to-face with the horrors of the obesity crisis in different parts of the world and confront the alarming truth of what may await them if they don't tackle their own challenges. At the end of each week, participants are weighed together on a giant scale to see if their hard work trying to lose weight - and the shocking things they have seen - has paid off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130173000 +0800" stop="20251130180000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Planet Action S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Planet Action takes you behind the scenes of the best action movies released. Each episode you'll get all the secrets straight from your favorite action heroes, get exclusive trivia and special reports from the most dangerous film sets, and get insight information on how the filmmakers make giant monsters come to life. This show is a sci-fi, cowboy, world-destruction, action-combo that will literally blow your mind!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130180000 +0800" stop="20251130181000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Just For Laughs Gags S24</title>
    <desc lang="en">Just For Laughs will tickle everyone's funny bone with its hilarious practical jokes, hidden camera pranks, and other creative hijinks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130181000 +0800" stop="20251130203000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Tomb Raider</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lara Croft, the fiercely independent daughter of a missing adventurer, must push herself beyond her limits when she discovers the island where her father, Lord Richard Croft disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130203000 +0800" stop="20251130210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Crimewatch 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">Traffic and Drug Offences: A high-speed chase leads to a joint SPF and CNB operation, exposing a web of drug offences. Watch how the Traffic Police work with the CNB to bring the offenders to justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130210000 +0800" stop="20251130213000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130213000 +0800" stop="20251130223000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Spy In The Ocean</title>
    <desc lang="en">The spy creatures are taking on their most exciting challenge yet, exploring the ocean, one of the most magical and dynamic environments on Earth. A brand-new cast of camera-toting spy creatures take us places no spy camera has ever gone before - from the colour and beauty of coral reefs to the extremes of rocky coasts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130223000 +0800" stop="20251130223000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Where The Crawdads Sing</title>
    <desc lang="en">A woman who raised herself in the marshes of the Deep South becomes a suspect in the murder of a man with whom she was once involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125000000 +0800" stop="20251125010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">阿麦从军</title>
    <desc lang="en">阿麦承袭盛国公爵位，因见商易之改变心灰意冷，不愿再留盛都，打算回青州。商易之吃醋阿麦与唐绍义单独见面，十分不甘。陈起有心趁南夏才经内乱，再次南征，与皇叔申亭渊合力做戏，哄骗小皇帝答应出征。陈起率领大军再临靖阳边关，南夏朝中武将力荐阿麦领军应战。为天下苍生今后免遭战乱，为黎民百姓能够安居乐业，阿麦再披战袍奔赴战场。大战前夕，陈起约见阿麦劝她弃战，阿麦反借机伏击陈起，二人打心理战。不料陈起竟以靖阳城内百姓性命为要挟，试图炸城，阿麦不得已弃陈起而直奔回城，留唐绍义断后。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125010000 +0800" stop="20251125020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">詹姆士出走料理 V</title>
    <desc lang="en">《詹姆士出走料理》以寻找詹姆士私厨菜单为节目主轴，为了寻找记忆中的美味料理，詹姆士将带领大家探索市场，品尝在地美味、寻访料理达人。并在节目中展现特殊食材的处理方式、尝试新的酱料或是新的料理作法，制作创意料理(料理教学)，最后在节目片尾时作出一道『詹姆士创意料理.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125020000 +0800" stop="20251125030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">麻婆斗妇</title>
    <desc lang="en">梁欣为杰奇解决美白霜的问题，条件是要杰奇和她假结婚，让她能获得拘留权。杰奇为此唉声叹气，王度要当杰奇的替死鬼，和梁欣结婚，杰奇知道后拉了梁欣到婚姻注册局注册，等到王度赶到，已经太迟了！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125030000 +0800" stop="20251125040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">麻婆斗妇</title>
    <desc lang="en">建海把饭格放在菲菲家门口后离开，子俊悄悄出现，将麝香放进饭菜里。菲菲的哥哥吃后食物中毒，医生告知食物里有麝香，若给孕妇吃了恐怕会流产。建海感疑惑，想起那天他放了饭格后曾见过子俊出现，怀疑是他干的。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125040000 +0800" stop="20251125050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125050000 +0800" stop="20251129223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129223000 +0800" stop="20251130010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">西游记之女儿国</title>
    <desc lang="en">唐僧师徒途经忘川河，因激怒河神而误入西梁女界。闯入其中，众人才发现这个国家只有女性，并且建国以来此地就没来过男性。而且国有祖训，将男人视为天敌。典籍中更有预言，有朝一日，会有东土而来的僧人带着一只猴子、一头猪和一个小蓝人闯入其中，他们到来之日，便是女儿国走向毁灭之时......。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130010000 +0800" stop="20251130020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">21点灵</title>
    <desc lang="en">谷欣陪天隆拜祭妻子，遇到德刚。天隆见德刚买来妻子生前爱吃的食物拜祭，老怀堪慰。德刚又再冲去厕所，谷欣说出德刚患癌的事，天隆忧心忡忡。谷欣见天隆和德刚其实彼此关心，决定设法化解父子俩的误会。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130020000 +0800" stop="20251130030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">21点灵</title>
    <desc lang="en">德刚怀疑Kai见鬼，向谷欣求助。谷欣通过交谈，知道Kai和一名叫Max的小鬼魂在一起。Max想要回家，却不知自己住在哪里。谷欣和德刚联手调查，终于查到Max的住处。Max的父亲应门，他明显能够见到Max，可是却把众人赶走……。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130030000 +0800" stop="20251130035500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">邻里厨王 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">主持人李国煌和权怡凤将带领大家一起寻找生活在你我周围，爱煮会煮的“邻里厨王”！四位参赛者必须用“指定食材”烹煮一道美食，看谁能成为“邻里厨王”！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130035500 +0800" stop="20251130042000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">极件任务</title>
    <desc lang="en">“世界阿尔巴白松露拍卖会”是意大利一年一度的重要盛事；今年，新加坡将首次参与这个跨国竞标活动。这一集，特派员蔡琦慧将飞到白松露产地，将一批极为珍贵、又极为脆弱的真菌，千里迢迢地带回新加坡，送到拍卖会场地。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130042000 +0800" stop="20251130051000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">3个女人一个宝</title>
    <desc lang="en">演员：郭舒贤饰林慧娴；郭蕙雯饰崔芷青；郑各评饰傅炜铭；戚玉武饰袁仁贤；许美珍饰Katie Ong/王凯蒂；唐育书饰Jovan。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130051000 +0800" stop="20251130060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">3个女人一个宝</title>
    <desc lang="en">演员：郭舒贤饰林慧娴；郭蕙雯饰崔芷青；郑各评饰傅炜铭；戚玉武饰袁仁贤；许美珍饰Katie Ong/王凯蒂；唐育书饰Jovan。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130060000 +0800" stop="20251130065000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">阿嬷来做饭</title>
    <desc lang="en">《阿嬷来做饭》是全新实况趣味的烹饪节目。每集节目将邀请一位阿嬷来做菜、示范拿手料理，并传承她的好厨艺。由主持人钟琴搭配不同的男嘉宾主持人，同步跟着阿嬷一起做菜，过程中观察阿嬷烹调的独特方式与习惯、领受她无价的真传，将阿嬷的家传菜肴发扬光大。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130065000 +0800" stop="20251130072000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130072000 +0800" stop="20251130081000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">长辈甜心</title>
    <desc lang="en">年龄不过是个数字！退休后的于芳（向云饰），秉持着活到老学到老的精神，和一群志同道合的朋友不断挑战新事物。尽管面对年老人生的种种挑战和悲伤，他们仍不放弃，努力创造精彩的乐龄生活。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130081000 +0800" stop="20251130090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">长辈甜心</title>
    <desc lang="en">年龄不过是个数字！退休后的于芳（向云饰），秉持着活到老学到老的精神，和一群志同道合的朋友不断挑战新事物。尽管面对年老人生的种种挑战和悲伤，他们仍不放弃，努力创造精彩的乐龄生活。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130090000 +0800" stop="20251130091500 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/英).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130091500 +0800" stop="20251130093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">Super BOOMi S7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/英).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130093000 +0800" stop="20251130100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">哆啦A梦</title>
    <desc lang="en">在这系列卡通动画里，小朋友们将看到哆啦A梦 - 这只来自未来世界的机器猫，如何应用它的法宝，协助其主人大雄解决生活上的各种难题。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100000 +0800" stop="20251130103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">华文“浆”好玩 S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">究竟是哪位小朋友居然敢顶撞蒋依讲博士， 还告诉她“门儿都没有呢？” 这就是所谓的初生之犊不怕虎吗？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130103000 +0800" stop="20251130110000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">奇趣特工队 S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">凯奇是一个充满好奇心和正义感的男孩，他还有一个神秘的身份：奇趣特工队队长。他和他的伙伴们，调皮骄傲又听得懂外星语的宠物 "闪电猫" 、彬彬有礼、温和待人的管家 "艾尔" 、以及意外流落地球的外星访客 "嘟嘟公主"，组成了守护小镇的奇趣特工队。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130110000 +0800" stop="20251130120000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">星期二特写 ：香料密码</title>
    <desc lang="en">砂拉越原住民 Awin 是一名胡椒农。在农民世家出生就注定难逃成为胡椒农的宿命。她从小抗拒胡椒，长大后却猛然觉悟，唯有胡椒才能带领她与族人脱离贫困。魏忪濠年轻时因车祸毁容，人生一度暗淡。因为爱，他娶妻生子，也因为胡椒，他创业卖肉骨茶，肉骨茶生意让他走 出困境，重获幸福。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130120000 +0800" stop="20251130130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">嫣语赋</title>
    <desc lang="en">讲述了秋府最不受宠的大小姐秋嫣如何凭借自己的努力和智慧从深闺大院中走出来，在一桩桩迷案中抽丝剥茧，在一次次困难中辗转前行，与冷面腹黑王爷梁翊从一路斗智斗勇到相伴相知，最终二人收获了属于他们的幸福和爱情的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130000 +0800" stop="20251130140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">嫣语赋</title>
    <desc lang="en">讲述了秋府最不受宠的大小姐秋嫣如何凭借自己的努力和智慧从深闺大院中走出来，在一桩桩迷案中抽丝剥茧，在一次次困难中辗转前行，与冷面腹黑王爷梁翊从一路斗智斗勇到相伴相知，最终二人收获了属于他们的幸福和爱情的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130140000 +0800" stop="20251130153000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">医点不夸张</title>
    <desc lang="en">《医点不夸张》每集节目会邀请两位知名的专科医师，两位艺人、网红分享对抗病魔的经验。主持人还会用贴近生活的方式，让观众对健康问题更有感，一起长知识！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130153000 +0800" stop="20251130163000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开着餐车趴趴走</title>
    <desc lang="en">前往槟城前，三人在十八丁体验了制炭和造船。在现代和传统交织的槟城，他们体验空中索道，了解豆蔻种植和水粉制作。最重要的是，三人尝遍各具特色的槟城美食。最后，他们以吃法特别的加东叻沙，作为本次的交流美食。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130163000 +0800" stop="20251130173000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">浴水重生</title>
    <desc lang="en">天晴和长峰终于确立恋爱关系，两人打打闹闹又不失甜蜜。严教练宣布天晴、Beatrice、大壮和Ocean将组队参加接力赛，四人的表现却欠缺默契且互相指责。子慧重返职场的首个任务是筹办慈善晚会。有国外舞团临阵缺席，希琳自告奋勇让学生顶上。希琳运用创意让演出完美呈现，众人刮目相看。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130173000 +0800" stop="20251130183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">浴水重生</title>
    <desc lang="en">希琳以慈善晚宴的舞蹈试图说服Sue让她参与来临的公演，无奈还是碰了一鼻子灰。Kay用匿名网友身份鼓励希琳，也提议希琳将跳舞视频放上社交媒体。天晴生日这天，长峰抓住跟踪狂国立，狠狠教训一顿。Summer及时阻止，长峰才知悉这名鬼祟男子竟是天晴的生父，两人甚至有着长达十多年的纠葛。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130183000 +0800" stop="20251130190000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城六点半</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《狮城6点半》每日为您提供最全面的本地新闻头条与报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130190000 +0800" stop="20251130200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">千娜開山貓追靜柔，想讓她流產。聖元和子婷趕到懸崖卻找不到淑君，健司通知他們去醫院看她。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130200000 +0800" stop="20251130210000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">惠珠無意中聽到千娜用死胎陷害靜柔，氣得去找她理論。千娜拿磚頭砸惠珠，把她打下山坡，昏迷不醒。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130210000 +0800" stop="20251130220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">天之骄女</title>
    <desc lang="en">嘉良知道天雷要走私毒品，說服他讓自己一起去碼頭接貨。尚豪偷偷告訴山河時間和地點，沒想到被一龍聽見。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130220000 +0800" stop="20251130223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130223000 +0800" stop="20251130233000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">分家解密</title>
    <desc lang="en">1965年8月9日，李光耀总理在电视戏剧性的落泪画面，成了大家的集体回忆。殊不知，更令人震撼的桥段其实藏在解密档案和私人书信里。新马分家刚尘埃落定，警方竟揭发暗杀李先生的阴谋，外交官则担心马方或“军事占领”新加坡，而英国人为新加坡基地的未来苦恼 — 秘密存放的核武怎么办？高风险的外交斡旋、人性的脆弱，一切尽在节目下集。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125003000 +0800" stop="20251125013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">天伦之情</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 尹松一步步折磨着治焕和世娜，而随着他们的谎言逐渐被揭开，尹松突然的造访让两人感到惊恐不安。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125013000 +0800" stop="20251129233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">天伦之情</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 尚哲因治焕给公司造成的巨大损失而勃然大怒，决定将他驱逐出去。 同时，尹松在世娜家过了一夜，几乎把世娜逼到了崩溃的边缘。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129233000 +0800" stop="20251130003000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">现在开始是Showtime</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 本剧讲述肆意操纵鬼神的魔术师车次雄（朴海镇饰）和具有神通能力的热血女巡警高瑟海（秦基周饰）展开罗曼史，还以偶然卷入的事件中隐 藏的线索为基础，与鬼神合作解决事件。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130003000 +0800" stop="20251130023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">17号音乐仓库 （第三季）</title>
    <desc lang="en">每一本书都有属于它的故事，每一本书的读者也都有属于自已的阅读感受。当我们与一本书相遇的时候，脑海中也许会响起一首专属OST。仓库主理人与仓库好友将在书店开启一场“Book OST”主题Live，他们会带来哪些推荐书单及预期适配的“OST”呢？他们将分享哪些趣事，讲述怎样的过往，延伸出哪些关于人生意义的探讨，唱响关于生活怎样的赞歌？作为“空巢书单”的主理人，“惊喜观众”吴昊宸会分享怎样的人生经历，这场开进书店的Live会碰撞出大家怎样奇妙的化学反应？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130023000 +0800" stop="20251130100000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100000 +0800" stop="20251130113000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">歌手2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">《歌手2024》设立全新的揭榜和袭榜赛制，整体上回归《歌手2018》，赛制为三场一轮，每场均有500位现场大众听审与500位在线大众听审投票，每位听审选择3位自己认为本场表现最佳的歌手。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130113000 +0800" stop="20251130130000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">生活达人S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 本节目为您找出在不同领域有杰出表现的达人。他们可能不起眼、也容易被我们忽略，但他们拥有的技能绝对是无人能及的。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130000 +0800" stop="20251130140000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">飞吧！ 玩客</title>
    <desc lang="en">由人气主持人何美，搭配拥有超强综艺感的「四大男神」-谢佳见、陈谦文、杨奇煜及台日混血男星各务孝太领航，乘着亚洲航空四大航线，深入东南亚三大国家——马来西亚、泰国与菲律宾七大城市，带观众展开一场热情又神秘的冒险旅程，解锁不为人知的秘境与文化魅力！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130140000 +0800" stop="20251130150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">网络陷阱</title>
    <desc lang="en">特洛伊木马表面看似普通的链接或文件，实际上却隐藏着恶意软件，可能使黑客远程控制我们的设备。让我们来关注中国正在发生的相关事件。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130150000 +0800" stop="20251130160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">基督山小姐</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 该剧讲述了一个被信任的朋友逼到死亡的女人下定决心报仇，找回被夺走的人生。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130160000 +0800" stop="20251130170000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">基督山小姐</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 该剧讲述了一个被信任的朋友逼到死亡的女人下定决心报仇，找回被夺走的人生。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130170000 +0800" stop="20251130180000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">你太过分了</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 命运的转折让一位耀眼的明星歌手和她的模仿者的生活交织在一起，经历了爱、恨与怜悯。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130180000 +0800" stop="20251130190000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">你太过分了</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 命运的转折让一位耀眼的明星歌手和她的模仿者的生活交织在一起，经历了爱、恨与怜悯。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130190000 +0800" stop="20251130210000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">亚洲新声</title>
    <desc lang="en">该节目由新声启航人Jessie J、新声召集人张靓颖、新声见证人张信哲、新声护航员尤长靖四位歌手加盟，携手亚洲新声代歌手共同开启跨越文化界限的音乐盛宴.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130210000 +0800" stop="20251130220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">玩火之风</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) Phraphai 是一位熟练的心脏外科医生，她嫁给了电气工程师Din。两人有一个三岁的女儿。自从成为医生和母亲后，繁忙的工作及家庭生活，使Phraphai对爱情提不起兴致。在喝醉的状态下，Din滑倒并与Frame睡在一起。然而，对于Frame来说，这并不是一个错误。她想要更多，她想办法让Din与妻子断绝关系，但Phraphai很聪明。她找出了证据并向Din下了最后通牒，结果一场全面的爱情战争就此拉开序幕。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130220000 +0800" stop="20251130230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">玩火之风</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) Phraphai 是一位熟练的心脏外科医生，她嫁给了电气工程师Din。两人有一个三岁的女儿。自从成为医生和母亲后，繁忙的工作及家庭生活，使Phraphai对爱情提不起兴致。在喝醉的状态下，Din滑倒并与Frame睡在一起。然而，对于Frame来说，这并不是一个错误。她想要更多，她想办法让Din与妻子断绝关系，但Phraphai很聪明。她找出了证据并向Din下了最后通牒，结果一场全面的爱情战争就此拉开序幕。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130230000 +0800" stop="20251130233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130233000 +0800" stop="20251130233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">现在开始是Showtime</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 本剧讲述肆意操纵鬼神的魔术师车次雄（朴海镇饰）和具有神通能力的热血女巡警高瑟海（秦基周饰）展开罗曼史，还以偶然卷入的事件中隐 藏的线索为基础，与鬼神合作解决事件。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129000000 +0800" stop="20251129090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129090000 +0800" stop="20251129093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">X, Y &amp; Zain!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zain pees the bed! Xoey &amp; Yuri are curious as to what had happened seeing he is too old for such incidents! They head over to the bladder, where a surprise awaits them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129093000 +0800" stop="20251129100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sembang Sihat S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Is cholesterol always bad? What's the difference between good and bad cholesterol? How does it affect your heart health? Rahimah Rahim shares her experience, while Iskandar Shah identifies foods with good or bad cholesterol---but is he right?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129100000 +0800" stop="20251129110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Jangan Lupa Janji</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ikmal suspects Mikail's involvement in Mona's death. To Sally's surprise, Mikail tells Datuk Mokhzini that he would like to marry her. Urged by Raihana to marry Mawar, Ikmal steps up as head of the family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129110000 +0800" stop="20251129120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Tuah 13 S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Besties since school, Hidayah, Nuraini and Zubaidah celebrate their friendship by pooling their general knowledge in the pursuit of $13,000. Fun, energetic and vivacious, the girls show that you can dance your way to the end!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129120000 +0800" stop="20251129130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">S.O.S</title>
    <desc lang="en">S.O.S is an action drama revolving around the team members of a lifesaving service that patrols and guards the Sentosa beaches and how they deal with their families, relationships and challenges at work and their personal lives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129130000 +0800" stop="20251129140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">She Was Pretty</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ashraf tries to cast his feelings aside for Nadia to move forward with his life. Haniff pushes himself to the brink of exhaustion, causing concern among everyone on the Most team, especially Nadia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129140000 +0800" stop="20251129150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">She Was Pretty</title>
    <desc lang="en">The editorial team finds out that The Most is at risk of being shut down and that Haniff has been hiding this from them all along.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129150000 +0800" stop="20251129153000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Roller Kata 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">It is a game show that will test wisdom of participants and artists by showing their prowess in answering word quizzes given.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129153000 +0800" stop="20251129160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kanvas Harapan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Imran Wee's life transformed from one of of luxury and drug trafficking to a simple life caring for his mother and helping inmates reintregate into society. His story shows it's never too late to turn your life around and find meaning in helping others. His message "It's your road, and yours alone, others may walk it with you, but no one can walk it for you", a quote from the grand poet Rumi, is one he advocates, for individuals to make the right choices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129160000 +0800" stop="20251129180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Doktor Idaman</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three urban women fall in love with a handsome doctor at Idaman Clinic. The three drive the doctor crazy. But only one managed to steal his heart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129180000 +0800" stop="20251129183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">X, Y &amp; Zain!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zain pees the bed! Xoey &amp; Yuri are curious as to what had happened seeing he is too old for such incidents! They head over to the bladder, where a surprise awaits them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129183000 +0800" stop="20251129190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Geo Park Indonesia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Geopark Indonesia discusses about every Geopark located in Indonesia. It provides full information Including the beautiful scenery from each places, traditional ceremonies, and the local culinary as well. By inviting all audience to love and appreciate natural wealth, the program has nominated as the best travel program by Komisi Penyiaran Indonesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129190000 +0800" stop="20251129200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">The Nuclear Option</title>
    <desc lang="en">From the first reactor to the future of fusion, this episode traces how nuclear energy has evolved and why new designs may shape the future of clean and reliable power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129200000 +0800" stop="20251129203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129203000 +0800" stop="20251129210000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Trek Selebriti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Trek Selebriti is back with more engagin session featuring local celebrities. Joint hosts Keanu Azman and Ariel Azli as they explore the experinces that have shaped the invited celebrities into who they are today.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129210000 +0800" stop="20251129213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ini Baru Rare: Iceland</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iceland, a sub-Arctic country, boasts breathtaking landscapes and natural phenomena that are rarely found elsewhere in the world. Recently, it has gained recognition among global travelers, becoming a paradise for photographers, 4WD drivers, and enthusiasts of cold climates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129213000 +0800" stop="20251129223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Gadis Masa</title>
    <desc lang="en">Maya's effort to save Khairi takes a disastrous turn, setting off a chain of unintended consequences. She now has to go back ten years earlier, when she and Khairi first crossed paths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129223000 +0800" stop="20251129233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Andai Itu Takdirnya</title>
    <desc lang="en">Aizril attacks Lukman after he deliberately provokes him by stating his intentions to marry Aleya. Azreen refuses to give up on Aizril and continues to pursue him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130000000 +0800" stop="20251130090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130090000 +0800" stop="20251130093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">X, Y &amp; Zain!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Xoey &amp; Yuri pay a visit to the pancreas where they find out more about hormone and enzymes and why a well balanced blood sugar level is so important.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130093000 +0800" stop="20251130100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Geo Park Indonesia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Geopark Indonesia discusses about every Geopark located in Indonesia. It provides full information Including the beautiful scenery from each places, traditional ceremonies, and the local culinary as well. By inviting all audience to love and appreciate natural wealth, the program has nominated as the best travel program by Komisi Penyiaran Indonesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100000 +0800" stop="20251130110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">The Nuclear Option</title>
    <desc lang="en">From the first reactor to the future of fusion, this episode traces how nuclear energy has evolved and why new designs may shape the future of clean and reliable power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130110000 +0800" stop="20251130120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sabotaj S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">SABOTAJ is the gameshow where winners and losers try to sabotage each other to win the final prize pot. Returning for its fourth season, from the introduction of live performances to Double the Score Card' and mystery boxes, SABOTAJ returns in its latest season with integration of new concepts and innovative games that would entice viewers and excite them further to play along.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130120000 +0800" stop="20251130123000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Iconic Season 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iconic Season 2 takes you on an enriching journey, diving deeper into the heart of local cultures firmly embedded in the daily lives of communities. Join us as we unveil even more fascinating iconic places and traditions, shedding light on the vibrant tapestry of our world's diverse heritage. Explore the unique stories and experiences that define the essence of these remarkable cultures.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130123000 +0800" stop="20251130130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Makan Viral</title>
    <desc lang="en">Makan Viral is a show where the host will travel to various destinations to test various foods and drinks, while meeting interesting people with interesting stories. The trip itself offers an interesting panoramic view with the opportunity to meet personalities who will share their passion for food and lifestyle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130000 +0800" stop="20251130140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cerita Dia Macam Ni</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cerita Dia Macam Ni delves into the quirky lives of the The Kassims and The Bakars where the untold version of the truth about their friendship and love story gets discovered. Who would've thought the kampung life could be this exciting!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130140000 +0800" stop="20251130150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cerita Dia Macam Ni</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cerita Dia Macam Ni delves into the quirky lives of the The Kassims and The Bakars where the untold version of the truth about their friendship and love story gets discovered. Who would've thought the kampung life could be this exciting!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130150000 +0800" stop="20251130153000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Trek Selebriti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Trek Selebriti is back with more engagin session featuring local celebrities. Joint hosts Keanu Azman and Ariel Azli as they explore the experinces that have shaped the invited celebrities into who they are today.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130153000 +0800" stop="20251130160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ini Baru Rare: Iceland</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iceland, a sub-Arctic country, boasts breathtaking landscapes and natural phenomena that are rarely found elsewhere in the world. Recently, it has gained recognition among global travelers, becoming a paradise for photographers, 4WD drivers, and enthusiasts of cold climates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130160000 +0800" stop="20251130170000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Gadis Masa</title>
    <desc lang="en">Maya's effort to save Khairi takes a disastrous turn, setting off a chain of unintended consequences. She now has to go back ten years earlier, when she and Khairi first crossed paths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130170000 +0800" stop="20251130180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Krisalis</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ben meets his boss who wants to settle some unfinished business. Husin tells Remy to be wary of Ben's next move. As Auni confronts Sara about what happened to Husin, she is kidnapped by Ben's boss. Imran attacks Rina for causing him to lose his Masters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130180000 +0800" stop="20251130183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">X, Y &amp; Zain!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Xoey &amp; Yuri pay a visit to the pancreas where they find out more about hormone and enzymes and why a well balanced blood sugar level is so important.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130183000 +0800" stop="20251130190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Geo Park Indonesia</title>
    <desc lang="en">Geopark Indonesia discusses about every Geopark located in Indonesia. It provides full information Including the beautiful scenery from each places, traditional ceremonies, and the local culinary as well. By inviting all audience to love and appreciate natural wealth, the program has nominated as the best travel program by Komisi Penyiaran Indonesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130190000 +0800" stop="20251130193000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Iconic Season 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iconic Season 2 takes you on an enriching journey, diving deeper into the heart of local cultures firmly embedded in the daily lives of communities. Join us as we unveil even more fascinating iconic places and traditions, shedding light on the vibrant tapestry of our world's diverse heritage. Explore the unique stories and experiences that define the essence of these remarkable cultures.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130193000 +0800" stop="20251130200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Makan Viral</title>
    <desc lang="en">Makan Viral is a show where the host will travel to various destinations to test various foods and drinks, while meeting interesting people with interesting stories. The trip itself offers an interesting panoramic view with the opportunity to meet personalities who will share their passion for food and lifestyle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130200000 +0800" stop="20251130203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130203000 +0800" stop="20251130213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sepahtu Reunion Live S8 ( 2023 )</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jep, Rahim, Pak Ya and Ebby Yus are back to entertain you in the latest season featuring special celebrity guests and unexpected cameos every week. Guest Artist - Elisya Sandha Cameo Appearance - Ruffedge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130213000 +0800" stop="20251130223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Gadis Masa</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now living in 2014 under the alias Maryam, Maya finds herself falling for Khairi all over again. But will she be able to stay focused on her mission to save him?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130223000 +0800" stop="20251130233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Andai Itu Takdirnya</title>
    <desc lang="en">Aleya recalls the past when Aizril mistreats her and remains unforgiving. Aizril assures his family that he will treat them better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251128220000 +0800" stop="20251129010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Badava</title>
    <desc lang="en">A jobless troublemaker is forced to move to Malaysia for work, only to lose his job and return home. The story follows how the hero rises to the challenge, using his courage to free the people and restore joy to the community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129010000 +0800" stop="20251129013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129013000 +0800" stop="20251129090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129090000 +0800" stop="20251129093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Chikoo Aur Bunty</title>
    <desc lang="en">The series showcases the story of two siblings named Chikoo and Bunty, who compete for affection and goodies while avoiding being reprimanded by their parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129093000 +0800" stop="20251129100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Chikoo Aur Bunty</title>
    <desc lang="en">The series showcases the story of two siblings named Chikoo and Bunty, who compete for affection and goodies while avoiding being reprimanded by their parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129100000 +0800" stop="20251129103000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Kaathu Karuppu</title>
    <desc lang="en">2 teenage enemies, KAATHU (Kaathavaraayan) and KARUPPU (Karuppazhagi), are forced to become siblings when their respective single parents decide to tie the knot. The several knots that come about because of their rivalries, in the form of drama, chaos and all things crazy is what this heartwarming and fun series is all about.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129103000 +0800" stop="20251129110000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Kaathu Karuppu</title>
    <desc lang="en">2 teenage enemies, KAATHU (Kaathavaraayan) and KARUPPU (Karuppazhagi), are forced to become siblings when their respective single parents decide to tie the knot. The several knots that come about because of their rivalries, in the form of drama, chaos and all things crazy is what this heartwarming and fun series is all about.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129110000 +0800" stop="20251129113000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Aaruvathu Sinam</title>
    <desc lang="en">Young Sashwin brings his relationship with young Aarthi to the next stage during a campfire. In present day, Agilan and Rakesh meet up to talk about the events that have transpired. Aarav talks to his family lawyer about his grandfather Rajaratnam's passing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129113000 +0800" stop="20251129120000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Aaruvathu Sinam</title>
    <desc lang="en">Aarav meets Pooja to discuss about Rakesh being the suspect in Rajaratnam's murder. Both Aarthi and Sashwin confront Radhika and Rakesh respectively, about their connection. But are they ready to bear the full weight of the truth?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129120000 +0800" stop="20251129130000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rayil Sneham 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join host Vikneswary as she travels to some of the interesting and intriguing destinations along the railway lines in Southeast Asia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129130000 +0800" stop="20251129160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Nalla Neram</title>
    <desc lang="en">Raju, an animal lover, is put in a dilemma when his wife develops a fear of his favourite elephant that had once even saved his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129160000 +0800" stop="20251129183000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Thank God</title>
    <desc lang="en">An egoistic real estate broker in huge debts, meets with an accident.God appears in front of him and informs him that he will have to play a "GAME OF LIFE". If he win, he will be sent back to earth and if not, he will be sent to hell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129183000 +0800" stop="20251129190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129190000 +0800" stop="20251129200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Growing Wild: Project Castaway</title>
    <desc lang="en">When it comes to agriculture, urban farmer Chris Leow is in his comfort zone. But when it comes to aquaculture, he quickly realises that he's a little out of his depth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129200000 +0800" stop="20251129203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with a new season of Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129203000 +0800" stop="20251129210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129210000 +0800" stop="20251129220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">50-50 S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following the breakout success of 50-50 Season 1, which captivated celebrities and audiences alike with its thrilling gameplay, high stakes, and rave reviews, Season 2 promises to elevate the excitement with fresh twists and intensified competition. In this 13-episode series, 12 contestants will battle through two Q&amp;A segments and a physical challenge each week, with the top performer earning immunity and the rest facing elimination based on open votes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251129220000 +0800" stop="20251130003000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Madraskaaran</title>
    <desc lang="en">A minor argument between two strangers escalates into a life-altering conflict, exploring how a seemingly insignificant event can drastically alter a person's perception and circumstances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130003000 +0800" stop="20251130010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130010000 +0800" stop="20251130013000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130013000 +0800" stop="20251130090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130090000 +0800" stop="20251130100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Vinmeen Studios 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Unplugged musical treats by renowned playback singers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100000 +0800" stop="20251130130000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Idhu Nammaalu (1988)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A Brahmin man marries a non-Brahmin woman for love, facing caste-based challenges and familial rejection while standing by his values.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130000 +0800" stop="20251130160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Fakt Mahilao Maate</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chaos ensues in the life of Chintan, a 28-year-old boy, when his innocent wish to be able to understand women gets granted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130160000 +0800" stop="20251130190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Vaseegara (2003)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young educated unemployed youth comes to attend the marriage of his Father's close friend's daughter. He ultimately makes her to fall in love with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130190000 +0800" stop="20251130200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Binge Café with Anu Hasan Season 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Binge Cafe with Anu Hasan is a one-of-a kind chat show featuring popular personalities from cinema, sports, etc. The show will feature our host Anu Hasan taking the celebrities down memory lane and make them re-live their journey, re-count fond memories and also talk about their current work, and upcoming projects, featuring Actress Amala Paul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130200000 +0800" stop="20251130203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Comedy Galatta Season 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to LOL with a new season of Comedy Galatta!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130203000 +0800" stop="20251130210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130210000 +0800" stop="20251130220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Netru Indru Naalai Season 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">This season, we are bringing in 3 Experts as well! Each new episode with a new topic will boast 3 experts who are most experienced in the demographic they are linked to in the show. As the panelists share their views and opinions on each topic, experts can chime in with actual statistics and evidence to either support or oppose the opinions and arguments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130220000 +0800" stop="20251130220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Gentleman</title>
    <desc lang="en">A modern day Robin Hood steals from the rich and gives to the poor. In society, he is a respected man who runs a small business. But, aided by his friend, he is also a notorious robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125000000 +0800" stop="20251125000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125000300 +0800" stop="20251125010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">East Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spotlight on East Asia, a region steeped in history and now helping to write the future of our world. We'll break down the key stories and explain why they matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125010000 +0800" stop="20251125013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125013000 +0800" stop="20251125020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125020000 +0800" stop="20251125030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125030000 +0800" stop="20251125040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">India has joined the AI race. It wants to be an AI Superpower by 2030 and wants to build the technology in an inclusive way. But will high cost and lack of talent become obstacles?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125040000 +0800" stop="20251125050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251125050000 +0800" stop="20251130000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Extraordinary People S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Extraordinary People S2 returns in its familiar format, presenting eight compelling profiles across four episodes. This new season continues to spotlight powerful stories of resilience, hope and community impact, exploring themes such as inclusion, second chance, education, personal health and social connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130000000 +0800" stop="20251130000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130000300 +0800" stop="20251130003000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130003000 +0800" stop="20251130010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130010000 +0800" stop="20251130013000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Masters Of Finance</title>
    <desc lang="en">Famous for his contrarian short during the global financial crisis, legendary trader Stephen Diggle is today a self-professed investor with a strategy built on four idiosyncratic opportunities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130013000 +0800" stop="20251130020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">More Singaporeans are lacing up their running shoes. But as the number of races grows, so do the risks. In our hot and humid climate, what does it really take to prepare for a race in Singapore?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130020000 +0800" stop="20251130023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130023000 +0800" stop="20251130030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130030000 +0800" stop="20251130040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Extraordinary People S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Extraordinary People S2 returns in its familiar format, presenting eight compelling profiles across four episodes. This new season continues to spotlight powerful stories of resilience, hope and community impact, exploring themes such as inclusion, second chance, education, personal health and social connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130040000 +0800" stop="20251130043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130043000 +0800" stop="20251130050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">In Search of Heat S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin learns how to make a Thai curry featuring wild ingredients, travels by boat back in time to experience the origin of royal dishes, and goes head to head with the Nam Prik Queen of Lak Praw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130050000 +0800" stop="20251130060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Growing Wild: Project Castaway</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Singapore adapt to rising sea levels by growing food on water? Can we design and build a floating farm that reimagines what our coastlines will look like? Challenge accepted!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130060000 +0800" stop="20251130063000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130063000 +0800" stop="20251130070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130070000 +0800" stop="20251130073000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130073000 +0800" stop="20251130080000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130080000 +0800" stop="20251130083000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130083000 +0800" stop="20251130090000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">In Search of Heat S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin learns how to make a Thai curry featuring wild ingredients, travels by boat back in time to experience the origin of royal dishes, and goes head to head with the Nam Prik Queen of Lak Praw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130090000 +0800" stop="20251130093000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130093000 +0800" stop="20251130100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">More Singaporeans are lacing up their running shoes. But as the number of races grows, so do the risks. In our hot and humid climate, what does it really take to prepare for a race in Singapore?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100000 +0800" stop="20251130100200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130100200 +0800" stop="20251130110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Growing Wild: Project Castaway</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Singapore adapt to rising sea levels by growing food on water? Can we design and build a floating farm that reimagines what our coastlines will look like? Challenge accepted!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130110000 +0800" stop="20251130113000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130113000 +0800" stop="20251130120000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Masters Of Finance</title>
    <desc lang="en">Famous for his contrarian short during the global financial crisis, legendary trader Stephen Diggle is today a self-professed investor with a strategy built on four idiosyncratic opportunities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130120000 +0800" stop="20251130123000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130123000 +0800" stop="20251130130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130000 +0800" stop="20251130130200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130130200 +0800" stop="20251130140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Japan Hour</title>
    <desc lang="en">A lifestyle program featuring delicious food, culture, hot springs and places of interest in Japan!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130140000 +0800" stop="20251130143000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130143000 +0800" stop="20251130150000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">In Search of Heat S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin learns how to make a Thai curry featuring wild ingredients, travels by boat back in time to experience the origin of royal dishes, and goes head to head with the Nam Prik Queen of Lak Praw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130150000 +0800" stop="20251130153000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130153000 +0800" stop="20251130160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">On The Red Dot</title>
    <desc lang="en">On The Red Dot offers weekly in-depth analysis and discussion on key issues and events that matter to Singaporeans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130160000 +0800" stop="20251130160200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130160200 +0800" stop="20251130170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Extraordinary People S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Extraordinary People S2 returns in its familiar format, presenting eight compelling profiles across four episodes. This new season continues to spotlight powerful stories of resilience, hope and community impact, exploring themes such as inclusion, second chance, education, personal health and social connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130170000 +0800" stop="20251130173000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130173000 +0800" stop="20251130180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Money Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money Mind is all about how to save, how to invest, and how to better spend your money. The show brings you weekly personal finance tips to help you make all the right money moves in Asia. Because, personal finance matters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130180000 +0800" stop="20251130183000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130183000 +0800" stop="20251130190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">More Singaporeans are lacing up their running shoes. But as the number of races grows, so do the risks. In our hot and humid climate, what does it really take to prepare for a race in Singapore?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130190000 +0800" stop="20251130190200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130190200 +0800" stop="20251130193000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Masters Of Finance</title>
    <desc lang="en">Famous for his contrarian short during the global financial crisis, legendary trader Stephen Diggle is today a self-professed investor with a strategy built on four idiosyncratic opportunities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130193000 +0800" stop="20251130200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">CNA Correspondent</title>
    <desc lang="en">They're your eyes and ears around the globe. CNA's network of correspondents shines a light on stories from their corners of the world, from groundbreaking events to up-and-coming trends..</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130200000 +0800" stop="20251130203000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130203000 +0800" stop="20251130210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">In Search of Heat S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">It is all about the sambal. Kevin treks through the lush Perak rainforests to hunt for the next unique sambal, before taking a trip to Isan to learn more about its 3 main flavour components.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130210000 +0800" stop="20251130210200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130210200 +0800" stop="20251130220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Growing Wild: Project Castaway</title>
    <desc lang="en">When it comes to agriculture, urban farmer Chris Leow is in his comfort zone. But when it comes to aquaculture, he quickly realises that he's a little out of his depth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130220000 +0800" stop="20251130223000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130223000 +0800" stop="20251130230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Talking Point</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a fresh approach to tackling the issues of the day, Talking Point investigates a current issue or event, offering different perspectives to local stories and reveals how it all affects you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251130230000 +0800" stop="20251130230300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>