<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V5.2.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Ch 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Ch U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNA">
    <display-name lang="en">CNA</display-name>
    <url>http://www.singteltv.com.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251229001500 +0800" stop="20251229024500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Royal Variety Performance 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The King's first time as Patron of the Royal Variety Charity at the annual Royal Variety Performance. Hosted by Amanda Holden and Alan Carr, with appearances from Elton John, Penn &amp; Teller and BGT winner Sydnie Christmas! Plus, spectacular performances from the London casts of Oliver!, Starlight Express and The Devil Wears Prada.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229024500 +0800" stop="20251229040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Piano - Series 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">The day of the final concert has arrived. The seven amateur pianists prepare to play their hearts out in front of a packed auditorium. Who'll win the Performance of the Night award?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229040000 +0800" stop="20251229050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Catch Phrase S9</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this entertaining series packed with laughs, celebrity contestants attempt to work out catchphrases based on fun animations. Animations include well known phrases, sayings and even film, song and book titles. The celebrities need to buzz in as quickly as they can when they know the answer and can say what they see in a chance to win money for their chosen charities. - Shirley Ballas, Oti Mabuse and Jonathan Ross.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229050000 +0800" stop="20251229060000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">LEGO Masters USA S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">This returning series brings imagination, design and creativity to life when teams of LEGO enthusiasts go head-to-head, with infinite possibilities and anunlimited supply of LEGO bricks. Teams of two will compete against each other in ambitious brick-building challenges to be crowned the country's most talented amateur LEGO builders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229060000 +0800" stop="20251229063000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supa Strikas</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Malay) Follow Shakes, Rasta and the rest of the Supa Strikas on their quest to become the world's greatest football team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229063000 +0800" stop="20251229070000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229070000 +0800" stop="20251229073000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Gigantosaurus S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rocky, Bill, Tiny and Mazu are four young dinosaurs growing up in the Cretaceous period. Life is always an adventure: new volcanoes are popping up all the time, long-necked brachiosauruses and enormous triceratopses roam free, meteor showers light up the night sky and... the fierce Gigantosaurus reigns over it all!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229073000 +0800" stop="20251229080000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Blippi 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Blippi's enthusiastic and expressive character engages children on their level through relatable adventures while sharing their excitement in discovering the world around us. Blippi is so entertaining, engaging and fun, kids don't even realize they're learning!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229080000 +0800" stop="20251229083000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ollie &amp; Friends S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dash and Paw are having fun playing as knights and dragons. Together with Ollie, they go on an adventure to learn more about what is scary-looking on the outside may not be so on the inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229083000 +0800" stop="20251229090000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pinkfong Songs &amp; Stories</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enjoy the best of Pinkfong's most loved songs and stories with all your favourite characters!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229090000 +0800" stop="20251229093000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Sesame Street Mecha Builders</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elmo, Cookie Monster, and Abby Cadabby are robot heroes-in-training who use their STEM superpowers to solve wacky larger-than-life problems!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229093000 +0800" stop="20251229093700 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Yakka Dee: Sr5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Return of the entertaining and inspiring series, with appealing animated character Dee revealing a whole new set of words. In each episode Dee sets off on a whirlwind word adventure. As she shows various visualisations of how the word's used, there are special surprises along the way - and everyone has a boogie when Dee's friend succeeds in saying the episode's featured word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229093700 +0800" stop="20251229094500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Yakka Dee: Sr5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Return of the entertaining and inspiring series, with appealing animated character Dee revealing a whole new set of words. In each episode Dee sets off on a whirlwind word adventure. As she shows various visualisations of how the word's used, there are special surprises along the way - and everyone has a boogie when Dee's friend succeeds in saying the episode's featured word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229094500 +0800" stop="20251229095200 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Yakka Dee: Sr5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Return of the entertaining and inspiring series, with appealing animated character Dee revealing a whole new set of words. In each episode Dee sets off on a whirlwind word adventure. As she shows various visualisations of how the word's used, there are special surprises along the way - and everyone has a boogie when Dee's friend succeeds in saying the episode's featured word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229095200 +0800" stop="20251229100000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Yakka Dee: Sr5</title>
    <desc lang="en">Return of the entertaining and inspiring series, with appealing animated character Dee revealing a whole new set of words. In each episode Dee sets off on a whirlwind word adventure. As she shows various visualisations of how the word's used, there are special surprises along the way - and everyone has a boogie when Dee's friend succeeds in saying the episode's featured word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229100000 +0800" stop="20251229103000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Ollie And Friends S8</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Imp has had enough, this time he's done his homework and plotted his best ever plan yet! He succeeds in stealing Sloppy's power tool belt! But now that he's got it, he doesn't know what to do with it. While the team tries to get their tool back, the Imp is almost kidnapped by a dastardly bounty hunter. Poly-GON!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229103000 +0800" stop="20251229110000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Tangranimals</title>
    <desc lang="en">Young Geo explores Tangra-planet, an amazing place with geometrical landscapes, along with his friends the Tangranimals . These amusing creatures can link together like Tangram pieces, and thus create all sorts of vehicles, creatures and objects. With that power, plus a good measure of imagination, Geo and his friends are ready to meet any challenge!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229110000 +0800" stop="20251229113000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Gigantosaurus S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rocky, Bill, Tiny and Mazu are four young dinosaurs growing up in the Cretaceous period. Life is always an adventure: new volcanoes are popping up all the time, long-necked brachiosauruses and enormous triceratopses roam free, meteor showers light up the night sky and... the fierce Gigantosaurus reigns over it all!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229113000 +0800" stop="20251229114500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Turbozaurs S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Turbozaurs are a dynamic team of friendly dinosaurs which can transform themselves instantly into amazing machines. They are discovered in the woods by three children, and together form a special rescue team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229114500 +0800" stop="20251229120000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Turbozaurs S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Turbozaurs are a dynamic team of friendly dinosaurs which can transform themselves instantly into amazing machines. They are discovered in the woods by three children, and together form a special rescue team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229120000 +0800" stop="20251229123000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Supa Strikas</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Malay) Follow Shakes, Rasta and the rest of the Supa Strikas on their quest to become the world's greatest football team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229123000 +0800" stop="20251229130000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Slugterra S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Slugterra is an epic sci-fi comedy adventure set deep underground, where the ammo's alive and only the quick survive! In this luminous, high-tech, underground world every cavern holds a new adventure, new battle and weird little slugs to be discovered!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229130000 +0800" stop="20251229133000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Miniforce X [S2]</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Dual language English and Mandarin) The Miniforce fight against Villains threatening the Earth! Our heroes Volt, Max, Sammy and Lucy come back with upgraded X-power!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229133000 +0800" stop="20251229134500 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Open Season: Call of Nature</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Boog and Elliot discover an abandoned Summer Camp in the middle of nowhere, they embark on a brave new adventure of creating a safe and special place to live that welcomes animals of every kind. Under the leadership of Boog and Elliot, the Campers must all work together to help create their own slice of paradise in the middle of the wilderness and to rediscover their inner wild.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229134500 +0800" stop="20251229140000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Open Season: Call of Nature</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Boog and Elliot discover an abandoned Summer Camp in the middle of nowhere, they embark on a brave new adventure of creating a safe and special place to live that welcomes animals of every kind. Under the leadership of Boog and Elliot, the Campers must all work together to help create their own slice of paradise in the middle of the wilderness and to rediscover their inner wild.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229140000 +0800" stop="20251229143000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">PJ Masks S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Instead of going to bed like all the other children, when our heroes get their pyjamas on, they magically transform into super heroes and become the PJ Masks!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229143000 +0800" stop="20251229150000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Pokemon Master Journeys: The Series (S24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join the continuing research fellowship adventures of Alola Champion Ash Ketchum and Goh, as they travel across all eight regions, including the new Galar region and Crown Tundra, based at Cerise Laboratory in Vermillion City in the Kanto region.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229150000 +0800" stop="20251229153000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Films &amp; Stars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Films and Stars cover the hottest events from the big screen every week.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229153000 +0800" stop="20251229160000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">FAM</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chef extraordinaire and everyone's dream husband, Gorden, has always had a huge following of fans and he has always loved the attention. Hence, when he gets his very own stalker, sending him flowers and gifts, he's thrilled. Sammi is tasked by Joy to find out more about who this stalker might be. After a few near misses, they finally discover the identity of the stalker but Gorden is in for a rude awakening. Jayden decides to take up a new profession that will boost his image.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160000 +0800" stop="20251229163000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Crimewatch 2025</title>
    <desc lang="en">Theft Onboard Aircraft: When S$120,000 in cash belonging to a passenger disappears in mid flight, the Police launch an investigation, looking at travel timelines, casino transactions and remittance trails. Every piece of evidence matters! Watch how the Airport Police Division's detailed, well-coordinated investigations lead to a swift arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229163000 +0800" stop="20251229173000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Jamie &amp; Jimmy's Festive Feast</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jamie's Festive Feast is a celebration of those lazy winter days at the end of the year. The festive period is the perfect time to kick back, spend some quality time with family and friends, and cook up some amazing dishes. Filmed at his Essex home, Jamie takes a walk through his perfect winter winddown foods, including some stress-free, big-hitting winter warmers, such as Oozy cheesy pasta, and simple one-pot wonders, such as Bloody Mary beef.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229173000 +0800" stop="20251229180000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Donal Skehan: Home Cook</title>
    <desc lang="en">Master builder and household favourite Tommy Walsh, expert pro cleaner Maxine nspired by his sunny days living in Los Angeles, treasured family memories, and his love of good food, Donal brings a collection of his favourite fondest recipes, adapted using no-fuss techniques, designed with the home cook in mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229180000 +0800" stop="20251229190000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 03</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229190000 +0800" stop="20251229193000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229193000 +0800" stop="20251229203000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo USA S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this game show, hosted by the iconic RuPaul, the simplest of words could be worth thousands of dollars. Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229203000 +0800" stop="20251229210000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Streets, Hong Kong</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over this eight-part series, renowned chef, Dan Hong will explore every corner of Hong Kong, learning about its history and culture and how this has shaped the local food scene. Determined to hunt down the most authentic fare, Dan will scour the streets, markets and hawker halls to meet the vendors and find out how these traditional dishes are made and served to hordes of hungry customers every day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229210000 +0800" stop="20251229213000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The daily evening-news programme featuring highlights and coverage of both local and international news with a local perspective.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229213000 +0800" stop="20251229220000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Seoul At Home</title>
    <desc lang="en">Michelin star chef Alvin Leung and Korean Celebrity chef Matthew Chung will be visiting different home and restaurants in Korea, in search of home made traditional foods and uncovering recipes that has passed through generations. Their goal is to recreate these traditional dishes, in a modern new way with their own special touches.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229220000 +0800" stop="20251229230000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Elsbeth S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Astute but unconventional attorney Elsbeth Tascioni utilizes her singular point of view to make unique observations and corner brilliant criminals alongside the NYPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229230000 +0800" stop="20251230000000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Transplant S4</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the climactic season, we will see Bash and Mags embarking on a rescue mission, in a remote woodland, setting the stage for the medical and personal challenges that will test the characters throughout the season.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230000000 +0800" stop="20251230003000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">The Streets, Hong Kong</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over this eight-part series, renowned chef, Dan Hong will explore every corner of Hong Kong, learning about its history and culture and how this has shaped the local food scene. Determined to hunt down the most authentic fare, Dan will scour the streets, markets and hawker halls to meet the vendors and find out how these traditional dishes are made and served to hordes of hungry customers every day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230003000 +0800" stop="20251230013000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Cobra: Rebellion S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following the sinkhole collapse, Sutherland and his wife Rachel travel to Godley Common to find their daughter Ellie. Multiple deaths are reported as rescuers work around the clock to retrieve victims just as news breaks that Shirasian Princess Yadira has been kidnapped and forced back to Shirasia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230013000 +0800" stop="20251230020000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Wheel Of Fortune S42</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan Seacrest takes over as the new host for the well-loved gameshow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230020000 +0800" stop="20251230030000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Lingo USA S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this game show, hosted by the iconic RuPaul, the simplest of words could be worth thousands of dollars. Lingo is the fast paced word-play game that keeps on innovating for new audiences, with its mix of skill, tension, humour and the chance to win big cash prizes. Teams are pitted against each other in a battle to fill in the blanks and find words.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230030000 +0800" stop="20251230040000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Wheel of Fortune: Season 03</title>
    <desc lang="en">Various celebrities compete against each other by solving word puzzles in order to win cash prizes that are determined by a spinning wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230040000 +0800" stop="20251230043000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Euromaxx</title>
    <desc lang="en">Everything you've ever wanted to know about Europe - from traditions and habits to culture shocks and record breakers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230043000 +0800" stop="20251230050000 +0800" channel="Ch 5">
    <title lang="en">Donal Skehan: Home Cook</title>
    <desc lang="en">Master builder and household favourite Tommy Walsh, expert pro cleaner Maxine nspired by his sunny days living in Los Angeles, treasured family memories, and his love of good food, Donal brings a collection of his favourite fondest recipes, adapted using no-fuss techniques, designed with the home cook in mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229000000 +0800" stop="20251229010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">最火搭档2</title>
    <desc lang="en">小曼逮捕婕妤，怀疑她和一连串的凶杀案有关。婕妤否认，并认为小曼就像当年对付荣格一样，没有弄清事实就冤枉她。小曼说当初荣格的确诱使嫌凶杀人，犯下了连环凶杀案，荣格并不是无辜的。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229010000 +0800" stop="20251229020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">最火搭档2</title>
    <desc lang="en">(大结局)小曼哀恸不已，要杀婕妤，但最后还是决定让她接受法律的制裁，同时小曼还得知一个惊人的事实！当朗峰来到现场时，却不见小曼，到底她去了哪里？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229020000 +0800" stop="20251229030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">微笑正义</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着一群对揭发事实真相极具热忱的新闻工作者，从中带出新闻背后不为人知的秘密。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229030000 +0800" stop="20251229040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">微笑正义</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着一群对揭发事实真相极具热忱的新闻工作者，从中带出新闻背后不为人知的秘密。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229040000 +0800" stop="20251229050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">查某人</title>
    <desc lang="en">在一个坠楼女子的丧礼上，三个家庭主妇相识了―戴秀梅 (庄米雪) 是热心的前女警；云飞雪 (许美珍) 是典型的 Auntie；邱双喜 (洪乙心) 在家兼职卖美容品。三人发现女子的死存有疑点，联手侦查后发现凶手是死者的丈夫。秀梅和飞雪成立侦探社。飞雪对帅哥高翔 (张振寰) 存有幻想，双喜则对高翔印象不佳。秀梅和飞雪洗脱双喜虐待女佣罪名，双喜加入侦探社。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229050000 +0800" stop="20251229060000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">查某人</title>
    <desc lang="en">在一个坠楼女子的丧礼上，三个家庭主妇相识了―戴秀梅 (庄米雪) 是热心的前女警；云飞雪 (许美珍) 是典型的 Auntie；邱双喜 (洪乙心) 在家兼职卖美容品。三人发现女子的死存有疑点，联手侦查后发现凶手是死者的丈夫。秀梅和飞雪成立侦探社。飞雪对帅哥高翔 (张振寰) 存有幻想，双喜则对高翔印象不佳。秀梅和飞雪洗脱双喜虐待女佣罪名，双喜加入侦探社。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229060000 +0800" stop="20251229070000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">特别的食物给特别的你</title>
    <desc lang="en">台北非营利组织《人生百味》每月举办一次《石头汤计划》，向市场摊贩募集食材，集结志工一起做饭，发送给台北车站的街友。杨君伟参与了《石头汤计划》为街友们派送便当，也深入了解街友们在街头的困境和难处。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229070000 +0800" stop="20251229073000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229073000 +0800" stop="20251229080000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">7天我可以</title>
    <desc lang="en">要在7天内学会一门运动到底有可能吗？《7天我可以！》系列中，新闻主播们拜访本地运动健儿，挑战在一周内突破自己的体能极限，完成运动员们设下的挑战！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229080000 +0800" stop="20251229090000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">没马跑 (中文版）</title>
    <desc lang="en">Money 气马赢撒谎又不顾汤店，马赢委屈解释自己曾经努力过，但一无所获，Money 同情。马赢行径古怪，大宝提议带他去看心理医生，被 Money 骂了一顿，但过后顾客欲栽赃陷害汤里有蟑螂，被大宝识破，Money 又对她有改观。老马去下棋，却与王禄起争执，众人大打出手之际，大宝突然出现，救走老马。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229090000 +0800" stop="20251229093000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城热话</title>
    <desc lang="en">周一至周五晚上7点，《狮城有约》谈话性栏目《狮城热话》以汇集多元声音及专家看法为目标，通过网络投票和引导观点碰撞，打造能让观众参与的时事舆论场。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229093000 +0800" stop="20251229100000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">但愿人长久</title>
    <desc lang="en">邓枢住院期间和邓丽君谈心，希望她能勇敢唱下去，勇敢去爱。马可发现志明盗卖的卡带封面是邓丽君，询问后才得知她是大歌星。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229100000 +0800" stop="20251229103000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">焦点</title>
    <desc lang="en">《焦点》追踪国际时事，实地报道区域课题，以新加坡的视角分析时局发展的前因后果和潜在影响。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229103000 +0800" stop="20251229113000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">甘味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">甘味人生，是一出阐述「一家人世代传承家业」的励志写实戏剧。剧中赵家是制作传统手工酱油的一个大家庭，家庭的父母兄弟姊妹，共同为这个家努力打拼的历程为主轴，描写刻画每个人在打拼的过程当中，与纠结在矛盾的感情世界里，所经历的悲欢喜乐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229113000 +0800" stop="20251229130000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">甘味人生</title>
    <desc lang="en">甘味人生，是一出阐述「一家人世代传承家业」的励志写实戏剧。剧中赵家是制作传统手工酱油的一个大家庭，家庭的父母兄弟姊妹，共同为这个家努力打拼的历程为主轴，描写刻画每个人在打拼的过程当中，与纠结在矛盾的感情世界里，所经历的悲欢喜乐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229130000 +0800" stop="20251229133000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">一点新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《一点新闻》为您提供更新的本地与全球新闻头条。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229133000 +0800" stop="20251229140000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着洪氏和龙氏家族、他们的工作生活和朋友展开，在之前的剧集中，龙景峰的幽灵与洪氏家族成员结下了深厚的友谊。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229140000 +0800" stop="20251229143000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着洪氏和龙氏家族、他们的工作生活和朋友展开，在之前的剧集中，龙景峰的幽灵与洪氏家族成员结下了深厚的友谊。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229143000 +0800" stop="20251229153000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">开心速递</title>
    <desc lang="en">故事围绕着洪氏和龙氏家族、他们的工作生活和朋友展开，在之前的剧集中，龙景峰的幽灵与洪氏家族成员结下了深厚的友谊。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229153000 +0800" stop="20251229160000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">回归</title>
    <desc lang="en">区耀祖和邓丽娟离婚后，各自在两地经营粤德居，多年来相安无事，直至香港特区回归廿五周年，丽娟决定回港开设分店，更为争夺粤德居品牌，不惜与耀祖对簿公堂。幼子家健参加大湾区创业比赛，遇上担任导师的兄长家谦。兄弟长期分隔两地，南辕北辙，难免磨擦，但血浓于水，加深彼此认识后，重建深厚亲情，携手研发出高科技虚拟技术，让父母重新经历廿五年来的起起跌跌，明白原来一直关心对方，二人冰释前嫌，一家四口终得以团聚.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160000 +0800" stop="20251229163000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">回归</title>
    <desc lang="en">区耀祖和邓丽娟离婚后，各自在两地经营粤德居，多年来相安无事，直至香港特区回归廿五周年，丽娟决定回港开设分店，更为争夺粤德居品牌，不惜与耀祖对簿公堂。幼子家健参加大湾区创业比赛，遇上担任导师的兄长家谦。兄弟长期分隔两地，南辕北辙，难免磨擦，但血浓于水，加深彼此认识后，重建深厚亲情，携手研发出高科技虚拟技术，让父母重新经历廿五年来的起起跌跌，明白原来一直关心对方，二人冰释前嫌，一家四口终得以团聚.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229163000 +0800" stop="20251229173000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229173000 +0800" stop="20251229183000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229183000 +0800" stop="20251229193000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">狮城有约</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 总结一天大小事，关心属于你我的家园。每逢星期一至五，傍晚6.30-7.30pm，与你相约！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229193000 +0800" stop="20251229200000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">但愿人长久</title>
    <desc lang="en">邓丽君在日本做一场名为“唯一”的演唱会，她希望在演唱会穿上白纱。汪仲文来找邓丽君，他担心他们之间的事会阻碍她现在的选择，邓丽君却说她的真爱只是唱歌。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229200000 +0800" stop="20251229210000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">新传媒 LOVE972《新白蛇传》音乐剧</title>
    <desc lang="en">这个十月，一段千古传说，将燃起全新烈火。 你以为你熟悉《白蛇传》？ 白素贞、小青、许仙、法海——他们当然都在。 但这一次，他们的故事，不止步于西湖断桥。 而是踏入命运交错的深渊，揭开前所未见的真相。 全新人物登场，搅动风云： 一位根植百年的森林姥姥， 一名情深似海却命运曲折的书生宁采臣， 还有一位困于情与命运之间的神秘女鬼…… 当旧神话被重新改写， 爱与恨、忠与叛、天命与选择，如潮涌般交织上演。 一首首熟悉的中文金曲，穿梭于剧情之间被重新点燃； 多媒体视觉与编舞创意齐飞，情节紧凑，动静皆震撼； 972电台全体DJ齐聚舞台， 你熟悉的声音，将化身传奇角色； 更有特别嘉宾倾情加盟，为这段宿命之战添上意想不到的火花； 剧本由周崇庆亲自执笔，情感深刻，笑中带泪。 这不是你以为的《白蛇传》， 而是一场跨越千年的音乐重生。 2025年10月 · 隆重登场 人在江湖，情归何处—— 听一段旧传说，见一次新命运。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229210000 +0800" stop="20251229220000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">没马跑 (中文版）</title>
    <desc lang="en">大宝缠着老马要学煮汤，老马反开条件要她帮马赢建立煮汤的自信。大宝安排一出戏剌激马赢，果然有效，老马只好履行诺言。珍珠纠缠马仲，马仲找小宝来当他的挡箭牌，小宝却被珍珠羞辱委屈离去。大宝跟马赢上酒店，Money 赶去抓奸，却发现打错人。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229220000 +0800" stop="20251229223000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">(现场直播) 《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229223000 +0800" stop="20251229230000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">中东密探</title>
    <desc lang="en">在吉达的最后一天，搜集各式各样的世界之最。不只是前往沙乌地阿拉伯最大、世界第40名最繁忙的吉达港，远眺预计成为世界最高的吉达塔，也看到世界最高的旗竿跟喷泉。品尝完中东必吃的沙威玛之后，在令人意想不到的沙乌地阿拉伯夜间游乐园，体验疯狂又有趣的道地夜生活。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229230000 +0800" stop="20251230000000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">长相思第二季</title>
    <desc lang="en">玱玹挺过五叔和七叔的打压与暗算，成功接下西炎国的王位。小夭为了帮助玱玹的大业，打算倚仗中原氏族的团结助玱玹一臂之力，与赤水丰隆达成联姻的约定，而涂山璟以三十七年粮草收买防风邶在大婚典礼上当众抢婚，但防风邶也付出代价必须以死谢罪，从此相柳失去防风邶这个身份。尽管如此，青丘族长涂山璟与九头蛇妖相柳仍默默守护着小夭。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230000000 +0800" stop="20251230010000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">斗罗大陆之燃魂战</title>
    <desc lang="en">全大陆高级魂师学院精英赛决赛结束，唐三跟小伙伴们恋恋不舍地分别，约定五年后重逢，便各自奔赴前程。而后，唐三随父亲唐昊去往隐秘山谷特训，提升自身能力。得益于唐昊的协助，唐三在积累经验的过程中变得更加沉稳，能从容应对更多挑战。戴沐白和朱竹清获得家族的肯定，分别成为星罗太子和准太子妃。奥斯卡和宁荣荣为提升实力开启艰苦训练，马红俊也外出游历以增长见识。就在此时，武魂殿的比比东暗中筹谋，横扫多个宗门，企图称霸斗罗大陆。于是，唐三召集伙伴创立唐门，坚守正义，勇挑重担。他们合力勇闯海神岛，与武魂殿对抗，不惧黑暗与强权，共同守护大陆和平，成长为坚毅的战士。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230010000 +0800" stop="20251230020000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">食尚玩家 S13</title>
    <desc lang="en">在新一辑的“食尚玩家 - 2 天1夜GO"里，主持人纳豆，六月，曾子余等会带领观众周游许多耳目一新的地方，国家包括韩国，日本（长崎，福冈），越南等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230020000 +0800" stop="20251230030000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">《咖啡乌》是一部具有浓厚新加坡特色的当代剧，围绕住在组屋区的中低收入家庭与小贩的生活展开，描绘了他们的喜怒哀乐与人生追求。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230030000 +0800" stop="20251230040000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">咖啡乌</title>
    <desc lang="en">《咖啡乌》是一部具有浓厚新加坡特色的当代剧，围绕住在组屋区的中低收入家庭与小贩的生活展开，描绘了他们的喜怒哀乐与人生追求。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230040000 +0800" stop="20251230050000 +0800" channel="Ch 8">
    <title lang="en">多情城市</title>
    <desc lang="en">本剧以1960年代至1970年代的九份地区为背景，述说三个拜把兄弟如何赤手空拳打天下，藉由上一代的爱情故事串连与第二代之间共同的情感与记忆，深度探索两代之间的价值观差异。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229003000 +0800" stop="20251229020000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">亚洲新声</title>
    <desc lang="en">该节目由新声启航人Jessie J、新声召集人张靓颖、新声见证人张信哲、新声护航员尤长靖四位歌手加盟，携手亚洲新声代歌手共同开启跨越文化界限的音乐盛宴.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229020000 +0800" stop="20251229023000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">逛遍全中国</title>
    <desc lang="en">旅行体验师将去到贵州、广西 、广东 三个省份的宝藏景区，品尝当地特色美食，领略当地的好山好水，感受当地深厚人文历史和奇特风味。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229023000 +0800" stop="20251229143000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229143000 +0800" stop="20251229150000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">收场</title>
    <desc lang="en">收场.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229150000 +0800" stop="20251229160000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">熊猫一家人</title>
    <desc lang="en">实习生见证熊猫带娃开启野培，贤贤霸气护崽惹马晓钰激动爆哭。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160000 +0800" stop="20251229170000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">求学地图</title>
    <desc lang="en">本地少有以留学指南为主轴的资讯节目。节目以最为轻松的方式，让主持人重拾书包跟着本地留学生上学去，了解各国的教育制度、教育文化、就业市场。节目旨在给予本地家长和年轻人一个参考。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229170000 +0800" stop="20251229180000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">第二任丈夫</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 此剧讲述因无法停止的欲望酿成的悲剧，令一个女人无辜地失去家人，她在错综复杂的命运和爱情中展开复仇的故事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229180000 +0800" stop="20251229190000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">婚姻战争</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/泰) 佳明的律师一直盘问宝儿，她受不了说出她住在瓦善普里府时的不好经历。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229190000 +0800" stop="20251229200000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 汉杰想跟荷妮服饰的代表开会，却没想到代表竟是荷妮，汉杰立刻提出终止合作。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229200000 +0800" stop="20251229210000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 为了小菜，东锡和岳母又起了口角，善熙因为妈妈的偏心又和母亲吵架，女儿智恩忍不住说了重话让善熙很伤心。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229210000 +0800" stop="20251229220000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">全民星攻略</title>
    <desc lang="en">无论是厨房里的烦恼、家务中的小窍门、生活中的不方便，各种生活的疑难杂症，或许你都能在节目中找到解决方法——洗毛巾时加入柔软精会使毛巾「不易产生棉絮」还是「降低吸水性」？ 豆腐在烹煮过程中容易破碎，在煮之前「先泡盐水」还是「放冷冻至少一个小时」就可以避免？女生骑档车时头发若太长，应「绑一包塞入安全帽」还是「绑马尾塞外套中」比较安全？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229220000 +0800" stop="20251229230000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">金秘书为何那样</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 英俊不想心安理得让微笑照顾，就自己去打印文件, 郑部长误以为英俊要解散秘书室了.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229230000 +0800" stop="20251229233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻</title>
    <desc lang="en">《晚间新闻》每日为您提供最全面的本地与全球新闻报道。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229233000 +0800" stop="20251229233000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">全民星攻略</title>
    <desc lang="en">无论是厨房里的烦恼、家务中的小窍门、生活中的不方便，各种生活的疑难杂症，或许你都能在节目中找到解决方法——洗毛巾时加入柔软精会使毛巾「不易产生棉絮」还是「降低吸水性」？ 豆腐在烹煮过程中容易破碎，在煮之前「先泡盐水」还是「放冷冻至少一个小时」就可以避免？女生骑档车时头发若太长，应「绑一包塞入安全帽」还是「绑马尾塞外套中」比较安全？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229233000 +0800" stop="20251230003000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">全民星攻略</title>
    <desc lang="en">无论是厨房里的烦恼、家务中的小窍门、生活中的不方便，各种生活的疑难杂症，或许你都能在节目中找到解决方法——洗毛巾时加入柔软精会使毛巾「不易产生棉絮」还是「降低吸水性」？ 豆腐在烹煮过程中容易破碎，在煮之前「先泡盐水」还是「放冷冻至少一个小时」就可以避免？女生骑档车时头发若太长，应「绑一包塞入安全帽」还是「绑马尾塞外套中」比较安全？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230003000 +0800" stop="20251230013000 +0800" channel="Ch U">
    <title lang="en">明日也晴朗</title>
    <desc lang="en">(双声道 - 中/韩) 汉杰想跟荷妮服饰的代表开会，却没想到代表竟是荷妮，汉杰立刻提出终止合作。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229000000 +0800" stop="20251229090000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229090000 +0800" stop="20251229093000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Arc</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story is about Arc protecting the future of the Earth and mankind from looming threats. Yuma transforms into Ultraman Arc by inserting the Arc Cube, which contains the power of the being of light, into the mystic Arc Ariser and unleashing his power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229093000 +0800" stop="20251229100000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">SQFT</title>
    <desc lang="en">An informative and entertaining program that aims to show the uniqueness of the versatile small house and the minimalist life. This unique tv program also shares creativity with the use of small and limited space is unlimited. Viewers will also be taken to a new Tiny house construction project from start to finish over the course of 13 episodes in SQFT's Buiuld Info segment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229100000 +0800" stop="20251229110000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Azam &amp; Johan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Azam &amp; Johan aspire to be professional footballers. An accident renders Azam paralyzed, dashing his football dream. Their mother blames Johan for the accident. Azam feels his world has ended. Wrecked with guilt, Johan wants to give up football but his father stops him. Will the family be torn apart forever by the tragedy or overcome to find happiness again?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229110000 +0800" stop="20251229120000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Kerasnya Takdir</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jiha is uncertain about how to regain her losses and is worried about the financial security of her family. Mastura takes satisfaction from Munir and his family's pain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229120000 +0800" stop="20251229130000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">S.P.Y. S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">The case gets more intricate as it unfolds when the principal becomes a prime suspect. Maria continues to visit Azrul in secret as she tries to find a lawyer to help with his case. The divide between the team is apparent as Yusuf clashes with Natasha during their investigation. A discovery leads the team to the killer as they uncover another crime behind the motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229130000 +0800" stop="20251229140000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Aku Seorang Perempuan</title>
    <desc lang="en">After the tragic accident that kills his wife and daughter, Ehsan decides to leave the country to find peace. Meanwhile, there's trouble ahead for Siti Noraisya and Fareez's seemingly blissful married life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229140000 +0800" stop="20251229150000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sayap Cinta Terindah</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dhani takes on the responsibility of caring for his younger siblings - Ariel, David and Isyana - navigating the challlenges of their intertwined lives. As their journey unfolds, each sibling harbors hidden secrets waiting to be uncovered. Will Dhani uncover the truths they're keeping from him?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229150000 +0800" stop="20251229160000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Sepahtu Reunion Live S8 ( 2023 )</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jep, Rahim, Pak Ya and Ebby Yus are back to entertain you in the latest season featuring special celebrity guests and unexpected cameos every week. Guest Artist - Elly Mazlein Cameo Apperarance - Sham Visa and Rosnah Mat Aris.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160000 +0800" stop="20251229170000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Once Upon Our Love</title>
    <desc lang="en">Akira and Haris brace themselves for a meetup with their mysterious online sweethearts. They seek help from Farah and Ikhwan respectively for support and backup.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229170000 +0800" stop="20251229180000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Cinta Tiada Ganti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Riz pleads with Ara to bring him to meet Eliza. Eliza reunites with Riz as he apologizes to her for all that he has done.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229180000 +0800" stop="20251229183000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Arc</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story is about Arc protecting the future of the Earth and mankind from looming threats. Yuma transforms into Ultraman Arc by inserting the Arc Cube, which contains the power of the being of light, into the mystic Arc Ariser and unleashing his power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229183000 +0800" stop="20251229190000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Janji Sedap</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join our chef as he takes you to a culinary journey and learn how to whip up vibrant and flavoursome cuisine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229190000 +0800" stop="20251229200000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Bukan Sekadar Lafaz 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Syikin grows more jealous of Aira as she works on winning Hud's case against the claimant. Zaman rekindles his relationship with his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229200000 +0800" stop="20251229203000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229203000 +0800" stop="20251229213000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Manja S10</title>
    <desc lang="en">Manja Season 10 is back with a new vibe—bolder, brighter, and packed with everything you love! Join Zhin, Natasha, Shenty, and Iskandar for flavorful food trips, real talk, and fun adventures throughout Singapore. Also, a new segment, BOLEH IKUT, with interesting profiles, peeking behind the scenes of unique jobs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229213000 +0800" stop="20251229223000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Dedaun Hijau Di Angin Lalu</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jamilah is horrified to discover signs of abuse on Intan, while Hassan warns Dahlan to stop his violent behaviour before it goes too far.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229223000 +0800" stop="20251229233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Operandi Gerhana</title>
    <desc lang="en">Singapore. 1955. Gangland crime threatens to swallow Singapore. After failing to contain the violence for years, the authorities are left with no choice but to jump into the fray- fighting fire with fire. In the wake of riots and rising organised crime with no one left unscathed, two Police Constables, Hazir and Fattah, are given a high priority assignment to investigate the kidnapping of one of their own senior officers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229233000 +0800" stop="20251229233000 +0800" channel="Suria">
    <title lang="en">Berita</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the latest local and international news on Suria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229003000 +0800" stop="20251229010000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229010000 +0800" stop="20251229090000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
    <desc lang="en">End of Transmission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229090000 +0800" stop="20251229093000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Oor Kuruvi</title>
    <desc lang="en">The show format would be that of a Info-ed, hosted by a single compere who would be well versed in Tamil and information savy with great conversation skills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229093000 +0800" stop="20251229100000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Siri…Siri Siri Siri S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Compilation of comedy clips to tickle your laughing bone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229100000 +0800" stop="20251229103000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Indian Beat S16</title>
    <desc lang="en">A bilingual magazine show that serves as a platform by featuring activities and events organized by the various Tamil and Indian ethnic organizations around Singapore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229103000 +0800" stop="20251229110000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Siri…Siri Siri Siri S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Compilation of comedy clips to tickle your laughing bone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229110000 +0800" stop="20251229113000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rasikka Rusikka S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shabby and Prasad kicks off Season 6 and this time a round Rasikka Rusikka goes on a quest to explore budget cuisines.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229113000 +0800" stop="20251229120000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Rasikka Rusikka S6</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shabby and Prasad kicks off Season 6 and this time a round Rasikka Rusikka goes on a quest to explore budget cuisines.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229120000 +0800" stop="20251229143000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Madras To Pondicherry</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mala, a modern college girl witnesses the murder committed by Sudhagar and hops into a bus bound for Pondicherry. Sudhagar follows and tries to kill her on the journey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229143000 +0800" stop="20251229150000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229150000 +0800" stop="20251229160000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Savaal Singapore 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">This game show concept is an adaptation from the English version of We are Singaporeans . All questions and everything about the show will be about Singapore .There will be 6 celebrities in each episode and they will banter with the host and contestants and also ask the questions!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160000 +0800" stop="20251229190000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Priyamaana Thozhi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ashok and Julie are childhood friends. Julie is set to marry Michael, a cricketer who is hoping to get selected in the Indian team, but her wedding plans are threatened when Ashok is selected instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229190000 +0800" stop="20251229193000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Thinna Thinna Aasai</title>
    <desc lang="en">Coriander vadais and stuffed masala eggplant curry. Seafood platters and Soul Kadi. Mumbai, home to one of the best coastal cuisines of India, is the first stop on our host, Spancer's gastronomic journey. In his first ever trip to India, Spancer works his way through a lip-smacking array of local culinary delights, goes into the heart of a quaint fishing village to enjoy a seafood feast, and manages to master a complicated Maharashtrian recipe under the watchful eyes of a local celebrity chef.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229193000 +0800" stop="20251229200000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Thinna Thinna Aasai</title>
    <desc lang="en">Come along on the delicious, scrumptious, mouth-watering, mind-boggling food journey as our host, Spancer, eats his way through the culinary hotspots of southern and western India!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229200000 +0800" stop="20251229203000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Vaan Varu Vaan</title>
    <desc lang="en">VARU, a struggling writer who's trolled for her mediocre stories, is trying to write the greatest love story ever. But each time she tries to write, severe headaches, sleepiness and anything that will make her procrastinate will take over. Meanwhile VIKRAM enters her life. He has loved her from afar as a family friend for many years and now has entered into an arranged marriage alliance with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229203000 +0800" stop="20251229210000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229210000 +0800" stop="20251229213000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Goli Soda: Rising</title>
    <desc lang="en">Enraged by Naidu's murder, the Aachi Mess boys and girls plot to kidnap Ravi. Meanwhile, Janaki receives vital evidence about her father's death from an unexpected source.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229213000 +0800" stop="20251229220000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Koranjeh Velai Niranjeh Ooru S1</title>
    <desc lang="en">A television program where the host, Rabbit Mac takes viewers around Malaysia on a shoestring budget.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229220000 +0800" stop="20251229223000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Aah!</title>
    <desc lang="en">Naren runs a charming little bistro with a spooky reputation. He jokes that it's the haunted atmosphere that attracts customers, but the real secret is his cook, Mother Devi. Her delicious dishes are what truly bring people in. However, Naren has a special talent---he can tell which of his diners are living and which are lingering spirits. Newly hired Priya, the ever-loyal waitress, gets spooked from time to time, but she stays because of her growing affection for Naren.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229223000 +0800" stop="20251229230000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Yaar 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pari receives an unexpected visitor who puts things into perspective for her, causing her to re-evaluate her past actions. Meanwhile, the killer pays Mythilli a visit late at night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229230000 +0800" stop="20251229233000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Mellisai Hits S3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Collection of hit melody songs from 1990s - 2000s.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229233000 +0800" stop="20251229233000 +0800" channel="Vasantham">
    <title lang="en">Seithi</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tamil Seithi focuses primarily on local and international news, information and current affairs. Catch the online news portal at http://seithi.mediacorp.sg/.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229000000 +0800" stop="20251229000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229000300 +0800" stop="20251229010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">No Ordinary Rescue S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Over 3,000 children went missing without a trace, at the turn of the millennium in Shenzhen. Desperate parents use social media to reach out to others who may have seen their missing children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229010000 +0800" stop="20251229020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Belly Of A Nation 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's been a year and some hawkers prospered while others had to consolidate. On the anniversary of their New York branch, the hawkers have to decide whether to stay or go.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229020000 +0800" stop="20251229023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229023000 +0800" stop="20251229030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Hobsessions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two miniaturists shrink reality into magic: Xing Zhilei builds working tiny worlds for cats in China, while Anthony Ong creates Singapore dioramas, including a miniature Jurong East MRT station.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229030000 +0800" stop="20251229040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Extraordinary People</title>
    <desc lang="en">Champions of mental health: Faiza empowers caregivers of people with mental health issues, while Alaric provides a safe space for the marginalised to recover from drug addiction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229040000 +0800" stop="20251229043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229043000 +0800" stop="20251229050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Byte The Habit</title>
    <desc lang="en">Technology has infiltrated our lives. We set off with three families as they uncover their device habits – from bedtime to toilet time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229050000 +0800" stop="20251229060000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">New Stirrings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Episode 2 explores how hawkers reinvent and adapt to modern tastes while balancing growth, change and identity, capturing the evolving flavours of Singapore's hawker culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229060000 +0800" stop="20251229063000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229063000 +0800" stop="20251229070000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Us</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Taipei, we take a scooter tour of Banqiao's traditional Taiwanese fare, join a pair of writers at a retro restaurant for bento Taiwan-style, and hop on a karaoke taxi to visit a Driver's Club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229070000 +0800" stop="20251229073000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229073000 +0800" stop="20251229080000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore After Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">Food technologist Samantha Liew volunteers for Back Alley Barbers to serve migrant workers while award-winning photographer Edwin Koo runs a community project taking portraits of the elderly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229080000 +0800" stop="20251229083000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229083000 +0800" stop="20251229090000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">What's The Big Deal?</title>
    <desc lang="en">They were supposed to be the next smartphones -- devices so small and light, you could wear them. So why isn't our smartwatches that lifechanging yet? Rishi Budhrani finds out on What's the Big Deal?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229090000 +0800" stop="20251229093000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229093000 +0800" stop="20251229100000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Slumfood Millionaire: Provinces</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the Iban people living in Bintulu's industrial zone, a tasty meal is always within reach. The forest is your supermarket. When you forage and grow your own ingredients, you won't go hungry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229100000 +0800" stop="20251229100200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229100200 +0800" stop="20251229110000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">New Stirrings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Episode 2 explores how hawkers reinvent and adapt to modern tastes while balancing growth, change and identity, capturing the evolving flavours of Singapore's hawker culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229110000 +0800" stop="20251229113000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229113000 +0800" stop="20251229120000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Byte The Habit</title>
    <desc lang="en">Devices connect people but does it take away anything in return? Jean challenges the families to replace screen time for "me time" and discovers surprising blind spots in their digital habits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229120000 +0800" stop="20251229123000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229123000 +0800" stop="20251229130000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Tender Loving Food</title>
    <desc lang="en">Creation is an outlet. Food is their comfort. When creative juices flow, rice dumplings become works of art, Malay kuihs turn into beautiful creations and pandan cupcakes are picture perfect products.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229130000 +0800" stop="20251229130200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229130200 +0800" stop="20251229140000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">New Stirrings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Episode 1 explores Singapore's hawker roots through stories of heritage and succession where veteran and new hawkers keep tradition alive in the nation's shared dining halls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229140000 +0800" stop="20251229143000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229143000 +0800" stop="20251229150000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Lunch With Us</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Taipei, we take a scooter tour of Banqiao's traditional Taiwanese fare, join a pair of writers at a retro restaurant for bento Taiwan-style, and hop on a karaoke taxi to visit a Driver's Club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229150000 +0800" stop="20251229153000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229153000 +0800" stop="20251229160000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore After Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">Food technologist Samantha Liew volunteers for Back Alley Barbers to serve migrant workers while award-winning photographer Edwin Koo runs a community project taking portraits of the elderly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160000 +0800" stop="20251229160200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229160200 +0800" stop="20251229170000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Limitless S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following a family legacy, 15-year-old Leomhar Lobrido fights his way from Bago City to an international boxing tournament in Jordan, carrying the hopes and history of his late mum and country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229170000 +0800" stop="20251229173000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229173000 +0800" stop="20251229180000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Slumfood Millionaire: Provinces</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the Iban people living in Bintulu's industrial zone, a tasty meal is always within reach. The forest is your supermarket. When you forage and grow your own ingredients, you won't go hungry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229180000 +0800" stop="20251229183000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Now</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) Non-stop breaking stories, expert analysis and extensive news coverage every hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229183000 +0800" stop="20251229190000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Zero Waste Kitchen</title>
    <desc lang="en">We consume 16kg of fish per person yearly. But host Issac discovers that in one local fish farm, offcuts amount to 30,000 tonnes a year. What mouth-watering recipes using these offcuts can be created?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229190000 +0800" stop="20251229190200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229190200 +0800" stop="20251229200000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The Year Ahead 2026: World</title>
    <desc lang="en">A wrap-up of significant events in 2025 in Singapore and as well as around the world and how they will affect the year ahead. The show takes a look at major developments in areas including security, healthcare, transport and financial technology.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229200000 +0800" stop="20251229203000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229203000 +0800" stop="20251229210000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive</title>
    <desc lang="en">The very first foods fermented by humans, vegetables have been transformed from surplus into fermented products made more nourishing and delicious than ever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229210000 +0800" stop="20251229210200 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229210200 +0800" stop="20251229220000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">New Stirrings</title>
    <desc lang="en">A new generation of hawkers is redefining tradition. From Michelin-trained chefs to robots in the kitchen, showing how creativity and passion are keeping Singapore's hawker spirit alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229220000 +0800" stop="20251229223000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229223000 +0800" stop="20251229230000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Byte The Habit</title>
    <desc lang="en">Devices connect people but does it take away anything in return? Jean challenges the families to replace screen time for "me time" and discovers surprising blind spots in their digital habits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229230000 +0800" stop="20251229230300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">(Live) The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229230300 +0800" stop="20251230000000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">New Stirrings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Episode 2 explores how hawkers reinvent and adapt to modern tastes while balancing growth, change and identity, capturing the evolving flavours of Singapore's hawker culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230000000 +0800" stop="20251230000300 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Headline News</title>
    <desc lang="en">The latest top stories of the hour.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230000300 +0800" stop="20251230010000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">No Ordinary Rescue S2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Why are more mammals stranding on the coast of Taiwan? While in China, thousands of migratory birds fall prey to hunters and illegal trade. These ordinary people are coming together to fight back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230010000 +0800" stop="20251230020000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">The Year Ahead 2026: World</title>
    <desc lang="en">A wrap-up of significant events in 2025 in Singapore and as well as around the world and how they will affect the year ahead. The show takes a look at major developments in areas including security, healthcare, transport and financial technology.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230020000 +0800" stop="20251230023000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Singapore Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">From business to politics, health to technology, the latest news from Singapore and analysis of the impact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230023000 +0800" stop="20251230030000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Sour, Salty &amp; Alive</title>
    <desc lang="en">The very first foods fermented by humans, vegetables have been transformed from surplus into fermented products made more nourishing and delicious than ever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230030000 +0800" stop="20251230040000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Insight</title>
    <desc lang="en">Last year, Japan broke tourism records. It attracted 37 million foreign visitors, the most ever. And now it wants more. But how will the government sell this vision to those who tire of tourists?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230040000 +0800" stop="20251230043000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Asia Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">CNA correspondents bring you the top stories of the day with 'live' reports and interviews to keep you up-to-date on the day's events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251230043000 +0800" stop="20251230050000 +0800" channel="CNA">
    <title lang="en">Byte The Habit</title>
    <desc lang="en">Devices connect people but does it take away anything in return? Jean challenges the families to replace screen time for "me time" and discovers surprising blind spots in their digital habits.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>